[
  {
    "prompt": "Do you like the fast and the furious movies?",
    "response": "To be honest I've never seen any past the first one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "To be honest I've never seen any past the first one.",
    "response": "Me either! But I do like the podcast how did this get made."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me either! But I do like the podcast how did this get made.",
    "response": "Me too! I love listening to them make fun of Vin Deisel."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too! I love listening to them make fun of Vin Deisel.",
    "response": "That is the best part."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That is the best part.",
    "response": "What did you think of Paul Walker?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What did you think of Paul Walker?",
    "response": "Paul Walker was great."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Paul Walker was great.",
    "response": "I agree. I also like the girl who is kind of butch."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I agree. I also like the girl who is kind of butch.",
    "response": "Michelle Rodriguez. Is that the one?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Michelle Rodriguez. Is that the one?",
    "response": "Yes, her! She's great."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is Paul Walker the main guy in The Fast and the Furious?",
    "response": "Yes and Vin Diesel is the other main guy."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes and Vin Diesel is the other main guy.",
    "response": "Is there only one movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is there only one movie?",
    "response": "No. There is quite a few."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No. There is quite a few.",
    "response": "Are the same people in them all?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Are the same people in them all?",
    "response": "Mostly, but they add new characters. The Rock is one of the new guys they put in it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Mostly, but they add new characters. The Rock is one of the new guys they put in it.",
    "response": "Was part 2 good?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Was part 2 good?",
    "response": "It was decent."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was decent.",
    "response": "Did the same guy direct them all?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did the same guy direct them all?",
    "response": "No. The first one was Rob Cohen and Mel City"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you like Fast and Furious?",
    "response": "Yes!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes!",
    "response": "Which is your favorite?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which is your favorite?",
    "response": "I love the first one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I love the first one.",
    "response": "Isn't Vin Diesel so good in those movies?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Isn't Vin Diesel so good in those movies?",
    "response": "Totally he is!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Totally he is!",
    "response": "I want to see it again."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I want to see it again.",
    "response": "We should see it together."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "We should see it together.",
    "response": "Sounds like a plan."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Sounds like a plan.",
    "response": "Alright!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "what do you think about Fast & Furious?",
    "response": "Well, I think it's fast and furious"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, I think it's fast and furious",
    "response": "haha, you're funny, but it's kinda true, the movie series has been fast and furious"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "haha, you're funny, but it's kinda true, the movie series has been fast and furious",
    "response": "indeed. All the car fans must be having an orgasm when watching the movies"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "indeed. All the car fans must be having an orgasm when watching the movies",
    "response": "I don't consider myself a car fan, but I'm visually stunned by those crazy effects"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I don't consider myself a car fan, but I'm visually stunned by those crazy effects",
    "response": "you remember the one where Paul Walker driving across a lifted draw bridge?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "you remember the one where Paul Walker driving across a lifted draw bridge?",
    "response": "oh yeah, I remembe that one so vividly even today, I was watching that scene on my TV"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "oh yeah, I remembe that one so vividly even today, I was watching that scene on my TV",
    "response": "me too, it's sad to see Paul Walker away, now we won't be able to see him again"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "me too, it's sad to see Paul Walker away, now we won't be able to see him again",
    "response": "at least now he rests in heaven now, God bless him"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "at least now he rests in heaven now, God bless him",
    "response": "God bless him"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen the movie Fast and Furious?",
    "response": "Yes. It's been a while."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes. It's been a while.",
    "response": "Who is in it? Name one person."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who is in it? Name one person.",
    "response": "Van Diesel."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Van Diesel.",
    "response": "What year was it released?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What year was it released?",
    "response": "2002."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "2002.",
    "response": "Wrong."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Wrong.",
    "response": "2000?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "2000?",
    "response": "No. It was released in the year 2001."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No. It was released in the year 2001.",
    "response": "That's a long time ago."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "A lot of people I know are big fans of the Fast & Furious series.",
    "response": "I am not one of those people."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I am not one of those people.",
    "response": "Are you serious? I really thought that everyone liked those."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Are you serious? I really thought that everyone liked those.",
    "response": "I'm dead serious. I can't stand those films."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I'm dead serious. I can't stand those films.",
    "response": "Oh, come on! What's so bad about them?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh, come on! What's so bad about them?",
    "response": "They literally took street racing to global warfare. It's just plain dumb if you ask me."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They literally took street racing to global warfare. It's just plain dumb if you ask me.",
    "response": "But it's super fun to watch."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "But it's super fun to watch.",
    "response": "Well, I've never found them fun. Just annoying."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, I've never found them fun. Just annoying.",
    "response": "They at least have a stacked cast, though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They at least have a stacked cast, though.",
    "response": "I can agree with that much, sure."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hi.",
    "response": "Hey."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey.",
    "response": "You see the new fast and furious movie yet?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You see the new fast and furious movie yet?",
    "response": "No I haven't."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No I haven't.",
    "response": "Me either."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me either.",
    "response": "What number are they up to now?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What number are they up to now?",
    "response": "I think it's 8."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think it's 8.",
    "response": "Wow 8 films."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Wow 8 films.",
    "response": "Yeah didn't realize it was that many."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah didn't realize it was that many.",
    "response": "Me either."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "There is something I don't fully understand about 'The Fate of the Furious.'",
    "response": "What would that be?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What would that be?",
    "response": "Why did Charlize Theron's character need Dominic Toretto for her plan?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why did Charlize Theron's character need Dominic Toretto for her plan?",
    "response": "I have no idea."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I have no idea.",
    "response": "If you think about it, Dom's only skill is driving.  What use did a super hacker have of a driver?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "If you think about it, Dom's only skill is driving.  What use did a super hacker have of a driver?",
    "response": "Dom is also a good fighter, and is the only one who could stop his crew."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Dom is also a good fighter, and is the only one who could stop his crew.",
    "response": "But if Charlize's character didn't recruit Dom in the first place, the crew never would have intervened."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "But if Charlize's character didn't recruit Dom in the first place, the crew never would have intervened.",
    "response": "Oh, and then her plan would not have been ruined.  I think you're onto something."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh, and then her plan would not have been ruined.  I think you're onto something.",
    "response": "I'm glad I could get that off my chest.  The rest of the movie, after accepting that premise, was really fun."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I'm glad I could get that off my chest.  The rest of the movie, after accepting that premise, was really fun.",
    "response": "The action sequences were so well shot, and the set-pieces were executed flawlessly!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "so which one is your favorite fast and furious movie?",
    "response": "I think it is 2 fast 2 furious."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think it is 2 fast 2 furious.",
    "response": "Oh, I think that is the only part in which there is no vin diesel"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh, I think that is the only part in which there is no vin diesel",
    "response": "no, I think tokyo drift is another one without vin diesel"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "no, I think tokyo drift is another one without vin diesel",
    "response": "oh, are you sure?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "oh, are you sure?",
    "response": "yes, I am pretty sure."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "yes, I am pretty sure.",
    "response": "I thought tokyo drift had vin diesel, may be briefly."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I thought tokyo drift had vin diesel, may be briefly.",
    "response": "actually it is the first movie in which they show jason statham."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "actually it is the first movie in which they show jason statham.",
    "response": "really? When did they show jason statham in tokyo drift?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "really? When did they show jason statham in tokyo drift?",
    "response": "It was in post credit."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen Fast & Furious 6 before?",
    "response": "Which one is that?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which one is that?",
    "response": "It has all the main cast along with Luke Evans."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It has all the main cast along with Luke Evans.",
    "response": "I may have seen it, does Evans play the villain?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I may have seen it, does Evans play the villain?",
    "response": "Yea, he is Luke Hobbs and the crew get hired to take him down."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, he is Luke Hobbs and the crew get hired to take him down.",
    "response": "Is The Rock in this one?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is The Rock in this one?",
    "response": "Yea, he is the agent who offers them a deal if they help."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, he is the agent who offers them a deal if they help.",
    "response": "Yea, I remember that one, it was a fun watch."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, I remember that one, it was a fun watch.",
    "response": "Yea, one of my favorites of the series."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, one of my favorites of the series.",
    "response": "Yea, it is one of my favorites too."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What was your favorite 'Fast & Furious' movie?",
    "response": "That's a tough question to answer.  I loved Five, but Seven was so emotional."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's a tough question to answer.  I loved Five, but Seven was so emotional.",
    "response": "Yea, that last scene was such a touching goodbye to Paul Walker and his character."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, that last scene was such a touching goodbye to Paul Walker and his character.",
    "response": "I'd say it's a tie between those two.  How about you?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I'd say it's a tie between those two.  How about you?",
    "response": "I actually really loved the first two."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I actually really loved the first two.",
    "response": "You mean when it used to be about street racing?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You mean when it used to be about street racing?",
    "response": "Exactly.  That was always the main appeal for me."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Exactly.  That was always the main appeal for me.",
    "response": "They still have racing."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They still have racing.",
    "response": "They do, but the racing is portrayed almost like an afterthought."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They do, but the racing is portrayed almost like an afterthought.",
    "response": "You have a point.  After Tokyo Drift, that street racing element started to get placed in the background."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you like the love theme in the first Fast and the Furious?",
    "response": "Yes. It added a lot of depth"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes. It added a lot of depth",
    "response": "I was heartbroken when they went their seperate ways."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I was heartbroken when they went their seperate ways.",
    "response": "Yes. But, they came back together in the end."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes. But, they came back together in the end.",
    "response": "I liked the tension between Paul Walker and Vin Diesel."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I liked the tension between Paul Walker and Vin Diesel.",
    "response": "That was definitely the main conflict in the film."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That was definitely the main conflict in the film.",
    "response": "The acting was really good."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The acting was really good.",
    "response": "Yes. Each actor brought their all to the movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes. Each actor brought their all to the movie.",
    "response": "I think this is the best car movie ever."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think this is the best car movie ever.",
    "response": "I agree. It is awesome and one of the best car movies ever."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is your favorite movie about cars?",
    "response": "Eh their is not to many of them"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Eh their is not to many of them",
    "response": "I like fast and furious"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like fast and furious",
    "response": "I only like one of them"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I only like one of them",
    "response": "Which one do you like"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which one do you like",
    "response": "The one that is a spinoff i think"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The one that is a spinoff i think",
    "response": "What one is that man"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What one is that man",
    "response": "I like tokyo drift"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like tokyo drift",
    "response": "That one was pretty lit i mus say"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That one was pretty lit i mus say",
    "response": "The rest do not do it for me"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Let us talk about the Fast and the Furious.",
    "response": "Okay!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Okay!",
    "response": "Which is your favorite one out of all of them?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which is your favorite one out of all of them?",
    "response": "I like number 6."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like number 6.",
    "response": "Really?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Really?",
    "response": "Yeah I think it was very interesting."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah I think it was very interesting.",
    "response": "I was not on the edge of my seat for that one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I was not on the edge of my seat for that one.",
    "response": "Well that is you though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well that is you though.",
    "response": "Very true."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Very true.",
    "response": "It was great talking to you!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How did you like fast and furious 1?",
    "response": "I liked it a lot."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I liked it a lot.",
    "response": "Yea, I feel its the best of the franchise"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, I feel its the best of the franchise",
    "response": "The newer movies have too much action."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The newer movies have too much action.",
    "response": "The newer ones have a very different feel to the first few films."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The newer ones have a very different feel to the first few films.",
    "response": "Yea, but the actors pull it off very well."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, but the actors pull it off very well.",
    "response": "I do miss Paul Walker."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I do miss Paul Walker.",
    "response": "He was a very good reason for why the franchise worked."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He was a very good reason for why the franchise worked.",
    "response": "The cars really make the movies excitiing."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The cars really make the movies excitiing.",
    "response": "I like Vin diesels car in the 1st movie the best"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who's your favorite Fast and Furious character?",
    "response": "Hobbs, without a doubt."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hobbs, without a doubt.",
    "response": "Hobbs is played by Ludacris?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hobbs is played by Ludacris?",
    "response": "No, Agent Hobbs, played by the Rock.  Who is your favorite?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No, Agent Hobbs, played by the Rock.  Who is your favorite?",
    "response": "Either Han or his girlfriend."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Either Han or his girlfriend.",
    "response": "Yeah, she died to save him."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, she died to save him.",
    "response": "I cried so hard when both of them died.  I didn't know why they had to kill them off."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I cried so hard when both of them died.  I didn't know why they had to kill them off.",
    "response": "I can't wait to watch the new one"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I can't wait to watch the new one",
    "response": "I wonder how they're going to deal with the Paul Walker situation."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I wonder how they're going to deal with the Paul Walker situation.",
    "response": "But they already did.  In the last one he retired with the girl and his kid, that was the send."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You've seen 2 Fast 2 Furious right?",
    "response": "Yes I have it was one of my favorites."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes I have it was one of my favorites.",
    "response": "Do you remember the scene with the yacht?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you remember the scene with the yacht?",
    "response": "I don't recall that one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I don't recall that one.",
    "response": "Oh man, that was an awesome scene especially where the Yacht is escaping and Brian jumped the car onto the Yacht."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh man, that was an awesome scene especially where the Yacht is escaping and Brian jumped the car onto the Yacht.",
    "response": "That's right, that scene was absolutely epic."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's right, that scene was absolutely epic.",
    "response": "Wasn't Roman with him in the car?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Wasn't Roman with him in the car?",
    "response": "I believe so."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I believe so.",
    "response": "I just remember someone screaming and that must have been Roman."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I just remember someone screaming and that must have been Roman.",
    "response": "Yes it was."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I saw Furious 7 last night.",
    "response": "I hear they got a new director."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I hear they got a new director.",
    "response": "James Wan, replacing Justin Lin."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "James Wan, replacing Justin Lin.",
    "response": "Didn't Walker die before finishing the movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Didn't Walker die before finishing the movie?",
    "response": "Yes.  They used his younger brothers as stand ins to finish."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes.  They used his younger brothers as stand ins to finish.",
    "response": "Crazy.  What's the plot?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Crazy.  What's the plot?",
    "response": "The bad guy from 6 (Shaw) has a brother who vows vengeance on the gang."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The bad guy from 6 (Shaw) has a brother who vows vengeance on the gang.",
    "response": "Is Dwayne Johnson in this?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is Dwayne Johnson in this?",
    "response": "Yes.  He had a schedule conflict with Hercules but got it straightened out."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes.  He had a schedule conflict with Hercules but got it straightened out.",
    "response": "Nice.  I read the movie had  tribute to Walker."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think Fast and Furious: Tokyo Drift was a horrid movie.",
    "response": "Really? I thought the movie was pretty good. Why didn't you like it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Really? I thought the movie was pretty good. Why didn't you like it?",
    "response": "The acting was pathetic and it just really didn't fit in with the other two. I mean come on Paul and Vin were nowhere in it and their interation made the ones before."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The acting was pathetic and it just really didn't fit in with the other two. I mean come on Paul and Vin were nowhere in it and their interation made the ones before.",
    "response": "Well, I guess you have a point, but I thought the change of scenery was pretty cool and the cultural shift intrigued me."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, I guess you have a point, but I thought the change of scenery was pretty cool and the cultural shift intrigued me.",
    "response": "The change in scenery doesn't excuse that kids horrible accent and just all around bad acting skills."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The change in scenery doesn't excuse that kids horrible accent and just all around bad acting skills.",
    "response": "Well, which one did you like the most?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, which one did you like the most?",
    "response": "I really think the original Fast and Furious was the best out of all of them. You got the whole feeling of Paul Walker and his loyalty first to the police and then to Vin"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I really think the original Fast and Furious was the best out of all of them. You got the whole feeling of Paul Walker and his loyalty first to the police and then to Vin",
    "response": "Oh ya! Isn't that when the term Busta came into play? During that movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh ya! Isn't that when the term Busta came into play? During that movie?",
    "response": "Yes! It Did! When they were at the party Dom was like Busta id the only one that kept me outta cuffs! That was great!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes! It Did! When they were at the party Dom was like Busta id the only one that kept me outta cuffs! That was great!",
    "response": "I really should watch the first one again it's been so long!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I want to see the fate pf the furious so bad",
    "response": "I kind of want to see it"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I kind of want to see it",
    "response": "Ive been waiting for it to come out"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Ive been waiting for it to come out",
    "response": "I wonder what it will be like eithout paul walker"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I wonder what it will be like eithout paul walker",
    "response": "Im thinking its going to be sad"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Im thinking its going to be sad",
    "response": "Thats what i was thinking"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Thats what i was thinking",
    "response": "But i still want to see it"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "But i still want to see it",
    "response": "I will probably watch it out of curiousity"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I will probably watch it out of curiousity",
    "response": "You will probably like it"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You will probably like it",
    "response": "Maybe"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How well do you think The Rock fits into the Fast & Furious movies?",
    "response": "He is the only person I can see playing Hobbs in those movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He is the only person I can see playing Hobbs in those movies.",
    "response": "He does bring a certain level of awesome to the film."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He does bring a certain level of awesome to the film.",
    "response": "Totally, he's strong enough to be menacing but still able to make the jokes seem realistic."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Totally, he's strong enough to be menacing but still able to make the jokes seem realistic.",
    "response": "He usually does play big goofy guys that still ends up kicking your teeth in."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He usually does play big goofy guys that still ends up kicking your teeth in.",
    "response": "What was your favorite Hobbs moment, any film?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What was your favorite Hobbs moment, any film?",
    "response": "It would have to be when he was in prison with Statham."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It would have to be when he was in prison with Statham.",
    "response": "When Jason was saying how easy it would be on to beat up The Rock?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When Jason was saying how easy it would be on to beat up The Rock?",
    "response": "Yeah, then Hobbs just ribs the bench out of the wall and starts lifting it like weights."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, then Hobbs just ribs the bench out of the wall and starts lifting it like weights.",
    "response": "The look on Jason's face was priceless; of course, The Rocks face was just as good."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I love the Fast and Furious movies.",
    "response": "Why? It's mindless garbage."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why? It's mindless garbage.",
    "response": "I think it's fun and enjoy the action."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think it's fun and enjoy the action.",
    "response": "I think it's made for idiots. I don't get the appeal."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think it's made for idiots. I don't get the appeal.",
    "response": "It's supposed to be ridiculous. It's over the top and the corny dialogue makes it even better."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It's supposed to be ridiculous. It's over the top and the corny dialogue makes it even better.",
    "response": "The only reason I'd watch it is because Ludacris is in it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The only reason I'd watch it is because Ludacris is in it.",
    "response": "Yeah, he's great in all of them. I think they're all worth watching besides Tokyo Drift."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, he's great in all of them. I think they're all worth watching besides Tokyo Drift.",
    "response": "Maybe one day if I catch one of the movies on TV..."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Maybe one day if I catch one of the movies on TV...",
    "response": "I highly recommend 2 Fast 2 Furious. That's the funniest one by far."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I highly recommend 2 Fast 2 Furious. That's the funniest one by far.",
    "response": "I'll remember that, but don't get your hopes up."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How was the Fate of the Furious?",
    "response": "It was good. The submarine scene was crazy."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was good. The submarine scene was crazy.",
    "response": "Which sequel did Gal Gadot's character die again?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which sequel did Gal Gadot's character die again?",
    "response": "It was in Fast and Furious 6. Pretty sad."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was in Fast and Furious 6. Pretty sad.",
    "response": "Roman Pearce has to be the funniest character in the Fast & Furious Franchise."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Roman Pearce has to be the funniest character in the Fast & Furious Franchise.",
    "response": "His best scenes were with Paul Walker's character."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "His best scenes were with Paul Walker's character.",
    "response": "What is the best car chase in the fast & furious films?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the best car chase in the fast & furious films?",
    "response": "It has to be the tank chase in Fast & Furious 6."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It has to be the tank chase in Fast & Furious 6.",
    "response": "Dwayne Johnson stole the movie in Fast Five."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Dwayne Johnson stole the movie in Fast Five.",
    "response": "His fight scene with Vin Diesel was epic."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey man",
    "response": "Hey bro"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey bro",
    "response": "I am thinking of starting the fast and furious series"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I am thinking of starting the fast and furious series",
    "response": "They looking interesting to youu?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They looking interesting to youu?",
    "response": "They look like something i would like"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They look like something i would like",
    "response": "Well i can say they are pretty decent movies"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well i can say they are pretty decent movies",
    "response": "Well that is glad to hear"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well that is glad to hear",
    "response": "You should start at the first and do not skip any of them though"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You should start at the first and do not skip any of them though",
    "response": "I was actually gonna ask thanks for the advice"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I was actually gonna ask thanks for the advice",
    "response": "No problem man"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you like the Fast and Furious movies?",
    "response": "Yeah I do, but I liked them more when they were more about cars."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah I do, but I liked them more when they were more about cars.",
    "response": "Yeah, they stopped that around the fifth one it seems like."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, they stopped that around the fifth one it seems like.",
    "response": "Yeah, once the Rock got involved in the franchise it became more about action than racing."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, once the Rock got involved in the franchise it became more about action than racing.",
    "response": "It is not as good without Paul Walker."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It is not as good without Paul Walker.",
    "response": "I know right, it is just not the same with Bryan in them."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know right, it is just not the same with Bryan in them.",
    "response": "I think when Paul Walker passed away, they should of just ended the series there."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think when Paul Walker passed away, they should of just ended the series there.",
    "response": "Yeah, they had a really good send-off for him in the seventh movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, they had a really good send-off for him in the seventh movie.",
    "response": "That song they played at the end almost made me cry."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That song they played at the end almost made me cry.",
    "response": "It was the saddest part of any Fast and Furious movie, I can tell you that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "do you think jason statham was a good decision to include in fast and furious series?",
    "response": "I think it was totally worth it. He is awesome, I am huge fan of him."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think it was totally worth it. He is awesome, I am huge fan of him.",
    "response": "I am a bit skeptical about him, I don't know whether it's him or it's the role they assigned him."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I am a bit skeptical about him, I don't know whether it's him or it's the role they assigned him.",
    "response": "Why, what's wrong with him or his role?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why, what's wrong with him or his role?",
    "response": "I feel that somehow he is misfit for fast and furious series."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I feel that somehow he is misfit for fast and furious series.",
    "response": "Really? Why do you feel so? Any particular reason?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Really? Why do you feel so? Any particular reason?",
    "response": "I mean they have portrayed him as this invincible guy who can do anything."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I mean they have portrayed him as this invincible guy who can do anything.",
    "response": "I think almost everyone in fast and furious series is portrayed that way."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think almost everyone in fast and furious series is portrayed that way.",
    "response": "Well, Not everyone, Maybe yes, But his character is way too off the ground."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, Not everyone, Maybe yes, But his character is way too off the ground.",
    "response": "I think it is more subjective matter."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you remember which Fast and Furious didn't have Jordana Brewster?",
    "response": "I think she was in all of them except 2 Fast 2 Furious and the most recent one, The Fate of the Furious."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think she was in all of them except 2 Fast 2 Furious and the most recent one, The Fate of the Furious.",
    "response": "I wonder if she'll ever return. I really like her character of Mia Torretto."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I wonder if she'll ever return. I really like her character of Mia Torretto.",
    "response": "Same here, I'm a big fan of hers. I can understand how they would feel it being out of place if she was in there without Paul Walker's Brian."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Same here, I'm a big fan of hers. I can understand how they would feel it being out of place if she was in there without Paul Walker's Brian.",
    "response": "Such a tragic lost. I know what you mean. It does seem with every Fast and Furious they're introducing a new character."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Such a tragic lost. I know what you mean. It does seem with every Fast and Furious they're introducing a new character.",
    "response": "That's how you keep a franchise going! You keep the main stars and you slowly introduce new ones so the audience can grow attached!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's how you keep a franchise going! You keep the main stars and you slowly introduce new ones so the audience can grow attached!",
    "response": "I am definitely glad the Rock got to be a part of the universe. Ever since Fast 5 I've been on the Rock train the whole way!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I am definitely glad the Rock got to be a part of the universe. Ever since Fast 5 I've been on the Rock train the whole way!",
    "response": "The Rock is great! He's beyond ridiculous as each movie goes on but in a fun positive way."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The Rock is great! He's beyond ridiculous as each movie goes on but in a fun positive way.",
    "response": "I hope he stays with the franchise until the 10th? I think that's how many they said they were going to make."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I hope he stays with the franchise until the 10th? I think that's how many they said they were going to make.",
    "response": "I heard 10 also. I bet if they continue doing well at the box office we'll get spin offs. That'll be fun for all Fast and Furious fans!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey, you really like the \"Fast and Furious\" movies don't you?",
    "response": "Oh, yeah, for sure! They are some of favorite movies! Did you see \"The Fate of the Furious\" yet?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh, yeah, for sure! They are some of favorite movies! Did you see \"The Fate of the Furious\" yet?",
    "response": "No, not yet, but I thought I would ask you about it. Did you like it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No, not yet, but I thought I would ask you about it. Did you like it?",
    "response": "Oh yeah, it was awesome! I really like it when the movies kind of take Dom and the team all across the globe; it really gives the stories an \"epic adventure\" kind of feel."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh yeah, it was awesome! I really like it when the movies kind of take Dom and the team all across the globe; it really gives the stories an \"epic adventure\" kind of feel.",
    "response": "Cool! Where did they go in this one?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Cool! Where did they go in this one?",
    "response": "Well, I don't want to spoil too much, but they go pretty much everywhere in this one, including Cuba, Russia, and New York."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, I don't want to spoil too much, but they go pretty much everywhere in this one, including Cuba, Russia, and New York.",
    "response": "Wow, that's pretty awesome. I am guessing there are some crazy chase scenes like always too, right?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Wow, that's pretty awesome. I am guessing there are some crazy chase scenes like always too, right?",
    "response": "Oh yeah! There is a crazy scene involving a submarine in Russia that will totally blow your mind!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh yeah! There is a crazy scene involving a submarine in Russia that will totally blow your mind!",
    "response": "Wow! I really have to see it! Just when you think Dom has done it all, it pulls off some even crazier stunt!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Wow! I really have to see it! Just when you think Dom has done it all, it pulls off some even crazier stunt!",
    "response": "For sure! This one even tops Furious 7, and that is really saying something!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey there.",
    "response": "Hi."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hi.",
    "response": "Have you seen a fast and furious movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen a fast and furious movie?",
    "response": "Yeah I think I've seen them all except for the newest one that is out now."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah I think I've seen them all except for the newest one that is out now.",
    "response": "What was your least favorite one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What was your least favorite one.",
    "response": "Tokyo Drift was pretty bad."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Tokyo Drift was pretty bad.",
    "response": "Was that the one without all the main characters?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Was that the one without all the main characters?",
    "response": "Yeah.  Also had lil' bow wow."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah.  Also had lil' bow wow.",
    "response": "oh man."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "oh man.",
    "response": "yeah pretty bad."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is your favorite scene in the series",
    "response": "The one in the second movie with the break in"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The one in the second movie with the break in",
    "response": "That is one tight scene"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That is one tight scene",
    "response": "I honestly am impressed with it"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I honestly am impressed with it",
    "response": "I also like the chase scenes"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I also like the chase scenes",
    "response": "Those are intense like nail biting"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Those are intense like nail biting",
    "response": "I really love the tensity of them"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I really love the tensity of them",
    "response": "I hope the series keeps going"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I hope the series keeps going",
    "response": "same dude"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "same dude",
    "response": "It is one of my favorite series"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Whats your favorite movie?",
    "response": "Definitely the fast and the furious"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Definitely the fast and the furious",
    "response": "Those are great"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Those are great",
    "response": "They have so much action"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They have so much action",
    "response": "I love watching the street races in them"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I love watching the street races in them",
    "response": "I know it gives you a thrill that you dont get in real life"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know it gives you a thrill that you dont get in real life",
    "response": "Exactly"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Exactly",
    "response": "Its so fun to watch"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Its so fun to watch",
    "response": "Especially winning or losing cars"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Especially winning or losing cars",
    "response": "Its so tense"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen any of the Fast and Furious Movies?",
    "response": "Yea, it is my favorite series of movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, it is my favorite series of movies.",
    "response": "I really like Vin Diesel in the movies. Who is your favorite character?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I really like Vin Diesel in the movies. Who is your favorite character?",
    "response": "Paul Walker."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Paul Walker.",
    "response": "Yea. I really like him too."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea. I really like him too.",
    "response": "It is such a shame he passed away during filming."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It is such a shame he passed away during filming.",
    "response": "I was so sad to hear that he passed."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I was so sad to hear that he passed.",
    "response": "Me too. I know people that cried."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too. I know people that cried.",
    "response": "I though it was really cool that they let his brother film after he passed."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I though it was really cool that they let his brother film after he passed.",
    "response": "I didn't know the did that. That is really awesome."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen any of the Fast & Furious movies?",
    "response": "Yeah, I saw the most recent one that came out in the theaters."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, I saw the most recent one that came out in the theaters.",
    "response": "What is that one called?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is that one called?",
    "response": "The Fate of the Furious."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The Fate of the Furious.",
    "response": "Was it any good?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Was it any good?",
    "response": "Yeah, it was awesome."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, it was awesome.",
    "response": "Wasn't The Rock in that one?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Wasn't The Rock in that one?",
    "response": "The Rock and also Charlize Theron."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The Rock and also Charlize Theron.",
    "response": "I've only seen the first one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I've only seen the first one.",
    "response": "I've seen all of them."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hi.",
    "response": "Hi."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hi.",
    "response": "Have you seen all of the fast and furious movies?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen all of the fast and furious movies?",
    "response": "No I haven't seen them all I don't think."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No I haven't seen them all I don't think.",
    "response": "Do you have a least favorite movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you have a least favorite movie?",
    "response": "Well the second one was pretty bad."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well the second one was pretty bad.",
    "response": "That's the one with Ludacris?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's the one with Ludacris?",
    "response": "Yeah that's right.  It was pretty bad."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah that's right.  It was pretty bad.",
    "response": "I don't know if I saw that one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I don't know if I saw that one.",
    "response": "I wouldn't bother."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey, did you see the latest one, Fate of the Furious?",
    "response": "Yeah, I hated Charlize Theron's character."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, I hated Charlize Theron's character.",
    "response": "What about Dom, did you really think he went bad again?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What about Dom, did you really think he went bad again?",
    "response": "No, not for a minute. I was like, he doesn't have a choice!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No, not for a minute. I was like, he doesn't have a choice!",
    "response": "I don't get what Dom trusted Jason Statham's character with that though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I don't get what Dom trusted Jason Statham's character with that though.",
    "response": "Yeah, didn't he kill Dom's Asian friend?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, didn't he kill Dom's Asian friend?",
    "response": "That scene in Cuba was awesome, man. When the car was about to explode?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That scene in Cuba was awesome, man. When the car was about to explode?",
    "response": "Yeah, there was flame coming through the window and Dom was just like, \"Almost there!\" Haha."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, there was flame coming through the window and Dom was just like, \"Almost there!\" Haha.",
    "response": "The submarine! Tyrese Gibson knocking that guy out with the car door!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The submarine! Tyrese Gibson knocking that guy out with the car door!",
    "response": "Yeah, for once he's not just the comedic relief. He was like, \"How am I number 11 on the top ten most wanted list?\""
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I liked Fast Five, but miss the focus on street racing.",
    "response": "Me too, but I can forgive it for that film, it was so good and funny even."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too, but I can forgive it for that film, it was so good and funny even.",
    "response": "I think it was the one in the series that made the most money."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think it was the one in the series that made the most money.",
    "response": "I think you are right."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think you are right.",
    "response": "I wonder if you asked the actors if it would be their favorite."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I wonder if you asked the actors if it would be their favorite.",
    "response": "I think Vin Diesel has stated that it is, but I'm not sure, I'd have to look it up."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think Vin Diesel has stated that it is, but I'm not sure, I'd have to look it up.",
    "response": "What an insanely fun set of movies to work on, I bet it would be a hard choice for any of the actors to pick a favorite."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What an insanely fun set of movies to work on, I bet it would be a hard choice for any of the actors to pick a favorite.",
    "response": "I think it would be more fun to be a stunt driver on those films!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think it would be more fun to be a stunt driver on those films!",
    "response": "True, I wonder if any of the stunt drivers have been hurt."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "True, I wonder if any of the stunt drivers have been hurt.",
    "response": "I bet insurance would take good care of them if they were."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey man i got to ask something i cannot figure out",
    "response": "What is on your mind"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is on your mind",
    "response": "well i am trying to recall a specific actor"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "well i am trying to recall a specific actor",
    "response": "Well what movie"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well what movie",
    "response": "The guy who died who played on fast and the furious"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The guy who died who played on fast and the furious",
    "response": "Do you mean paul walker"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you mean paul walker",
    "response": "Yeah him he was a pretty chill actor in the movies"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah him he was a pretty chill actor in the movies",
    "response": "Overall yea he was a good actor"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Overall yea he was a good actor",
    "response": "I wish he lived to play in the rest he would make them much better"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I wish he lived to play in the rest he would make them much better",
    "response": "Definitely he would"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Are you a fan of the Fast and Furious movies?",
    "response": "Oh, yeah! I love them."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh, yeah! I love them.",
    "response": "Which one is your favorite?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which one is your favorite?",
    "response": "I would say the first, but I also like Furious 7."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I would say the first, but I also like Furious 7.",
    "response": "What's you're favorite scene?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What's you're favorite scene?",
    "response": "Hard to say. One of my favorites is when they drive the semi backwards."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hard to say. One of my favorites is when they drive the semi backwards.",
    "response": "Oh, yeah! That's intense. Who is your favorite character?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh, yeah! That's intense. Who is your favorite character?",
    "response": "I would say Dominic Toretto, played by Vin Diesel."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I would say Dominic Toretto, played by Vin Diesel.",
    "response": "I don't mind that the series is not super realistic. I see the racing as more of a form of artistic expression in cinema."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I don't mind that the series is not super realistic. I see the racing as more of a form of artistic expression in cinema.",
    "response": "I agree! It's a visual painting."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you see all of the Fast & Furious movies?",
    "response": "I have seen most of them."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I have seen most of them.",
    "response": "Which ones have you not watched?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which ones have you not watched?",
    "response": "I did not see Toyko drift or 2 Fast 2 Furious"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I did not see Toyko drift or 2 Fast 2 Furious",
    "response": "But you saw all the other ones?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "But you saw all the other ones?",
    "response": "Yes. I know it is odd to jump them like that but oh well."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes. I know it is odd to jump them like that but oh well.",
    "response": "Do you think they should have continued on after Paul Walker passed away?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you think they should have continued on after Paul Walker passed away?",
    "response": "I think that finishing the movie they were making was the right thing to do."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think that finishing the movie they were making was the right thing to do.",
    "response": "How many more do you think they will make?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How many more do you think they will make?",
    "response": "Who knows! As long as they keep making money!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you like Fast and Furious movies?",
    "response": "Yes.  Theyre great."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes.  Theyre great.",
    "response": "What is your favorite?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is your favorite?",
    "response": "I think Tokyo Drift."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think Tokyo Drift.",
    "response": "Oh yeah. the cars are amazing"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh yeah. the cars are amazing",
    "response": "I love the japanese culture."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I love the japanese culture.",
    "response": "It was cool.  The drifting was crazy."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was cool.  The drifting was crazy.",
    "response": "I would have crashed."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I would have crashed.",
    "response": "I want to learn."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I want to learn.",
    "response": "Lets watch it later."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I saw Fast and Furious last night.",
    "response": "Not to be confused with The Fast and the Furious?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Not to be confused with The Fast and the Furious?",
    "response": "Right, this is number four."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Right, this is number four.",
    "response": "Are Vinny Diesel and Paul Walker in it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Are Vinny Diesel and Paul Walker in it?",
    "response": "Yes."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes.",
    "response": "What happens in the movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What happens in the movie?",
    "response": "Walker and Diesel go after a drug lord."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Walker and Diesel go after a drug lord.",
    "response": "Is Letty still there?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is Letty still there?",
    "response": "Yes, played by Michelle Rodriguez."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, played by Michelle Rodriguez.",
    "response": "She is hot."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you think fast and furious movies are becoming repetitive?",
    "response": "Well, I certainly do feel that to a certain extent."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, I certainly do feel that to a certain extent.",
    "response": "I mean I can say for sure that last three movies have almost same story."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I mean I can say for sure that last three movies have almost same story.",
    "response": "I think what you are forgetting is in action movies, story is almost always the same."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think what you are forgetting is in action movies, story is almost always the same.",
    "response": "Well, I agree to it only partially."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, I agree to it only partially.",
    "response": "Why only partially?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why only partially?",
    "response": "I mean there has been action movies which had unique and solid story."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I mean there has been action movies which had unique and solid story.",
    "response": "I think the first fast and furious was one of it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think the first fast and furious was one of it.",
    "response": "Yes, because there were no fast and furious before part one, Obviously."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, because there were no fast and furious before part one, Obviously.",
    "response": "I think that is the common issue with movie series."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen all the Fast and Furious movies. I have seen them all at least once.",
    "response": "Yes, I have seen each of them during opening week. I love the action and the cars."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, I have seen each of them during opening week. I love the action and the cars.",
    "response": "I thought it was sad that they lost Paul Walker but I think they handled it well."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I thought it was sad that they lost Paul Walker but I think they handled it well.",
    "response": "Yes, I agree. They did a nice wrap up on his storyline for the fans."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, I agree. They did a nice wrap up on his storyline for the fans.",
    "response": "Man, when Dom drove off in one direction and Brian the other at the end I was in tears."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Man, when Dom drove off in one direction and Brian the other at the end I was in tears.",
    "response": "To be frank that is not why I go to those movies. It is all about the cars and the capers they pull."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "To be frank that is not why I go to those movies. It is all about the cars and the capers they pull.",
    "response": "They have some of the greatest car stunts I have ever seen. I love to watch it on the big screen."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They have some of the greatest car stunts I have ever seen. I love to watch it on the big screen.",
    "response": "There is nothing like it. The sound of the cars racing and chasing is amazing."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "There is nothing like it. The sound of the cars racing and chasing is amazing.",
    "response": "The characters are all well done, but the cars are the stars as far as I am concerned."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The characters are all well done, but the cars are the stars as far as I am concerned.",
    "response": "As long as they keep topping themselves with those stunts they will have a fan in me."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "So what's your favorite Fast & Furious movie?",
    "response": "I have to give that to Furious 7."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I have to give that to Furious 7.",
    "response": "Same here. What's your reason?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Same here. What's your reason?",
    "response": "For me, it holds a special place in my heart because it was the sendoff film for Brian."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "For me, it holds a special place in my heart because it was the sendoff film for Brian.",
    "response": "Was he your favorite character?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Was he your favorite character?",
    "response": "Yes, ever since the first one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, ever since the first one.",
    "response": "It was a really touching sendoff to see him go off and be a father."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was a really touching sendoff to see him go off and be a father.",
    "response": "Yeah. I'm tearing up just thinking about it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah. I'm tearing up just thinking about it.",
    "response": "Man, you're gonna make me cry by saying that!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Man, you're gonna make me cry by saying that!",
    "response": "I'm not crying, you're crying!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Can you believe how many fast and the furious movies there are?",
    "response": "I know, it\u2019s almost crazy that they keep making them but they are so good!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know, it\u2019s almost crazy that they keep making them but they are so good!",
    "response": "Which one is your favorite and which one is your least favorite?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which one is your favorite and which one is your least favorite?",
    "response": "I would say number 1 is my favorite because it\u2019s the original and number 2nis my least favorite?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I would say number 1 is my favorite because it\u2019s the original and number 2nis my least favorite?",
    "response": "Really? You don\u2019t like number 2?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Really? You don\u2019t like number 2?",
    "response": "I thought it had the worst acting and the bad guy was not a good bad guy."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I thought it had the worst acting and the bad guy was not a good bad guy.",
    "response": "I know what you mean, the bad guy is a little weak in that movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know what you mean, the bad guy is a little weak in that movie.",
    "response": "What about you? What\u2019s your favorite?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What about you? What\u2019s your favorite?",
    "response": "I would have to say number 6! I don\u2019t know why, it just is my favorite."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I would have to say number 6! I don\u2019t know why, it just is my favorite.",
    "response": "Yes, I know what you mean, number 6 has a great story line."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen the new Fast & Furious movie yet?",
    "response": "That's the one where Dom switches sides right?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's the one where Dom switches sides right?",
    "response": "Yeah. I positively loved it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah. I positively loved it.",
    "response": "I haven't really got to see it just yet."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I haven't really got to see it just yet.",
    "response": "Oh man you are missing out."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh man you are missing out.",
    "response": "I know. The trailer look amazing."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know. The trailer look amazing.",
    "response": "You need to come over and watch it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You need to come over and watch it.",
    "response": "Dude I am up for that. I want to see what happens with that sub"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Dude I am up for that. I want to see what happens with that sub",
    "response": "You're going to love it. I really miss Brian though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You're going to love it. I really miss Brian though.",
    "response": "Totally. It was a big lose to them."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who is your favorite fast and furious character?",
    "response": "My favorite character is Dom. Specifically in the fate of the furious."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "My favorite character is Dom. Specifically in the fate of the furious.",
    "response": "Is that the movie, where Dom turns against his entire family?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is that the movie, where Dom turns against his entire family?",
    "response": "He doesn't turn against his family, he finds out he has a new member of his family who is being threatened and has to protect him."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He doesn't turn against his family, he finds out he has a new member of his family who is being threatened and has to protect him.",
    "response": "Does he protect his new member of the family?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Does he protect his new member of the family?",
    "response": "He does by pretending to be a bad guy and his wife is the only person who believes is still good."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He does by pretending to be a bad guy and his wife is the only person who believes is still good.",
    "response": "Dom is always doing the right thing even if you can't see it at the time."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Dom is always doing the right thing even if you can't see it at the time.",
    "response": "Yes he does, he always puts him family first, now matter what."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes he does, he always puts him family first, now matter what.",
    "response": "Was their any other parts that you liked in the movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Was their any other parts that you liked in the movie?",
    "response": "They had to drive on ice, and have to take down a submarine."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you like the Fast and Furious franchise?",
    "response": "I only saw Tokyo Drift"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I only saw Tokyo Drift",
    "response": "Oh that is a great movie"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh that is a great movie",
    "response": "Yeah, I thought Han was great."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, I thought Han was great.",
    "response": "He is some of the others too"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He is some of the others too",
    "response": "Which ones?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which ones?",
    "response": "Los Bondoleros, Fast and Furious, Fast Five, and Fast and Furious 6"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Los Bondoleros, Fast and Furious, Fast Five, and Fast and Furious 6",
    "response": "I'll have to see if I can find them."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I'll have to see if I can find them.",
    "response": "You should, and we could watch them together"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You should, and we could watch them together",
    "response": "That would be fun"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you watched the latest Fast and Furious?",
    "response": "Yes I have. Actually I only watched the first one and the last one, that is until Vin Diesel decided to make another one haha."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes I have. Actually I only watched the first one and the last one, that is until Vin Diesel decided to make another one haha.",
    "response": "Did you like it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you like it?",
    "response": "I liked it. It was pretty good. I like Vin Diesel turning kinda bad in some parts of the movies, but I don't want to give away the ending if you haven't watched it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I liked it. It was pretty good. I like Vin Diesel turning kinda bad in some parts of the movies, but I don't want to give away the ending if you haven't watched it.",
    "response": "Any good car chases?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Any good car chases?",
    "response": "Obviously! There were a few. One was where they were going through downtown and ended up in a stand off and another big finale was towards the end of the movie. It was a bit over the top though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Obviously! There were a few. One was where they were going through downtown and ended up in a stand off and another big finale was towards the end of the movie. It was a bit over the top though.",
    "response": "I also like Ludacris' character, he adds comedy to the movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I also like Ludacris' character, he adds comedy to the movie.",
    "response": "I think they all did. I loved the love and hate relationship between The Rock and Jason Statham."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think they all did. I loved the love and hate relationship between The Rock and Jason Statham.",
    "response": "Yeah the tough guys good guys thing."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah the tough guys good guys thing.",
    "response": "I think they're all a good team."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I just don't know what to think about the Fast and The Furious films now?",
    "response": "I think I know what you mean, but you need to elaborate some more."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think I know what you mean, but you need to elaborate some more.",
    "response": "Well, look at the first film.  It was a decent action film revolving around racing and fast cars."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, look at the first film.  It was a decent action film revolving around racing and fast cars.",
    "response": "It also revolved around \"family\" as \"Dom\" always likes to say."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It also revolved around \"family\" as \"Dom\" always likes to say.",
    "response": "Right.  The stunts were great, but for the most part everything was believable."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Right.  The stunts were great, but for the most part everything was believable.",
    "response": "Which is the complete opposite of what they are doing now."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which is the complete opposite of what they are doing now.",
    "response": "Exactly!  In the Fast Five film, there was a scene where they were using their cars to drag a sealed bank vault down a busy street!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Exactly!  In the Fast Five film, there was a scene where they were using their cars to drag a sealed bank vault down a busy street!",
    "response": "In the Fate of The Furious, the Rock's character manhandled a torpedo.  I love it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "In the Fate of The Furious, the Rock's character manhandled a torpedo.  I love it.",
    "response": "Maybe it is because I am getting old, but I like my action scenes to be more realistic."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Maybe it is because I am getting old, but I like my action scenes to be more realistic.",
    "response": "I want to see how much farther the movies will push the envelope.  Will space be the final frontier for the movies?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you have a favorite actor by any chance?",
    "response": "Yes, and mine just happens to be Vin Diesel."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, and mine just happens to be Vin Diesel.",
    "response": "Let me guess, is it because of the Fast & Furious films."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Let me guess, is it because of the Fast & Furious films.",
    "response": "You guessed correctly. Those really sold me on his acting ability."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You guessed correctly. Those really sold me on his acting ability.",
    "response": "I think those movies are so overrated."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think those movies are so overrated.",
    "response": "I can understand that. They're incredibly popular."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I can understand that. They're incredibly popular.",
    "response": "Yeah, and because of that, so many people see them as film masterpieces."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, and because of that, so many people see them as film masterpieces.",
    "response": "That does get annoying rather quickly."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That does get annoying rather quickly.",
    "response": "Keep in mind, though. I never said I didn't like them."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Keep in mind, though. I never said I didn't like them.",
    "response": "Oh, I understand."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Can we talk about the trucker from the original The Fast and The Furious?",
    "response": "What about that trucker?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What about that trucker?",
    "response": "Well, he's the only guy who's been able to battle off Dom. If you think about everything Dom's been able to accomplish throughout the whole series, the Trucker was the only one to have successfully foil his plans."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, he's the only guy who's been able to battle off Dom. If you think about everything Dom's been able to accomplish throughout the whole series, the Trucker was the only one to have successfully foil his plans.",
    "response": "That's funny. I never thought about that but you're right. That trucker was prepared, with his shotgun, and he was so calm during the whole truck heist."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's funny. I never thought about that but you're right. That trucker was prepared, with his shotgun, and he was so calm during the whole truck heist.",
    "response": "Seriously, that trucker is legendary. He must be sitting at home watching the events from all the other Fast and Furious movies and laughing to himself about how he stood up to Dom."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Seriously, that trucker is legendary. He must be sitting at home watching the events from all the other Fast and Furious movies and laughing to himself about how he stood up to Dom.",
    "response": "It's amazing really, he was on his own in that truck and I think he took out Vince, and nearly got Dom too."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It's amazing really, he was on his own in that truck and I think he took out Vince, and nearly got Dom too.",
    "response": "Dom never really talks about this incident."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Dom never really talks about this incident.",
    "response": "You can safely say that Dom probably erased it from his mind like it never happened."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You can safely say that Dom probably erased it from his mind like it never happened.",
    "response": "The trucker needs to make a return in the next Fast and Furious as the ultimate nemesis."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The trucker needs to make a return in the next Fast and Furious as the ultimate nemesis.",
    "response": "I would die from laughter if that happened. I can see him teaming up with Charlize's character, Cyper, to exact revenge on Dom's team."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which movie in the Fast and Furious Franchise is your favorite?",
    "response": "I would have to say the first one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I would have to say the first one.",
    "response": "Have you seen them all?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen them all?",
    "response": "I've seen all of them except the last one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I've seen all of them except the last one.",
    "response": "Which one didn't you like?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which one didn't you like?",
    "response": "I couldn't bring myself to like Tokyo Drift."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I couldn't bring myself to like Tokyo Drift.",
    "response": "What didn't you like about Tokyo Drift."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What didn't you like about Tokyo Drift.",
    "response": "I felt like it was too disconnected from the other films."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I felt like it was too disconnected from the other films.",
    "response": "How do you feel Tokyo Drift was disconnected from the other films?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How do you feel Tokyo Drift was disconnected from the other films?",
    "response": "Tokyo Drift didn't really have the other characters or the same plot lines as the rest of the movies in the series."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Were you into cars before watching Fast and the Furious or after?",
    "response": "I saw the first one was I was little, so definitely after."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I saw the first one was I was little, so definitely after.",
    "response": "What about the movies made you get into cars?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What about the movies made you get into cars?",
    "response": "The cars were so cool, and Paul Walker was cool."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The cars were so cool, and Paul Walker was cool.",
    "response": "Did you like any specific cars from the movies?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you like any specific cars from the movies?",
    "response": "I was always a fan of the cars that Paul Walker drove."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I was always a fan of the cars that Paul Walker drove.",
    "response": "He always had foreign cars and modified cars like Mitsubishis and such."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He always had foreign cars and modified cars like Mitsubishis and such.",
    "response": "Yeah and they were more colorful as opposed to Vin Diesel's cars."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah and they were more colorful as opposed to Vin Diesel's cars.",
    "response": "So did you Tokyo Drift then?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "So did you Tokyo Drift then?",
    "response": "Yes, that one is my favorite. I have been a big drifting fan since and love the cars in that movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I'm not sure which ones I have.",
    "response": "Which ones of... in the series?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which ones of... in the series?",
    "response": "Yeah. I know I have the first 5 I think."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah. I know I have the first 5 I think.",
    "response": "Furious 5 is the first film where Rock plays the DSS agent"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Furious 5 is the first film where Rock plays the DSS agent",
    "response": "Yeah, that's why I remember I have it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, that's why I remember I have it.",
    "response": "i don't even remember what happens in 6 and 7..."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "i don't even remember what happens in 6 and 7...",
    "response": "In 6 the crew's scattered. And Letty suffers from amnesia, and Dom's sister Mia gets kidnapped, but gets rescued. And Dom drives out of the exploding plane. That's so lame."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "In 6 the crew's scattered. And Letty suffers from amnesia, and Dom's sister Mia gets kidnapped, but gets rescued. And Dom drives out of the exploding plane. That's so lame.",
    "response": "Oh Yeah, yeah. Then the 7 is about Letty regaining her memories. And the English guy's brother goes all crazy for vengeance."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh Yeah, yeah. Then the 7 is about Letty regaining her memories. And the English guy's brother goes all crazy for vengeance.",
    "response": "yep. Then they go to Abu Dhabi of all places. Then they tried to steal this computer program called God's eye"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "yep. Then they go to Abu Dhabi of all places. Then they tried to steal this computer program called God's eye",
    "response": "Oh yeah and they do that air drop thing into some place in Europe. And in the end Letty regains her memories."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "A lot of people tend to like the Fast & Furious series for the overall story.",
    "response": "Right. Are you getting to something."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Right. Are you getting to something.",
    "response": "I was going to ask you if you like any of the subplots of the movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I was going to ask you if you like any of the subplots of the movies.",
    "response": "Well, now that you mention it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, now that you mention it.",
    "response": "Well, go on."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, go on.",
    "response": "I was kind of into the whole thing with Letty being brainwashed."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I was kind of into the whole thing with Letty being brainwashed.",
    "response": "That was in number 6, right."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That was in number 6, right.",
    "response": "That's right. I liked the process of her going from being brainwashed to being back with her team."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's right. I liked the process of her going from being brainwashed to being back with her team.",
    "response": "I imagine that would be satisfying to watch."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I imagine that would be satisfying to watch.",
    "response": "Wait, so you haven't seen it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you thing the Rock and Vin love eachother?",
    "response": "Like, more than Vin loved Paul?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Like, more than Vin loved Paul?",
    "response": "Yeah man!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah man!",
    "response": "Really?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Really?",
    "response": "Heck yeah! You know they both love fast cars and pumping iron."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Heck yeah! You know they both love fast cars and pumping iron.",
    "response": "That's true."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's true.",
    "response": "When they're not busying stealing cars and getting into trouble, they probably like to camp and stuff."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When they're not busying stealing cars and getting into trouble, they probably like to camp and stuff.",
    "response": "Like camp at the beach or something?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Like camp at the beach or something?",
    "response": "Sure, beach, mountains, jail cell..."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Sure, beach, mountains, jail cell...",
    "response": "ha ha ha"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Man i got an opinion some people give me flack for",
    "response": "What is that?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is that?",
    "response": "Well i got complained to and beraded for saying this"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well i got complained to and beraded for saying this",
    "response": "What was it you said"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What was it you said",
    "response": "That the fast and furious movies should have only been a trilogy"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That the fast and furious movies should have only been a trilogy",
    "response": "That is not that bad of  a thing"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That is not that bad of  a thing",
    "response": "every movie after the third has been nothing but hot garbage to be honest"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "every movie after the third has been nothing but hot garbage to be honest",
    "response": "Well i liked a few of them"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well i liked a few of them",
    "response": "What did you like about them"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What did you like about them",
    "response": "I liked the way it was simple fun"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey.",
    "response": "Hi there."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hi there.",
    "response": "Do you think this will be the last fast and the furious movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you think this will be the last fast and the furious movie?",
    "response": "What number are they up to now?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What number are they up to now?",
    "response": "8."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "8.",
    "response": "oh wow."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "oh wow.",
    "response": "Yeah quite a bit."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah quite a bit.",
    "response": "Then no, I don't think they will stop making them."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Then no, I don't think they will stop making them.",
    "response": "I thought they might after Paul Walker's death."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I thought they might after Paul Walker's death.",
    "response": "Yeah I forgot about that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I was so happy when Ludacris showed back up in the Fast5.",
    "response": "Tej is definitely welcome at my house anytime."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Tej is definitely welcome at my house anytime.",
    "response": "Well when he's gonna show up with nice cars, hot women, and gets you paid; why wouldn't he be?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well when he's gonna show up with nice cars, hot women, and gets you paid; why wouldn't he be?",
    "response": "I like him a lot better after he lost the afro and sweats though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like him a lot better after he lost the afro and sweats though.",
    "response": "Agreed, it certainly upped his cool factor."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Agreed, it certainly upped his cool factor.",
    "response": "My favorite scene was in the 7th movie I think, when he was talking to Rome and Rome was telling him how rare his car was."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "My favorite scene was in the 7th movie I think, when he was talking to Rome and Rome was telling him how rare his car was.",
    "response": "Then Tej walked outside and he had the same exact one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Then Tej walked outside and he had the same exact one.",
    "response": "Yes, I busted out laughing at that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, I busted out laughing at that.",
    "response": "That was classic, but for me, his best scene was his first appearance. After the race when Brian gives him some of the winnings and he turns to show it off to the crowd."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That was classic, but for me, his best scene was his first appearance. After the race when Brian gives him some of the winnings and he turns to show it off to the crowd.",
    "response": "And thus the legend was born."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen the Fast and Furious movies?",
    "response": "Yeah. I've seen most of them. I think they are getting repetitive though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah. I've seen most of them. I think they are getting repetitive though.",
    "response": "Really? I kind of like them."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Really? I kind of like them.",
    "response": "It just seems that the whole premise has been lost."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It just seems that the whole premise has been lost.",
    "response": "What do you mean? There are cars, drugs, racing, seems all legit."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What do you mean? There are cars, drugs, racing, seems all legit.",
    "response": "Well, after Tokyo Drift, it seems like they were just rehashing the same story over and over."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, after Tokyo Drift, it seems like they were just rehashing the same story over and over.",
    "response": "The newer ones are really different though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The newer ones are really different though.",
    "response": "I know, and I don't like it. They moved away from racing and more to trafficking."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know, and I don't like it. They moved away from racing and more to trafficking.",
    "response": "I guess. They aren't so much just racers now. They are into more criminal acts."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I guess. They aren't so much just racers now. They are into more criminal acts.",
    "response": "Exactly. I don't really like it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you think the fast and Furious franchise is actually done?",
    "response": "Well, they did call the last one the fate of the eight."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, they did call the last one the fate of the eight.",
    "response": "I suppose so, but the franchises just seem to keep making movies even after they stop being good."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I suppose so, but the franchises just seem to keep making movies even after they stop being good.",
    "response": "This last one was still pretty good."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "This last one was still pretty good.",
    "response": "It was okay, I missed Paul walker."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was okay, I missed Paul walker.",
    "response": "They did an okay job of explaining why he wasn't around."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They did an okay job of explaining why he wasn't around.",
    "response": "I thought they still could have used some old footage or something as a memorial to his character."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I thought they still could have used some old footage or something as a memorial to his character.",
    "response": "Vin Diesel and the Rock were still pretty awesome."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Vin Diesel and the Rock were still pretty awesome.",
    "response": "There's no way that the Rock would lose a fist fight to the guy from Crank."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "There's no way that the Rock would lose a fist fight to the guy from Crank.",
    "response": "That's a good point, his arms are the same size as the other guy's waist!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "i wonder if they will ever make a movie in the series with a different theme",
    "response": "What you mean bro"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What you mean bro",
    "response": "A fast and furious movie not about cars"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "A fast and furious movie not about cars",
    "response": "Like something deeper"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Like something deeper",
    "response": "Yeah that exactly"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah that exactly",
    "response": "It would be pretty neat would it not"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It would be pretty neat would it not",
    "response": "I would sign up for that"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I would sign up for that",
    "response": "It is pretty impressive idea to expand the franchise"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It is pretty impressive idea to expand the franchise",
    "response": "It is always good for new things"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It is always good for new things",
    "response": "Yeah same ol gets boring"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who is your favorite Fast and Furious character?",
    "response": "I really like Han myself."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I really like Han myself.",
    "response": "Really? Why's that?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Really? Why's that?",
    "response": "He seems to be really cool and chill. Always calm under pressure."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He seems to be really cool and chill. Always calm under pressure.",
    "response": "I see."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I see.",
    "response": "He also has him moments of humor, and he feels like he stands out among characters that seem more similar."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He also has him moments of humor, and he feels like he stands out among characters that seem more similar.",
    "response": "Anything else you like?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Anything else you like?",
    "response": "Well, he was in Tokyo Drift, which I like. I think Japan is interesting and drifting looks cool."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, he was in Tokyo Drift, which I like. I think Japan is interesting and drifting looks cool.",
    "response": "Yeah that wasn't too bad a movie, was it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah that wasn't too bad a movie, was it?",
    "response": "Nope. I liked it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you like you the first \"The Fast and the Furious\"?",
    "response": "Yes! That was best movie of all the fast and furious movies. Brian Walker was just starting out and did a great job."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes! That was best movie of all the fast and furious movies. Brian Walker was just starting out and did a great job.",
    "response": "I actually liked the first movie because of Vin Diesel. I personally think he made the movie a blast."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I actually liked the first movie because of Vin Diesel. I personally think he made the movie a blast.",
    "response": "Vin Diesel was good but all the actors in the movie made it a great success."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Vin Diesel was good but all the actors in the movie made it a great success.",
    "response": "The story line was also great because what movie about cars is not great?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The story line was also great because what movie about cars is not great?",
    "response": "That is so true. I haven't seen a movie that involves cars that was not great?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That is so true. I haven't seen a movie that involves cars that was not great?",
    "response": "This movie started the beginning of many fast and furious movies to come."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "This movie started the beginning of many fast and furious movies to come.",
    "response": "Tell me about it. Now there's like eight of them out now. I liked Ja Rule character as well."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Tell me about it. Now there's like eight of them out now. I liked Ja Rule character as well.",
    "response": "Ja Rule was alright in the movie but I think any rapper could play his part."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Ja Rule was alright in the movie but I think any rapper could play his part.",
    "response": "I believe Ja Rule was uniquely fitted for that position."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I love the fast and furious movies",
    "response": "Me too"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too",
    "response": "I love that ludacris stars in them"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I love that ludacris stars in them",
    "response": "Same here, hes great"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Same here, hes great",
    "response": "I didnt realize he was a good actor too"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I didnt realize he was a good actor too",
    "response": "Me either, he is very talented"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me either, he is very talented",
    "response": "I agree with that"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I agree with that",
    "response": "These movies are made for him"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "These movies are made for him",
    "response": "Yes he is perfect in them"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes he is perfect in them",
    "response": "He really is"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Tyrese has to be my favorite character in the Fast and Furious series. He's just so funny.",
    "response": "Roman Pearce! He's got the best one liners. He's pretty much the comic relief of the series now."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Roman Pearce! He's got the best one liners. He's pretty much the comic relief of the series now.",
    "response": "I love how he makes light of the situations they get in and he's always the one who has to struggle through."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I love how he makes light of the situations they get in and he's always the one who has to struggle through.",
    "response": "The last one, Fate of the Furious, he was hilarious in that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The last one, Fate of the Furious, he was hilarious in that.",
    "response": "I loved when he took the Lamborghini out to the ice and everyone looked at him like he was crazy for taking that type of car out to that environment."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I loved when he took the Lamborghini out to the ice and everyone looked at him like he was crazy for taking that type of car out to that environment.",
    "response": "That scene was wild. I loved the craziness that was the submarine they were trying to out run."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That scene was wild. I loved the craziness that was the submarine they were trying to out run.",
    "response": "I've never seen a car chase involving a submarine before. A first for everything!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I've never seen a car chase involving a submarine before. A first for everything!",
    "response": "I mean it was great because it was a submarine, but that submarine was also launching torpedoes at the cars!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I mean it was great because it was a submarine, but that submarine was also launching torpedoes at the cars!",
    "response": "I'm trying to think of another scene in the series or any other movies that had something that outrageous."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I'm trying to think of another scene in the series or any other movies that had something that outrageous.",
    "response": "I'm drawing a blank, but Fate of the Furious had a lot of over the top moments!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who is your favorite Fast & Furious actor?",
    "response": "Paul Walker. I love his character of Brian O'Connor. From good guy, to bad guy...back to good again."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Paul Walker. I love his character of Brian O'Connor. From good guy, to bad guy...back to good again.",
    "response": "Then back to bad. I adore Ludarcis' character. He's so funny!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Then back to bad. I adore Ludarcis' character. He's so funny!",
    "response": "He and Tyrese Gibbs are awesome. The way their two characters are always fighting, yet they are there for each other always."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He and Tyrese Gibbs are awesome. The way their two characters are always fighting, yet they are there for each other always.",
    "response": "I have to admit that Jason Statham's addition to the franchise made things easy on the eyes."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I have to admit that Jason Statham's addition to the franchise made things easy on the eyes.",
    "response": "I loved the way he and Hobbs met. Even though he is a bad guy, I love Deckard Shaw."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I loved the way he and Hobbs met. Even though he is a bad guy, I love Deckard Shaw.",
    "response": "That accent! The way he fights, the way he always is one step ahead of Dom and his team."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That accent! The way he fights, the way he always is one step ahead of Dom and his team.",
    "response": "Even when he is put in maximum security, he is still one step ahead of Hobbs."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Even when he is put in maximum security, he is still one step ahead of Hobbs.",
    "response": "I was so sure that Elana and Hobbs were going to end up together, instead of her and Dom."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I was so sure that Elana and Hobbs were going to end up together, instead of her and Dom.",
    "response": "I was too. But, she and Dom made a striking couple for a little while."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "So does  the new movie  hold up  in the  fast  and  furious  series ?",
    "response": "It is ok  but  I  think  its  off  character  for  some  of  the  guys."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It is ok  but  I  think  its  off  character  for  some  of  the  guys.",
    "response": "And when is  the  kids  from  tokyo   drift  supposed to  show  up?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "And when is  the  kids  from  tokyo   drift  supposed to  show  up?",
    "response": "I  thought  after  Brian  and Han  left ."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I  thought  after  Brian  and Han  left .",
    "response": "And  now most of the bad  guys are  good  guys?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "And  now most of the bad  guys are  good  guys?",
    "response": "I found parts of  stathams role  to  be funny  though ."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I found parts of  stathams role  to  be funny  though .",
    "response": "I  did like when he  saved the baby."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I  did like when he  saved the baby.",
    "response": "I   think  he is  the   new  star  of the  franchise  soon  to  replace   vin disel ."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I   think  he is  the   new  star  of the  franchise  soon  to  replace   vin disel .",
    "response": "And what do you think of vin disel  having to  go  against his  own  team ?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "And what do you think of vin disel  having to  go  against his  own  team ?",
    "response": "I thought  they made him  look  way too  strong  ."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who is your favorite Fast & Furious actor.",
    "response": "My favorite actor is Tyrese."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "My favorite actor is Tyrese.",
    "response": "Tyrese is amazing in this series."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Tyrese is amazing in this series.",
    "response": "I agree, he was specially awesome in the 4th movie of this series."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I agree, he was specially awesome in the 4th movie of this series.",
    "response": "I like how he brings comedy to this movie series."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like how he brings comedy to this movie series.",
    "response": "Yes, comedy is important in these movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, comedy is important in these movies.",
    "response": "I agree because with all of the action, comedy is a great balance."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I agree because with all of the action, comedy is a great balance.",
    "response": "Tyrese has been one of my favorite actors since Baby Boy."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Tyrese has been one of my favorite actors since Baby Boy.",
    "response": "It's amazing how he can act and sing."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It's amazing how he can act and sing.",
    "response": "Yes, being a dual threat is amazing."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Want to talk about movies",
    "response": "Sure that sounds fun"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Sure that sounds fun",
    "response": "Great"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Great",
    "response": "Whats your favorite?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Whats your favorite?",
    "response": "Definitely the fast and the furious"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Definitely the fast and the furious",
    "response": "I love those movies too"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I love those movies too",
    "response": "They are really exciting and fun to watch"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They are really exciting and fun to watch",
    "response": "They are and the actors are great"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They are and the actors are great",
    "response": "Definitely"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Definitely",
    "response": "I love vin disel"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you like Fast and the Furious Tokyo Drift?",
    "response": "Yes at first it was off putting since it was new characters but I got used to it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes at first it was off putting since it was new characters but I got used to it.",
    "response": "Yeah that was a little off putting for me too."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah that was a little off putting for me too.",
    "response": "I did like the drifting and different race styles that was in that movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I did like the drifting and different race styles that was in that movie.",
    "response": "Speaking of that do you remember the first race of the movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Speaking of that do you remember the first race of the movie?",
    "response": "The one where Sean Boswell I think his name is was racing?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The one where Sean Boswell I think his name is was racing?",
    "response": "Yes, I actually liked his character."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, I actually liked his character.",
    "response": "Yeah he was a good installment to the franchise."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah he was a good installment to the franchise.",
    "response": "I just remember him trying to learn to drift and crashing into all kinds of things in that first one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I just remember him trying to learn to drift and crashing into all kinds of things in that first one.",
    "response": "Yeah that was a good part in the movie showing how even people have to learn in movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen Fate of the Furious yet?",
    "response": "Which one is that?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which one is that?",
    "response": "The newest one, eighth in the installment."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The newest one, eighth in the installment.",
    "response": "Of course, that makes complete sense."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Of course, that makes complete sense.",
    "response": "It stars Charlize Theron as Cipher."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It stars Charlize Theron as Cipher.",
    "response": "Oh yes, I have seen it.  She is one of the best villains I think."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh yes, I have seen it.  She is one of the best villains I think.",
    "response": "Yea, she did a great job, as she does in almost all her work."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, she did a great job, as she does in almost all her work.",
    "response": "It was sad to see a movie in the franchise without Paul."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was sad to see a movie in the franchise without Paul.",
    "response": "Yea he will always be missed."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea he will always be missed.",
    "response": "He did so much for the franchise and the scene in general."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Morning.",
    "response": "Hello."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hello.",
    "response": "Do you plan on seeing the new fast and furious?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you plan on seeing the new fast and furious?",
    "response": "I don't know.  Maybe if I'm bored one day."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I don't know.  Maybe if I'm bored one day.",
    "response": "I know what you mean."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know what you mean.",
    "response": "Are you going to see it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Are you going to see it?",
    "response": "Yeah I think I might."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah I think I might.",
    "response": "Well it does look like a good popcorn movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well it does look like a good popcorn movie.",
    "response": "Yeah that's what I'm thinking."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah that's what I'm thinking.",
    "response": "exactly."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I want o have a family movie night this weekend",
    "response": "Oh great idea, what kind of movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh great idea, what kind of movie?",
    "response": "I am not sure, I am thinking something fast paced and exciting"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I am not sure, I am thinking something fast paced and exciting",
    "response": "How about  fast and furious?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How about  fast and furious?",
    "response": "Oh yeah, I bet the kids would love that"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh yeah, I bet the kids would love that",
    "response": "The cars are really amazing, and I love Vin deisel"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The cars are really amazing, and I love Vin deisel",
    "response": "I loved Paul Walker, I was sad to hear he died"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I loved Paul Walker, I was sad to hear he died",
    "response": "I agree, such a waste, he was a really good actor"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I agree, such a waste, he was a really good actor",
    "response": "Want to join us for movie night?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Want to join us for movie night?",
    "response": "I would love that, thanks"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you like the Fast & Furious movies?",
    "response": "Yes, quite a bit."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, quite a bit.",
    "response": "I like them as well."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like them as well.",
    "response": "Who is your favorite character."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who is your favorite character.",
    "response": "I like the character Paul Walker played."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like the character Paul Walker played.",
    "response": "That is my favorite as well."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That is my favorite as well.",
    "response": "It is too bad he passed away in that accident."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It is too bad he passed away in that accident.",
    "response": "It sure is."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It sure is.",
    "response": "We lost a good one there.  I don't think the movies will be the same going forward."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "We lost a good one there.  I don't think the movies will be the same going forward.",
    "response": "No, they definitely won't."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "So, you're a car fan.",
    "response": "You could say that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You could say that.",
    "response": "You have seen the fast and furious movies right?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You have seen the fast and furious movies right?",
    "response": "Um, duh."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Um, duh.",
    "response": "They are so good!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They are so good!",
    "response": "You dont have to tell me twice!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You dont have to tell me twice!",
    "response": "I didnt think they could get better after the second one, but when the rock showed up everything changed."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I didnt think they could get better after the second one, but when the rock showed up everything changed.",
    "response": "Yeah I think the rock single handedly saved the franchise."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah I think the rock single handedly saved the franchise.",
    "response": "Man, we have to marathon those movies soon."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Man, we have to marathon those movies soon.",
    "response": "Lets get to it!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Are there any rumors yet about 'Fast 9?'",
    "response": "There are a few details.  For instance, Vin Diesel and The Rock are set to reprise their roles."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "There are a few details.  For instance, Vin Diesel and The Rock are set to reprise their roles.",
    "response": "That's cool, but I'm actually surprised."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's cool, but I'm actually surprised.",
    "response": "How so?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How so?",
    "response": "Didn't they not get along during the shooting of the movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Didn't they not get along during the shooting of the movie?",
    "response": "I did hear something like that.  Apparently they had a feud but were cordial to each other on set."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I did hear something like that.  Apparently they had a feud but were cordial to each other on set.",
    "response": "I suppose as long as you can work with the person, it's fine.  What was the feud even about?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I suppose as long as you can work with the person, it's fine.  What was the feud even about?",
    "response": "There was a rumor that it was about who would have the bigger role.  The Rock apparently conceded."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "There was a rumor that it was about who would have the bigger role.  The Rock apparently conceded.",
    "response": "So there was a chance that 'Fate of the Furious' could have been about Hobbs, The Rock's character, going bad instead."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "So there was a chance that 'Fate of the Furious' could have been about Hobbs, The Rock's character, going bad instead.",
    "response": "That would have been just as fun to watch.  And as a former cop, Hobbs would have been more interesting."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The fast amd the furious movies are so exciting",
    "response": "I know, i love them"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know, i love them",
    "response": "I love when brian and mia get together"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I love when brian and mia get together",
    "response": "Me too they are so adorable"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too they are so adorable",
    "response": "They are the cutest couple"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They are the cutest couple",
    "response": "And brian and dom became like best friends"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "And brian and dom became like best friends",
    "response": "They are such good movies"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They are such good movies",
    "response": "I know they are amazing"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know they are amazing",
    "response": "I wish they were going to come out with more"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I wish they were going to come out with more",
    "response": "Me too"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey do you like movies?",
    "response": "Yes I do Like movies"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes I do Like movies",
    "response": "Have you seen that race car one?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen that race car one?",
    "response": "The fast and the furious?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The fast and the furious?",
    "response": "Yeah that movie is really good."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah that movie is really good.",
    "response": "It is so sad that that Paul Walker died."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It is so sad that that Paul Walker died.",
    "response": "Yes I can't believe it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes I can't believe it.",
    "response": "What was your favorite car?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What was your favorite car?",
    "response": "Mine was the red car Toretto had."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Mine was the red car Toretto had.",
    "response": "That my also my favorite one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "who is your favorite Fast & Furious character",
    "response": "for sure it's Dom."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "for sure it's Dom.",
    "response": "Really? I always like Hobbs better."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Really? I always like Hobbs better.",
    "response": "no way. Dom is the best!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "no way. Dom is the best!",
    "response": "Hobbs is so much bigger and stronger though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hobbs is so much bigger and stronger though.",
    "response": "yeah, but Hobbs wasn't even one of the original characters."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "yeah, but Hobbs wasn't even one of the original characters.",
    "response": "True, but he steals the show in the later sequels"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "True, but he steals the show in the later sequels",
    "response": "There wouldn't even be a movie without Dom, he's the center of almost all the movies"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "There wouldn't even be a movie without Dom, he's the center of almost all the movies",
    "response": "yeah, except for 2, which he was barely in."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "yeah, except for 2, which he was barely in.",
    "response": "that one was the worst"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who plays Dom's love interest in the first Fast and the Furious movie?",
    "response": "Michelle Rodriguez"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Michelle Rodriguez",
    "response": "Does she do a good job?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Does she do a good job?",
    "response": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes",
    "response": "Is she in a lot of the films?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is she in a lot of the films?",
    "response": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes",
    "response": "What is her character like?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is her character like?",
    "response": "She is a tough girl"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "She is a tough girl",
    "response": "Does she do a good job with it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Does she do a good job with it?",
    "response": "Yes. She is very good in that role."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen any of the fast and the furious movies?",
    "response": "Yea, I saw the first couple I think."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, I saw the first couple I think.",
    "response": "How did you like Tokyo Drift?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How did you like Tokyo Drift?",
    "response": "It was not my favorite."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was not my favorite.",
    "response": "Yea. It felt a little out of place to me."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea. It felt a little out of place to me.",
    "response": "Same. Did you see all of them?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Same. Did you see all of them?",
    "response": "All but the last one that just came out."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "All but the last one that just came out.",
    "response": "That's cool. Does Tokyo Drift fit in the series better after you have seen most of the movies?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's cool. Does Tokyo Drift fit in the series better after you have seen most of the movies?",
    "response": "Yea it fit in better. It helps you understand the characters more."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea it fit in better. It helps you understand the characters more.",
    "response": "Oh ok. I will have to watch them."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What do you think about the Luke Hobbs character?",
    "response": "Wait, who's that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Wait, who's that.",
    "response": "He's Dwayne Johnson's character in the Fast & Furious series."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He's Dwayne Johnson's character in the Fast & Furious series.",
    "response": "Oh, right. I like him."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh, right. I like him.",
    "response": "I do, too. I just felt like they threw him in there too suddenly."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I do, too. I just felt like they threw him in there too suddenly.",
    "response": "That's true. He just kind of appeared for Fast Five."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's true. He just kind of appeared for Fast Five.",
    "response": "Without any story to carry over, either."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Without any story to carry over, either.",
    "response": "Well, I'm not sure if you remember this or not."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, I'm not sure if you remember this or not.",
    "response": "What's that?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What's that?",
    "response": "Tokyo Drift, chronologically, comes way after any of the others, so by that point, Hobbs was already introduced to the team."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you see the new Fast & the Furious?",
    "response": "Yes I did but it's not the same without Mia and Brian."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes I did but it's not the same without Mia and Brian.",
    "response": "I know Paul Walker wasn't in this one because he passed, but why wasn't Mia?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know Paul Walker wasn't in this one because he passed, but why wasn't Mia?",
    "response": "I don't know. I think each movie gets more unrealstic."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I don't know. I think each movie gets more unrealstic.",
    "response": "You're totally right the action scenes Dom and his team do aren't believable."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You're totally right the action scenes Dom and his team do aren't believable.",
    "response": "Is that the last Fast & Furious movie to come out?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is that the last Fast & Furious movie to come out?",
    "response": "I am pretty sure it is. I have seen them all except for Too Fast & Furious."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I am pretty sure it is. I have seen them all except for Too Fast & Furious.",
    "response": "I have seen them all. My favorite is Tokyo Drift."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I have seen them all. My favorite is Tokyo Drift.",
    "response": "Yeah I like that one because Bow Wow is in it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah I like that one because Bow Wow is in it.",
    "response": "I just like those cars the best."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is your favorite Fast and Furious Movie?",
    "response": "I really like Furious 7. What do you think?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I really like Furious 7. What do you think?",
    "response": "Yeah I really like that one too."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah I really like that one too.",
    "response": "It was so amazing when they made the car fly! I almost believed they did for a second."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was so amazing when they made the car fly! I almost believed they did for a second.",
    "response": "Yeah, I was surprised too. It was even funnier to see Paul Walker's character's expression."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, I was surprised too. It was even funnier to see Paul Walker's character's expression.",
    "response": "I know, he looked so scared!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know, he looked so scared!",
    "response": "The only thing that I think needed more work was the dialogue. It just seemed kind of cheesy."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The only thing that I think needed more work was the dialogue. It just seemed kind of cheesy.",
    "response": "The dialogue is usually a little cliche, but I only watch for the action."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The dialogue is usually a little cliche, but I only watch for the action.",
    "response": "Oh yeah, the action is really good."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh yeah, the action is really good.",
    "response": "I'm excited to see what they do for the next one!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hi.",
    "response": "Hey."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey.",
    "response": "Did you see the last fast and the furious movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you see the last fast and the furious movie?",
    "response": "What was it called?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What was it called?",
    "response": "Furious 7."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Furious 7.",
    "response": "Yeah I did see that one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah I did see that one.",
    "response": "The whole movie felt a bit sad though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The whole movie felt a bit sad though.",
    "response": "Why is that?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why is that?",
    "response": "Paul Walker's death."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Paul Walker's death.",
    "response": "Oh yeah, they had that nice tribute to him at the end of the movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Was one better than two?",
    "response": "Was that the one with the boat or race?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Was that the one with the boat or race?",
    "response": "The boat was two and the physics were impossible but thats 2 fast 2 furious."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The boat was two and the physics were impossible but thats 2 fast 2 furious.",
    "response": "I prefer the original."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I prefer the original.",
    "response": "Well than did you like the mexican race one?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well than did you like the mexican race one?",
    "response": "Is that 4 or 5?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is that 4 or 5?",
    "response": "I believe it is 4"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I believe it is 4",
    "response": "There is many films its hard to keep track"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "There is many films its hard to keep track",
    "response": "Its all about the cars."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Its all about the cars.",
    "response": "Agreed."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "So have you seen all the Fast & Furious movies?",
    "response": "I believe so, they're all so great"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I believe so, they're all so great",
    "response": "but which one is your favorite?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "but which one is your favorite?",
    "response": "if you have to choose, it's gonna be the one that involves cars jumping over a drawbridge, I don't remember which one that was"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "if you have to choose, it's gonna be the one that involves cars jumping over a drawbridge, I don't remember which one that was",
    "response": "sounds like the second one when Paul Walker was an under cover FBI agent"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "sounds like the second one when Paul Walker was an under cover FBI agent",
    "response": "yea that's the one, god I miss Paul Walker already"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "yea that's the one, god I miss Paul Walker already",
    "response": "yea me as a fan of the series as well, it's so sad to see Paul Walker gone, at such young age"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "yea me as a fan of the series as well, it's so sad to see Paul Walker gone, at such young age",
    "response": "you know there was a song dedicated to him, \"see you again\"?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "you know there was a song dedicated to him, \"see you again\"?",
    "response": "oh yeah, How could I miss that song, I heard it has 28 million views on Youtube already?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "oh yeah, How could I miss that song, I heard it has 28 million views on Youtube already?",
    "response": "yeah, it's crazy, but Paul deserved it"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who is your favorite Fast and Furious character?",
    "response": "I like The Rock, he's great."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like The Rock, he's great.",
    "response": "Oh you mean his character Luke Dobbs. Yeah he's funny."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh you mean his character Luke Dobbs. Yeah he's funny.",
    "response": "He was so funny in Furious 7."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He was so funny in Furious 7.",
    "response": "Yeah when he jumped a ambulance of a bridge onto a plan? That was insane."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah when he jumped a ambulance of a bridge onto a plan? That was insane.",
    "response": "I liked when he flexed so hard it ripped of the cast on his arm."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I liked when he flexed so hard it ripped of the cast on his arm.",
    "response": "That or when he picked up the gun and said, \"I am the cavalry.\""
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That or when he picked up the gun and said, \"I am the cavalry.\"",
    "response": "Yeah, he's great. Did you see him in Fast 8?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, he's great. Did you see him in Fast 8?",
    "response": "Yeah he was good in that too."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah he was good in that too.",
    "response": "Yes, he's a good addition to the series indeed."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you like The Fast and the Furious part 2?",
    "response": "Not as much as part 1"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Not as much as part 1",
    "response": "Did you love part 1 way more?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you love part 1 way more?",
    "response": "Yes, the story was way more organic and an overall great film."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, the story was way more organic and an overall great film.",
    "response": "Did you like Paul Walker?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you like Paul Walker?",
    "response": "Yes, he had a lot of depth."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, he had a lot of depth.",
    "response": "I bet that franchise has made a ton of money."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I bet that franchise has made a ton of money.",
    "response": "Yeah, they have made tons of movies"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, they have made tons of movies",
    "response": "Do you like the ones with The Rock in them?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you like the ones with The Rock in them?",
    "response": "Yeah, they are pretty good, but they are no part 1."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I dont remember which one is my favorite, but i love the one with safe",
    "response": "Where they switched the safes at the end of the movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Where they switched the safes at the end of the movie?",
    "response": "Yes that one"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes that one",
    "response": "That was fast five"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That was fast five",
    "response": "Oh okay well fast five is my favorite then"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh okay well fast five is my favorite then",
    "response": "I liked that one too"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I liked that one too",
    "response": "Ot9 was really cool how it was done"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Ot9 was really cool how it was done",
    "response": "Yes it was the ending was such a twist"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes it was the ending was such a twist",
    "response": "Im glad they showed how it was really done"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Im glad they showed how it was really done",
    "response": "Me too"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "So I saw the new Fast and Furious.",
    "response": "Oh, there's a new one?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh, there's a new one?",
    "response": "Yeah."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah.",
    "response": "I guess there's always a new one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I guess there's always a new one.",
    "response": "Yeah, they're kind of starting over now because --"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, they're kind of starting over now because --",
    "response": "Wasn't there one set in Japan, that was all about drifting?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Wasn't there one set in Japan, that was all about drifting?",
    "response": "Yeah, Tokyo Drift."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, Tokyo Drift.",
    "response": "I saw the previews for that. It reminded me of Tokyo Xtreme Racer."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I saw the previews for that. It reminded me of Tokyo Xtreme Racer.",
    "response": "That's... what?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's... what?",
    "response": "Oh, right. You didn't own a Dreamcast, did you."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I just watched Fast and Furious.",
    "response": "I've seen that movie. What did you think?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I've seen that movie. What did you think?",
    "response": "I thought it was good."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I thought it was good.",
    "response": "Yeah, I really like the interplay between Vin Diesel and Paul Walker."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, I really like the interplay between Vin Diesel and Paul Walker.",
    "response": "I do, too. It's funny that they have to work together even though they're enemies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I do, too. It's funny that they have to work together even though they're enemies.",
    "response": "I know that is really funny, plus the action is really good."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know that is really funny, plus the action is really good.",
    "response": "Yeah, it is.  I can't believe Paul Walker is dead now."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, it is.  I can't believe Paul Walker is dead now.",
    "response": "I know it's so crazy to think about when you watch the movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know it's so crazy to think about when you watch the movies.",
    "response": "It is really sad."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It is really sad.",
    "response": "I know, I was really sad when he died."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you remember Brian aka Paul Walker from the Fast & Furious movies.",
    "response": "Yes, I heard he died awhile back."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, I heard he died awhile back.",
    "response": "Yes he did, do you remember the tribute they did for him at the end of the seventh movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes he did, do you remember the tribute they did for him at the end of the seventh movie?",
    "response": "Yes, do you know who did that song?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, do you know who did that song?",
    "response": "I believe it was Whiz Khalifa."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I believe it was Whiz Khalifa.",
    "response": "That's actually one of my favorite songs now."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's actually one of my favorite songs now.",
    "response": "It's such a good song and im happy that they did a tribute for Brian who was such a vital part of peoples lifes after all these movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It's such a good song and im happy that they did a tribute for Brian who was such a vital part of peoples lifes after all these movies.",
    "response": "Yep and i'm glad they did a good job capturing what it means to be part of someone's life."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yep and i'm glad they did a good job capturing what it means to be part of someone's life.",
    "response": "The feels were so strong during that moment in the movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The feels were so strong during that moment in the movie.",
    "response": "Yep, the song brings back those feels everytime I heard it now."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What's the best Fast and Furious movie?",
    "response": "Definitely the first one!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Definitely the first one!",
    "response": "I would agree!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I would agree!",
    "response": "It was so original back then, all the actors were great too!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was so original back then, all the actors were great too!",
    "response": "I like the story line because it actually made me care!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like the story line because it actually made me care!",
    "response": "Seeing a young Paul Walker and Vin Diesel is so unreal too."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Seeing a young Paul Walker and Vin Diesel is so unreal too.",
    "response": "I liked when they try to beat the train at the end"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I liked when they try to beat the train at the end",
    "response": "It had me on the edge of my seat!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It had me on the edge of my seat!",
    "response": "It was so sad when they both made it but then Vin crashed!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was so sad when they both made it but then Vin crashed!",
    "response": "But it still had a happy ending so I'm happy!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What do you think the next Fast & Furious movie will be about?",
    "response": "I didn't realize there were going to be more."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I didn't realize there were going to be more.",
    "response": "There are.  Number nine and ten are already planned."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "There are.  Number nine and ten are already planned.",
    "response": "It is tough to say.  How are they going to top the flying car landing from Seven, or the submarine from Eight?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It is tough to say.  How are they going to top the flying car landing from Seven, or the submarine from Eight?",
    "response": "To be honest, it seems like the logical progression would be something in space."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "To be honest, it seems like the logical progression would be something in space.",
    "response": "As absurd as it sounds, I would not put it past this franchise."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "As absurd as it sounds, I would not put it past this franchise.",
    "response": "Especially because no matter how outlandish it seems to get, they keep making money."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Especially because no matter how outlandish it seems to get, they keep making money.",
    "response": "Do you know how much they made with 'Fate of the Furious?'"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you know how much they made with 'Fate of the Furious?'",
    "response": "I believe it grossed $1.23 billion."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I believe it grossed $1.23 billion.",
    "response": "In other words, they will keep raising the stakes for the main characters because there is such a high demand for these movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hi there.",
    "response": "Hello."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hello.",
    "response": "Do you like fast and the furious?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you like fast and the furious?",
    "response": "I like some of the films."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like some of the films.",
    "response": "There are quite a few."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "There are quite a few.",
    "response": "How many are they up to now?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How many are they up to now?",
    "response": "I believe this is the 8th one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I believe this is the 8th one.",
    "response": "wow that is a lot."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "wow that is a lot.",
    "response": "Do you think it will be good?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you think it will be good?",
    "response": "I have no idea."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which Fast and Furious movie was it that they found out Lettie is alive?",
    "response": "That was Fast Five (Fast and Furious Five)."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That was Fast Five (Fast and Furious Five).",
    "response": "How did they explain her death?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How did they explain her death?",
    "response": "She was in that car accident in #4 and then she crawled out.  She had amnesia."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "She was in that car accident in #4 and then she crawled out.  She had amnesia.",
    "response": "Did they explain how Dom had a relationship with that Brazil cop?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did they explain how Dom had a relationship with that Brazil cop?",
    "response": "They did show them together at the beginning, but it sort of dropped off after that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They did show them together at the beginning, but it sort of dropped off after that.",
    "response": "I heard in Fast 8 that the Brazil cop and Dom had a baby, is that true?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I heard in Fast 8 that the Brazil cop and Dom had a baby, is that true?",
    "response": "Yes they explained they had an affair while Lettie was \"dead\"."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes they explained they had an affair while Lettie was \"dead\".",
    "response": "What did they name the baby?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What did they name the baby?",
    "response": "Brian -- after the character in the movie, but I think they should have named him Paul."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The whole Fast & Furious series of movies changed the way I looked at cars forever.",
    "response": "I know, I see a car similar to any from the movies and it takes me back to some scene."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know, I see a car similar to any from the movies and it takes me back to some scene.",
    "response": "They really shouldn't have made any without Vin Deisel."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They really shouldn't have made any without Vin Deisel.",
    "response": "I don't know that he was too interested at the time."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I don't know that he was too interested at the time.",
    "response": "No, I suppose not, but I am glad he got over that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No, I suppose not, but I am glad he got over that.",
    "response": "Have you ever watched many in a row?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you ever watched many in a row?",
    "response": "I have, and I always notice that Dom's arms just grow significantly."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I have, and I always notice that Dom's arms just grow significantly.",
    "response": "Do you think it was steroids?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you think it was steroids?",
    "response": "I don't nkow, probably, or maybe it's me, jealous, that I will never have his arms."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I don't nkow, probably, or maybe it's me, jealous, that I will never have his arms.",
    "response": "Just keep working out, and eat your vegetables."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you like the Fast and Furious movies?",
    "response": "Are you kidding? They are awesome!!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Are you kidding? They are awesome!!",
    "response": "They really are! I loved the first two so much."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They really are! I loved the first two so much.",
    "response": "Me too. I like the newer ones even more, though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too. I like the newer ones even more, though.",
    "response": "Really? I like them, but not nearly as much."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Really? I like them, but not nearly as much.",
    "response": "Fast Five was just so awesome."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Fast Five was just so awesome.",
    "response": "It kind of turned the franchise into a heist series, though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It kind of turned the franchise into a heist series, though.",
    "response": "Yeah, but I love heist films!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, but I love heist films!",
    "response": "Me too, but it just wasn't what I expected from them."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too, but it just wasn't what I expected from them.",
    "response": "Well I am glad they did it! They got even better with time!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you like Vin Diesel's acting in The Fast and the Furious?",
    "response": "Yes, he played it very well."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, he played it very well.",
    "response": "I agree."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I agree.",
    "response": "He plays a good tough guy."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He plays a good tough guy.",
    "response": "Paul Walker was a great person to play opposite him."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Paul Walker was a great person to play opposite him.",
    "response": "I liked the way their relationship formed"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I liked the way their relationship formed",
    "response": "They played it very well."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They played it very well.",
    "response": "The filmmakers should be proud of that film."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The filmmakers should be proud of that film.",
    "response": "I think so too and part 2 and 3."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think so too and part 2 and 3.",
    "response": "The second and third one are good. I like how they take the characters and stayed true to the original."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you remember that race in 2 fast 2 furious?",
    "response": "Which one?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which one?",
    "response": "The bridge jump race."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The bridge jump race.",
    "response": "Oh yes of course I remember."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh yes of course I remember.",
    "response": "That has to be my favorite street race in the franchise."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That has to be my favorite street race in the franchise.",
    "response": "Yes it was an incredible race and exciting."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes it was an incredible race and exciting.",
    "response": "Do you remember who won that race?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you remember who won that race?",
    "response": "Brian of course, how can you not remember that?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Brian of course, how can you not remember that?",
    "response": "I sometimes forget, wasn't he driving the silver and blue car in that one?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I sometimes forget, wasn't he driving the silver and blue car in that one?",
    "response": "Yes he was."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you remember the scene from the first Fast & Furious in the Tran's garage?",
    "response": "I'm not sure if I do."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I'm not sure if I do.",
    "response": "When Brian was looking for the stolen stuff from the truck robberies?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When Brian was looking for the stolen stuff from the truck robberies?",
    "response": "Oh right, when he almost got found out by Dom."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh right, when he almost got found out by Dom.",
    "response": "Yeah, the scene with the mechanic is what I mean specifically."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, the scene with the mechanic is what I mean specifically.",
    "response": "Oh when he's watching the guy get tortured."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh when he's watching the guy get tortured.",
    "response": "Yeah that's it, it took me so long to figure out what he Tran was talking about when he asked 40 weight or 50 weight."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah that's it, it took me so long to figure out what he Tran was talking about when he asked 40 weight or 50 weight.",
    "response": "Are you for real right now?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Are you for real right now?",
    "response": "Yes I know now, but I completely spaced about oil viscosities when I was watching it the first few times."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes I know now, but I completely spaced about oil viscosities when I was watching it the first few times.",
    "response": "I think I'm gonna find a new mechanic, no offense."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you know that Fast and the Furious chronology was different from it's story chronology?",
    "response": "What do you mean by that?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What do you mean by that?",
    "response": "Like the movies do not all go in order."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Like the movies do not all go in order.",
    "response": "I had no idea about that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I had no idea about that.",
    "response": "Yea, there were 2 short films that were released, one bridges the gap between the first and the second and one the second and the fourth."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, there were 2 short films that were released, one bridges the gap between the first and the second and one the second and the fourth.",
    "response": "That is interesting, I had no idea."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That is interesting, I had no idea.",
    "response": "Tokyo Drift was the third released but actually takes place after the sixth movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Tokyo Drift was the third released but actually takes place after the sixth movie.",
    "response": "That is just strange, why would they do that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That is just strange, why would they do that.",
    "response": "They probably did not plan on the franchise lasting this long when they made the third."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They probably did not plan on the franchise lasting this long when they made the third.",
    "response": "They were definitely wrong about that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Man i wonder how many of those people get hurt",
    "response": "Hurt how"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hurt how",
    "response": "Well in the fast and furious movies"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well in the fast and furious movies",
    "response": "well they seem to be alright it seems"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "well they seem to be alright it seems",
    "response": "But those stunts are pretty rough"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "But those stunts are pretty rough",
    "response": "Well all stunts are"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well all stunts are",
    "response": "Yeah i wonder if they all use stunt doubles"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah i wonder if they all use stunt doubles",
    "response": "Would not surprise me"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Would not surprise me",
    "response": "Well they are trained for that"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well they are trained for that",
    "response": "Pretty much"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you think that Dom's car is better than Brians in The original Fast& Furious?",
    "response": "Are you talking about in the end when they are racing"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Are you talking about in the end when they are racing",
    "response": "Yes Dom has a classic car and Brian has a Japanese car"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes Dom has a classic car and Brian has a Japanese car",
    "response": "I think on a straightaway Dom's car wins hands down"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think on a straightaway Dom's car wins hands down",
    "response": "Why do you think that?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why do you think that?",
    "response": "American Muscle had a ton of horsepower, Brians car would win with a lot of curves but that's the only way"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "American Muscle had a ton of horsepower, Brians car would win with a lot of curves but that's the only way",
    "response": "Brian's car had NOS though which should have accounted for extra speed"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Brian's car had NOS though which should have accounted for extra speed",
    "response": "Plus don't forget Dom has been racing his entire life so he could have gotten every bit of speed out of his car"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Plus don't forget Dom has been racing his entire life so he could have gotten every bit of speed out of his car",
    "response": "Yeah I see your point"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah I see your point",
    "response": "Best case scenario they tied"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yo you seen the new fast and furious movie?",
    "response": "Which one is that"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which one is that",
    "response": "Crap I'm not sure"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Crap I'm not sure",
    "response": "Dude me neither"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Dude me neither",
    "response": "Is that the one where what's his name died after"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is that the one where what's his name died after",
    "response": "I think so"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think so",
    "response": "No I don't think it is"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No I don't think it is",
    "response": "You sure?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You sure?",
    "response": "Yeah I'm sure, there's a new one out"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah I'm sure, there's a new one out",
    "response": "Ok naw I haven't seen it then"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen all the Fast and Furious movies?",
    "response": "Nope. I've only seen like the first two and then the 6th one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Nope. I've only seen like the first two and then the 6th one.",
    "response": "Yea, it's pretty ridiculous that they can make so many movies from that one franchise."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, it's pretty ridiculous that they can make so many movies from that one franchise.",
    "response": "I don't get it. I mean I liked the first one alright, but I feel like the other movies would just kind of all be the same storyline."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I don't get it. I mean I liked the first one alright, but I feel like the other movies would just kind of all be the same storyline.",
    "response": "How'd you like the 6th one?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How'd you like the 6th one?",
    "response": "Well first off, I only watched it because it was playing on the airplane I was on."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well first off, I only watched it because it was playing on the airplane I was on.",
    "response": "Haha, so you were basically forced to watch it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Haha, so you were basically forced to watch it?",
    "response": "I guess you could say that. I mean the movie was alright, it was pretty ridiculous at times and I didn't really know/remember half of the characters since it had been so long since I last saw a Fast and Furious movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I guess you could say that. I mean the movie was alright, it was pretty ridiculous at times and I didn't really know/remember half of the characters since it had been so long since I last saw a Fast and Furious movie.",
    "response": "Well maybe you should watch the other ones then. Haha."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well maybe you should watch the other ones then. Haha.",
    "response": "Yea, no thanks. I mean I know of people who really enjoy them, but personally not really my cup of tea."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "My favorite movie is the fast and the furious 6",
    "response": "That was was pretty good"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That was was pretty good",
    "response": "Yea inloved that one the most"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea inloved that one the most",
    "response": "Is so hard to pick for me"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is so hard to pick for me",
    "response": "It is a hard choice"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It is a hard choice",
    "response": "They are all really good"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They are all really good",
    "response": "They are, the whole series was amazing"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They are, the whole series was amazing",
    "response": "I havent seen the newest one yet"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I havent seen the newest one yet",
    "response": "Me either"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me either",
    "response": "I wonder if its good"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "So, what do you think of the new furious movie, the Fate of the Furious?",
    "response": "I watched it in the theaters the other day and it is by far one of my favorites!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I watched it in the theaters the other day and it is by far one of my favorites!",
    "response": "Mine as well. My friends and I watched it just the other day. I can never get enough of Dom and Hobbs."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Mine as well. My friends and I watched it just the other day. I can never get enough of Dom and Hobbs.",
    "response": "Oh! And I can't believe they brought Deckard back."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh! And I can't believe they brought Deckard back.",
    "response": "Lord, I could never imagine that he could be portrayed as a good guy."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Lord, I could never imagine that he could be portrayed as a good guy.",
    "response": "He actually saved Dom's son. The interaction with him and the baby was hilarious."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He actually saved Dom's son. The interaction with him and the baby was hilarious.",
    "response": "The Fate of the Furious was not only great action, but great comedy as well."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The Fate of the Furious was not only great action, but great comedy as well.",
    "response": "All around balanced. I do hope they make more movies in the Furious Franchise, I love to see more of Dom, Letty and Hobbs and maybe more of Deckard as well."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "All around balanced. I do hope they make more movies in the Furious Franchise, I love to see more of Dom, Letty and Hobbs and maybe more of Deckard as well.",
    "response": "i'm sure there will be more to come. They do have a new story to tell after all. Dom's son."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "i'm sure there will be more to come. They do have a new story to tell after all. Dom's son.",
    "response": "cheers!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I am keen on the main actor for the fast and furious series",
    "response": "Which one"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which one",
    "response": "I like Vin diesal"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like Vin diesal",
    "response": "He is really good at acting"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He is really good at acting",
    "response": "he makes the persona come to life"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "he makes the persona come to life",
    "response": "It is as if he is the person he is portraying"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It is as if he is the person he is portraying",
    "response": "I know it is pretty wonderful"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know it is pretty wonderful",
    "response": "Overall i want to see more of his movies"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Overall i want to see more of his movies",
    "response": "Well he is in a lot of the movies"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well he is in a lot of the movies",
    "response": "You know what i mean"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you like the beginning of the original Fast and the Furious movie?",
    "response": "Yes. The car chase was intense."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes. The car chase was intense.",
    "response": "I wondered who those people were with the cars."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I wondered who those people were with the cars.",
    "response": "It was a heart pounding scene."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was a heart pounding scene.",
    "response": "They filmed that chase really good."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They filmed that chase really good.",
    "response": "Yes. That film was directed well."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes. That film was directed well.",
    "response": "What was the most suspenseful part of the scene to you?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What was the most suspenseful part of the scene to you?",
    "response": "When they were about to go into that construction zone."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When they were about to go into that construction zone.",
    "response": "I remember that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I remember that.",
    "response": "That was a really cool intro."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you have a favorite Fast & Furious movie?",
    "response": "At this point I'd say that my favorite is Furious 7. How about you?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "At this point I'd say that my favorite is Furious 7. How about you?",
    "response": "My definite favorite is 2 Fast 2 Furious. That movie's a classic if you ask me."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "My definite favorite is 2 Fast 2 Furious. That movie's a classic if you ask me.",
    "response": "Really? I didn't think it was that good."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Really? I didn't think it was that good.",
    "response": "At first, neither did I. I've just come to appreciate it for the story details it offers."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "At first, neither did I. I've just come to appreciate it for the story details it offers.",
    "response": "What story details?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What story details?",
    "response": "Since it doesn't have Dom or Letty in it, it gives us a better look at characters like Brian, Roman, and Tej."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Since it doesn't have Dom or Letty in it, it gives us a better look at characters like Brian, Roman, and Tej.",
    "response": "I guess that makes sense."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I guess that makes sense.",
    "response": "Overall, though, I definitely still have a soft spot for that movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Overall, though, I definitely still have a soft spot for that movie.",
    "response": "I can definitely respect that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Are you going to see the new Fast & Furious film?",
    "response": "Maybe. It's not the same without Paul Walker."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Maybe. It's not the same without Paul Walker.",
    "response": "Agreed, but the movies are always good, no matter the cast."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Agreed, but the movies are always good, no matter the cast.",
    "response": "I know. Vin Diesel is my favorite actor."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know. Vin Diesel is my favorite actor.",
    "response": "Really? Mine is Dwayne Johnson."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Really? Mine is Dwayne Johnson.",
    "response": "You can't go wrong with that cast!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You can't go wrong with that cast!",
    "response": "I know! And the action is amazing."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know! And the action is amazing.",
    "response": "They sure are highly budgeted films."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They sure are highly budgeted films.",
    "response": "Do you think they will make a ninth film?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you think they will make a ninth film?",
    "response": "No, I doubt it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you by any chance have a favorite character in the Fast & Furious movies?",
    "response": "Honestly, I really don't."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Honestly, I really don't.",
    "response": "Seriously? I thought that everyone has a favorite character in that series."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Seriously? I thought that everyone has a favorite character in that series.",
    "response": "Truth be told, I really don't have a favorite anything in that series."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Truth be told, I really don't have a favorite anything in that series.",
    "response": "But you told me that you watch those movies pretty much all the time."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "But you told me that you watch those movies pretty much all the time.",
    "response": "That's true, but I don't know why."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's true, but I don't know why.",
    "response": "That doesn't make sense."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That doesn't make sense.",
    "response": "Enough about me! Do you have a favorite character in it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Enough about me! Do you have a favorite character in it?",
    "response": "Yeah. Mine's Dominic."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah. Mine's Dominic.",
    "response": "It's because of Vin Diesel, isn't it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Whats your favorite fast and furious movie?",
    "response": "I really like the first one"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I really like the first one",
    "response": "Me too where you find out everything"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too where you find out everything",
    "response": "It hooks you in from the beginning"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It hooks you in from the beginning",
    "response": "Yes it does"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes it does",
    "response": "The first one is great"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The first one is great",
    "response": "I really like them all though"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I really like them all though",
    "response": "Me too"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too",
    "response": "They are exciting"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They are exciting",
    "response": "Exactly"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Okay, yes, Gal Gadot needs to have a resurrection or whatever they do that brings back supposedly killed off characters!",
    "response": "Is that right? That's going to be weird. They killed him off in Tokyo Drift, and then he came back in the Justin Lin ones since they were suppose to have occurred before Tokyo Drift."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is that right? That's going to be weird. They killed him off in Tokyo Drift, and then he came back in the Justin Lin ones since they were suppose to have occurred before Tokyo Drift.",
    "response": "Yeah the whole sequence is a bit confusing if you haven't been following the series the whole way through."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah the whole sequence is a bit confusing if you haven't been following the series the whole way through.",
    "response": "If I remember correctly it goes The Fast and The Furious, 2 Fast 2 Furious, Fast and Furious, Fast Five, Fast & Furious 6, Tokyo Drift, Furious 7, The Fate of the Furious."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "If I remember correctly it goes The Fast and The Furious, 2 Fast 2 Furious, Fast and Furious, Fast Five, Fast & Furious 6, Tokyo Drift, Furious 7, The Fate of the Furious.",
    "response": "You got it. That's the correct chronological order."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You got it. That's the correct chronological order.",
    "response": "It always throws me off since there was also that one short after the first and second one where it covers Paul Walker's trip to Miami and obtaining that Skyline."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It always throws me off since there was also that one short after the first and second one where it covers Paul Walker's trip to Miami and obtaining that Skyline.",
    "response": "The bonus feature, not a lot of people have seen that or know that it exist."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The bonus feature, not a lot of people have seen that or know that it exist.",
    "response": "Yeah it's a fun extra for the fans. I'm looking forward to seeing if they do bring Han back somehow. I wouldn't be surprised."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah it's a fun extra for the fans. I'm looking forward to seeing if they do bring Han back somehow. I wouldn't be surprised.",
    "response": "Yeah they brought back Michelle Rodriguez' character, so I'm not surprised if Han comes back and Gal Gadot needs to come back too!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah they brought back Michelle Rodriguez' character, so I'm not surprised if Han comes back and Gal Gadot needs to come back too!",
    "response": "Okay, yes, Gal Gadot needs to have a resurrection or whatever they do that brings back supposedly killed off characters!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you think The Rock is good for the Fast and Furious franchise?",
    "response": "I do not think he fits"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I do not think he fits",
    "response": "Why is that?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why is that?",
    "response": "Because he tried to take the spotlight from Dom"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Because he tried to take the spotlight from Dom",
    "response": "True"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "True",
    "response": "He is better fit for comedy roles"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He is better fit for comedy roles",
    "response": "Yeah, Fast and Furious is too hardcore for him."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, Fast and Furious is too hardcore for him.",
    "response": "Did you watch the original recently?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you watch the original recently?",
    "response": "Yes. I love it"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes. I love it",
    "response": "Me too"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How do you like Fast Furious?",
    "response": "I think it's a great movie series, if Harry Potter accompanied my childhood, I think Fast and Furious accompanied my teenagehood."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think it's a great movie series, if Harry Potter accompanied my childhood, I think Fast and Furious accompanied my teenagehood.",
    "response": "I kinda feel the same, well you kinda make us look old, haha"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I kinda feel the same, well you kinda make us look old, haha",
    "response": "did I? that wasn't intentional, but which one was your favorite?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "did I? that wasn't intentional, but which one was your favorite?",
    "response": "you remember the one where the crew dragged a safe across the street of Rio?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "you remember the one where the crew dragged a safe across the street of Rio?",
    "response": "oh yeah, it was such a blast in that summer, I can still remember it vividly"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "oh yeah, it was such a blast in that summer, I can still remember it vividly",
    "response": "It's crazy what they can do with cars, do you remember which car they used to drag the safe?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It's crazy what they can do with cars, do you remember which car they used to drag the safe?",
    "response": "that I'm not sure, it seemed to be a bullet proof super tough military SUV"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "that I'm not sure, it seemed to be a bullet proof super tough military SUV",
    "response": "indeed, I don't see myself buying one in the near future"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "indeed, I don't see myself buying one in the near future",
    "response": "me neither"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What did you think of the 3rd Fast & Furious movie?",
    "response": "I had mixed feelings about that one, I mean none of the original characters and some random guy as lead."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I had mixed feelings about that one, I mean none of the original characters and some random guy as lead.",
    "response": "Yeah I get what you mean, but it was still pretty cool."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah I get what you mean, but it was still pretty cool.",
    "response": "Yeah especially when Han was showing off why he drifts and the girl passes him her phone number."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah especially when Han was showing off why he drifts and the girl passes him her phone number.",
    "response": "I was thinking the same thing. What did you think about Twink's ride."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I was thinking the same thing. What did you think about Twink's ride.",
    "response": "The green Hulk mobile?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The green Hulk mobile?",
    "response": "Yeah, I though it was pretty sweet."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, I though it was pretty sweet.",
    "response": "You also think tires are free don't you?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You also think tires are free don't you?",
    "response": "Well obviously someone liked it or it wouldn't be in the movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well obviously someone liked it or it wouldn't be in the movie.",
    "response": "Obviously they only liked it enough to have it in like 2 scenes for comic relief."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I love how the rock got involved with these movies",
    "response": "Me too"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too",
    "response": "The fast and furious has vin diesel and the rock"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The fast and furious has vin diesel and the rock",
    "response": "What more could a movie have"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What more could a movie have",
    "response": "I dont think anything"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I dont think anything",
    "response": "These movies are perfect"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "These movies are perfect",
    "response": "I wish paul walker was still around though"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I wish paul walker was still around though",
    "response": "Me too"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too",
    "response": "That would be better"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That would be better",
    "response": "Yes it would"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is there anything about the Fast & Furious series that you particularly like?",
    "response": "That would definitely be the action."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That would definitely be the action.",
    "response": "I knew it! Which one do you think had the best action scenes?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I knew it! Which one do you think had the best action scenes?",
    "response": "That's definitely Furious 7."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's definitely Furious 7.",
    "response": "Some of those scenes were ridiculous!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Some of those scenes were ridiculous!",
    "response": "I know! Driving sports cars through buildings in Dubai? That's just nuts!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know! Driving sports cars through buildings in Dubai? That's just nuts!",
    "response": "But you have to admit, it makes for great fun."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "But you have to admit, it makes for great fun.",
    "response": "Of course. That's why I liked it as much as I did."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Of course. That's why I liked it as much as I did.",
    "response": "I also liked how in the first few minutes, Luke literally gives a Rock Bottom to one of the bad guys."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I also liked how in the first few minutes, Luke literally gives a Rock Bottom to one of the bad guys.",
    "response": "You know, sometimes I forget that Dwayne Johnson was ever a wrestler."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Am I the only one that gets sort of angry at the Fast & Furious characters?",
    "response": "In what sense?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "In what sense?",
    "response": "In that those guys are all villains.  They are actual bad guys."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "In that those guys are all villains.  They are actual bad guys.",
    "response": "Now that you mention it, they are all thieves and crooks."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Now that you mention it, they are all thieves and crooks.",
    "response": "More than that even, it's their total disregard for everyone outside of their \"family.\""
  },
  {
    "prompt": "More than that even, it's their total disregard for everyone outside of their \"family.\"",
    "response": "That is so true.  In 'Fast Five,' they basically destroyed parts of Brazil while dragging that bank vault with their cars."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That is so true.  In 'Fast Five,' they basically destroyed parts of Brazil while dragging that bank vault with their cars.",
    "response": "And don't forget 'The Fate of the Furious' when they go to Germany and kill a bunch of police officers who try to stop them from stealing."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "And don't forget 'The Fate of the Furious' when they go to Germany and kill a bunch of police officers who try to stop them from stealing.",
    "response": "That was even worse.  They always cheer and have a good time about it too."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That was even worse.  They always cheer and have a good time about it too.",
    "response": "I think that's why for me, I just can't sympathize with any of them."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think that's why for me, I just can't sympathize with any of them.",
    "response": "It's very hard to root for characters with such few morals!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey man what is good",
    "response": "Nothing much watching some movies"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Nothing much watching some movies",
    "response": "What movies"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What movies",
    "response": "The first fast and furious movie"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The first fast and furious movie",
    "response": "I absolutely love that one"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I absolutely love that one",
    "response": "It is the best still to me"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It is the best still to me",
    "response": "I do not like most of the sequels"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I do not like most of the sequels",
    "response": "They were not that bad"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They were not that bad",
    "response": "Some of them were come on"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Some of them were come on",
    "response": "Not really man"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How many movies are in The Fast and the Furious franchise?",
    "response": "Eight"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Eight",
    "response": "Are they all good?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Are they all good?",
    "response": "Yes and the first one is the best."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes and the first one is the best.",
    "response": "How many directors did it have?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How many directors did it have?",
    "response": "There have been 5 so far."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "There have been 5 so far.",
    "response": "What is the name of Vin Diesel's character?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the name of Vin Diesel's character?",
    "response": "Dom"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Dom",
    "response": "There were a lot of stunts in that movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "There were a lot of stunts in that movie.",
    "response": "Yes and it was very thrilling."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen any of the Fast and Furious movies?",
    "response": "I think I have. I liked them."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think I have. I liked them.",
    "response": "Do they seem ok for kids?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do they seem ok for kids?",
    "response": "No probably not."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No probably not.",
    "response": "Ok. My son likes cars and was asking about these movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Ok. My son likes cars and was asking about these movies.",
    "response": "How did he hear about them?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How did he hear about them?",
    "response": "His friend showed him some of one of the movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "His friend showed him some of one of the movies.",
    "response": "Oh and now he wants to watch the rest?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh and now he wants to watch the rest?",
    "response": "Yeah exactly."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah exactly.",
    "response": "Well you could pre-screen the first movie and see what you think."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What was your favorite fast and furious movie?",
    "response": "The 1st one and the one that takes place in Brazil."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The 1st one and the one that takes place in Brazil.",
    "response": "Yeah those were cool, they had lots of action."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah those were cool, they had lots of action.",
    "response": "I liked when big safe of money was being chased in Brazil."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I liked when big safe of money was being chased in Brazil.",
    "response": "Oh yeah, big action scene."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh yeah, big action scene.",
    "response": "So much action!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "So much action!",
    "response": "Who is your favorite character?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who is your favorite character?",
    "response": "Vin Diesel."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Vin Diesel.",
    "response": "Oh yeah, I like Ludacris."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh yeah, I like Ludacris.",
    "response": "Because he's so manly."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which Fast & Furious character do you like out of all the movies?",
    "response": "Well my favorite Character of all the Fast and Furious Characters is Paul Walker. Broke my heart when he passed."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well my favorite Character of all the Fast and Furious Characters is Paul Walker. Broke my heart when he passed.",
    "response": "Yeah mine too such a tragedy to loose a fellow cast member in real life."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah mine too such a tragedy to loose a fellow cast member in real life.",
    "response": "Despite the tragedy , the Fast and Furious movies are really good. I mean they gross 207.3 million USD on their very first of the trilogy ."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Despite the tragedy , the Fast and Furious movies are really good. I mean they gross 207.3 million USD on their very first of the trilogy .",
    "response": "Rob Cohen really knew what he was doing with the story line to capture an audience."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Rob Cohen really knew what he was doing with the story line to capture an audience.",
    "response": "I heard they got a 53% on rotten tomatoes critics, for Fast and the Furious."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I heard they got a 53% on rotten tomatoes critics, for Fast and the Furious.",
    "response": "Really honestly after Fate and the Furious will there be anymore Furious movies?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Really honestly after Fate and the Furious will there be anymore Furious movies?",
    "response": "Don't get your ducks in a row, but their just might be a Fast and the Furious 9."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Don't get your ducks in a row, but their just might be a Fast and the Furious 9.",
    "response": "You really think so I will be excited but now too excited like now they are dragging it!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You really think so I will be excited but now too excited like now they are dragging it!",
    "response": "Dragging it or not I am confident they will make sales Rob Cohen is a good director. he will capture the audience."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you see the new Fast and Furious movie?",
    "response": "Fast 8, yeah it was good."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Fast 8, yeah it was good.",
    "response": "What was your favorite part?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What was your favorite part?",
    "response": "I thought the part with him fighting people while having the baby wear headphones was funny."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I thought the part with him fighting people while having the baby wear headphones was funny.",
    "response": "Yeah that was funny, but why did he put the headphones on full blast?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah that was funny, but why did he put the headphones on full blast?",
    "response": "I don't know."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I don't know.",
    "response": "Have you ever accidentally had the volume real loud on some headphones? It's aweful. Can't be good for a baby."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you ever accidentally had the volume real loud on some headphones? It's aweful. Can't be good for a baby.",
    "response": "No you're right. What about the camera in the necklace? How did Dom know how to do all that?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No you're right. What about the camera in the necklace? How did Dom know how to do all that?",
    "response": "I don't know, he's Dom. He can do anything. He grew up just a street racer, but now can take down international terrorists."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I don't know, he's Dom. He can do anything. He grew up just a street racer, but now can take down international terrorists.",
    "response": "True. I guess your right. Just don't think too hard about it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hi.",
    "response": "Hey."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey.",
    "response": "Would you consider yourself a fan of fast and the furious?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Would you consider yourself a fan of fast and the furious?",
    "response": "Yeah I would say so, but not a huge fan or anything."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah I would say so, but not a huge fan or anything.",
    "response": "Yeah I would say the same about myself."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah I would say the same about myself.",
    "response": "Do you have a favorite movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you have a favorite movie?",
    "response": "I liked the first one the best."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I liked the first one the best.",
    "response": "I saw the first one on the other day and it took me back."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I saw the first one on the other day and it took me back.",
    "response": "Yeah reminds me of where I was when that came out."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah reminds me of where I was when that came out.",
    "response": "Hard to believe they're still making them."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey, do you like fast and furious?",
    "response": "Yea, I mean, they aren't great movies but they sure are fun!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, I mean, they aren't great movies but they sure are fun!",
    "response": "Which one is your favorite?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which one is your favorite?",
    "response": "Definitely Tokyo Drift."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Definitely Tokyo Drift.",
    "response": "Me too, Han was awesome in that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too, Han was awesome in that.",
    "response": "Yea, too bad they killed him off."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, too bad they killed him off.",
    "response": "Yea, but he still came back on the next movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, but he still came back on the next movie.",
    "response": "Yea, since it was about the past."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, since it was about the past.",
    "response": "Did you know wonder woman played his girlfriend?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you know wonder woman played his girlfriend?",
    "response": "Yea, he's lucky!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Where do you think they filmed Fast and the Furious?",
    "response": "California"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "California",
    "response": "It must have been hard to shoot it"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It must have been hard to shoot it",
    "response": "Yeah. Closing down all of those streets must have been tough."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah. Closing down all of those streets must have been tough.",
    "response": "I agree. It's a complicated project."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I agree. It's a complicated project.",
    "response": "Did you enjoy the races?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you enjoy the races?",
    "response": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes",
    "response": "What was your favorite part?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What was your favorite part?",
    "response": "The story Dom told about his dad."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The story Dom told about his dad.",
    "response": "That was sad. It told a lot about his character though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I just saw The Fate of the Furious.",
    "response": "No Paul Walker, sadly."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No Paul Walker, sadly.",
    "response": "Otherwise the same crew - Vinny Diesel, Dwayne Johnson, Michelle Rodriguez."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Otherwise the same crew - Vinny Diesel, Dwayne Johnson, Michelle Rodriguez.",
    "response": "Who directed?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who directed?",
    "response": "F. Gary Gray."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "F. Gary Gray.",
    "response": "Any new stars?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Any new stars?",
    "response": "Charlize Theron is the protagonist."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Charlize Theron is the protagonist.",
    "response": "I loved her in Monster."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I loved her in Monster.",
    "response": "It's nice that Dom names his son Brian."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It's nice that Dom names his son Brian.",
    "response": "Very good touch."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What was the first one about? The original",
    "response": "The original was in 2001. It was about how the group was under investigation and the cop guy falls for the sister"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The original was in 2001. It was about how the group was under investigation and the cop guy falls for the sister",
    "response": "Oh yeah, That Brewster chick. She's hot."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh yeah, That Brewster chick. She's hot.",
    "response": "MIa Torretto. That's funny how Vin Diesel gets an italian name. He's black"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "MIa Torretto. That's funny how Vin Diesel gets an italian name. He's black",
    "response": "But he could pass for an Italian."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "But he could pass for an Italian.",
    "response": "I guess that's the entire point. Diesel made a movie about himself and his multiracial background. That's how he was discovered initially by Spielberg."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I guess that's the entire point. Diesel made a movie about himself and his multiracial background. That's how he was discovered initially by Spielberg.",
    "response": "Going from Saving Private Ryan to Fast and Furious. That's a huge change."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Going from Saving Private Ryan to Fast and Furious. That's a huge change.",
    "response": "I love that car though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I love that car though.",
    "response": "1970 Dodge charger."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "1970 Dodge charger.",
    "response": "I was like so sad when that car was totaled. That's just wrong man."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you see the last Fast and Furious movie?",
    "response": "Is that the seventh one?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is that the seventh one?",
    "response": "No, it is the eigth one, Fate of the Furious"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No, it is the eigth one, Fate of the Furious",
    "response": "Then no, I am behind a movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Then no, I am behind a movie.",
    "response": "It is good, the Rock is great in it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It is good, the Rock is great in it.",
    "response": "He is the best part now, Dom in overrated."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He is the best part now, Dom in overrated.",
    "response": "Agreed, I cannot wait for his movie with Jason."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Agreed, I cannot wait for his movie with Jason.",
    "response": "Yes, that is a spinoff I will see."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, that is a spinoff I will see.",
    "response": "Which one is your favorite moive?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which one is your favorite moive?",
    "response": "I like Fast Five, I still miss Giselle."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Man I wonder something",
    "response": "Sure what do you wonder"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Sure what do you wonder",
    "response": "I wonder if Vin diesel can actually drive like he does in the movies"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I wonder if Vin diesel can actually drive like he does in the movies",
    "response": "Well i am sure he has to perform some of his stunts"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well i am sure he has to perform some of his stunts",
    "response": "I am not really talking about the stunts"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I am not really talking about the stunts",
    "response": "What are you talking about"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What are you talking about",
    "response": "Just the driving in general"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Just the driving in general",
    "response": "Well it would be possible"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well it would be possible",
    "response": "I guess"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I guess",
    "response": "I mean i am sure its not fake"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What do you think of the upcoming Fate of the Furious?",
    "response": "Personally I can't believe they are doing an 8th film."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Personally I can't believe they are doing an 8th film.",
    "response": "I know right? I mean I'm all for a movie about cars, and racing them, but come on!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know right? I mean I'm all for a movie about cars, and racing them, but come on!",
    "response": "I know right? Its kind of completely lost its touch."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know right? Its kind of completely lost its touch.",
    "response": "It's like the entire movie has forgotten the reason why the movie was put together in the first place."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It's like the entire movie has forgotten the reason why the movie was put together in the first place.",
    "response": "Right? The movie just needs to go back to the basics, fast cars, fast women, and good times."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Right? The movie just needs to go back to the basics, fast cars, fast women, and good times.",
    "response": "At least they still have most of the original characters."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "At least they still have most of the original characters.",
    "response": "Yea, my favorite is Dom, I'm really wondering what is up with him in this latest movie tho."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, my favorite is Dom, I'm really wondering what is up with him in this latest movie tho.",
    "response": "Yea it really looks like he's going to be a bad guy."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea it really looks like he's going to be a bad guy.",
    "response": "Yea what do you think that's all about?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "So you said that you're a fan of Furious 7?",
    "response": "Yes, I am. I really liked that movie when I first watched it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, I am. I really liked that movie when I first watched it.",
    "response": "What did you like about it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What did you like about it?",
    "response": "There was a lot of things. It'd be hard to tell you just one......"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "There was a lot of things. It'd be hard to tell you just one......",
    "response": "Well break it down for me!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well break it down for me!",
    "response": "I really liked the story, especially what they ended up doing with Brian's character."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I really liked the story, especially what they ended up doing with Brian's character.",
    "response": "Right. I was very nervous about what they'd do with him after Paul's passing."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Right. I was very nervous about what they'd do with him after Paul's passing.",
    "response": "Same here, but I think they handled it the best way they possibly could."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Same here, but I think they handled it the best way they possibly could.",
    "response": "So many people cried during that closing scene, didn't they?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "So many people cried during that closing scene, didn't they?",
    "response": "You bet. I counted at least ten people immediately next to me all in tears inside the theater."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Whos is your favorite Fast and Furious character?",
    "response": "I like Dom"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like Dom",
    "response": "Same here. Did you like Paul Walker's character too?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Same here. Did you like Paul Walker's character too?",
    "response": "Yes, he was cool."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, he was cool.",
    "response": "Which movie did you like the most?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which movie did you like the most?",
    "response": "The first one"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The first one",
    "response": "Yeah, me too."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, me too.",
    "response": "I think the second one got too big."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think the second one got too big.",
    "response": "Yeah, the first one was more about street racing and cars."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, the first one was more about street racing and cars.",
    "response": "It was. I loved the drag race."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "So what did you think about Fast & Furious 7 ?",
    "response": "That's the one where Paul Walker was still alive right ?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's the one where Paul Walker was still alive right ?",
    "response": "Yea he was able to act for some of the movie, his brother had to do the rest with the help of CGI."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea he was able to act for some of the movie, his brother had to do the rest with the help of CGI.",
    "response": "Wow, I couldn't even tell that it wasn't Paul himself acting."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Wow, I couldn't even tell that it wasn't Paul himself acting.",
    "response": "Yes, the movie was done so well a long with the outstanding acting from the crew."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, the movie was done so well a long with the outstanding acting from the crew.",
    "response": "Yep, so who was you're favorite character in the movie ?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yep, so who was you're favorite character in the movie ?",
    "response": "Well if i'm being honest it would be Paul."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well if i'm being honest it would be Paul.",
    "response": "Me too, it's sad he passed away."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too, it's sad he passed away.",
    "response": "What do you think about their decision about containing the series ?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What do you think about their decision about containing the series ?",
    "response": "I think that it was a great spot to stop at in the story-line and with Paul gone,but we'll have to see how it goes."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hi.",
    "response": "Hey."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey.",
    "response": "Have you seen any of the fast and furious movies?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen any of the fast and furious movies?",
    "response": "Yeah."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah.",
    "response": "Do you have a favorite?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you have a favorite?",
    "response": "I like 5."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like 5.",
    "response": "Is that the one in Brazil?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is that the one in Brazil?",
    "response": "No, it's the one where they take on a cartel in mexico"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No, it's the one where they take on a cartel in mexico",
    "response": "Oh I don't think I saw that one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh I don't think I saw that one.",
    "response": "It's quite good."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like the first two Fast & Furious movies the best.",
    "response": "I liked them all pretty much."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I liked them all pretty much.",
    "response": "Did you like Paul Walker?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you like Paul Walker?",
    "response": "Yes for sure."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes for sure.",
    "response": "It was a shame when he died him and Vin Diesel together made those movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was a shame when he died him and Vin Diesel together made those movies.",
    "response": "I know and to die in a car."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know and to die in a car.",
    "response": "His brother stepped in for one of the movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "His brother stepped in for one of the movies.",
    "response": "Did you see that one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you see that one.",
    "response": "Yes I did."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes I did.",
    "response": "I think they did a good job with what they had to work with."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen the movie Fast Five?",
    "response": "No, I haven't. Is it in the Fast and Furious series?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No, I haven't. Is it in the Fast and Furious series?",
    "response": "Yeah, it is. It came out two years after the first one with Paul Walker."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, it is. It came out two years after the first one with Paul Walker.",
    "response": "Oh, what is this one about?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh, what is this one about?",
    "response": "Paul Walker and Vin Diesel's characters have to team up again to escape from the authorities."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Paul Walker and Vin Diesel's characters have to team up again to escape from the authorities.",
    "response": "That sounds similar to the first one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That sounds similar to the first one.",
    "response": "It is similar, but this time they're the bad guys instead of the good guys."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It is similar, but this time they're the bad guys instead of the good guys.",
    "response": "Oh, okay. Who else is in the movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh, okay. Who else is in the movie?",
    "response": "Dwayne Johnson plays a federal agent."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Dwayne Johnson plays a federal agent.",
    "response": "That's cool, I really like him."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen the latest Fast and the Furious movie?",
    "response": "Which one is that? Fast 10?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which one is that? Fast 10?",
    "response": "No it's The Fate of the Furious!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No it's The Fate of the Furious!",
    "response": "So, Fast 8? Which one is the one that Paul Walker was in?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "So, Fast 8? Which one is the one that Paul Walker was in?",
    "response": "That was Furious 7, this one's the 8th one or something like that since they're numbered weird."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That was Furious 7, this one's the 8th one or something like that since they're numbered weird.",
    "response": "How did they handle the lack of Paul Walker?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How did they handle the lack of Paul Walker?",
    "response": "They just mentioned Brian and Mia but that they're retired and not apart of the team anymore."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They just mentioned Brian and Mia but that they're retired and not apart of the team anymore.",
    "response": "Oh that's nice, and I guess a respectful way to deal with him being gone instead of dying like other characters."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh that's nice, and I guess a respectful way to deal with him being gone instead of dying like other characters.",
    "response": "Yeah! Its a different tone I think, but not that bad."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah! Its a different tone I think, but not that bad.",
    "response": "Okay, I'll watch it!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like the first Fast & Furious movie because I loved that classic car.",
    "response": "Yes that is awesome."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes that is awesome.",
    "response": "Dom was afraid to drive it but did that car was pretty fast."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Dom was afraid to drive it but did that car was pretty fast.",
    "response": "Yes I wish I could drive that car."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes I wish I could drive that car.",
    "response": "You like Vin Diesel?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You like Vin Diesel?",
    "response": "Yes he is pretty cool."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes he is pretty cool.",
    "response": "You don't see many actors that are in most of the series of movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You don't see many actors that are in most of the series of movies.",
    "response": "No and he is in the new one. The Rock is also in the new one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No and he is in the new one. The Rock is also in the new one.",
    "response": "I like The Rock too."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like The Rock too.",
    "response": "I used to watch him back when he wrestled I guess that was the 90's."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which movie from the Fast & Furious franchise did you enjoy the most?",
    "response": "I actually liked the first one the most."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I actually liked the first one the most.",
    "response": "Why is that one your favorite?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why is that one your favorite?",
    "response": "Well it's the first one so it was all new it had never been done before and we didn't know what to expect, plus they did an awesome job."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well it's the first one so it was all new it had never been done before and we didn't know what to expect, plus they did an awesome job.",
    "response": "That's a good point, the first movie was a roller coaster for me."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's a good point, the first movie was a roller coaster for me.",
    "response": "I felt the same, after that you kind of knew what to expect."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I felt the same, after that you kind of knew what to expect.",
    "response": "Is it one of your favorite movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is it one of your favorite movies.",
    "response": "Yes, though it's not my most favorite movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, though it's not my most favorite movie.",
    "response": "Do you ever wonder what it would be like to be in that movie to be Dom or Brian?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you ever wonder what it would be like to be in that movie to be Dom or Brian?",
    "response": "I think I would have liked to be Dom he's such an interesting character."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What did you think of Tokyo Drift.",
    "response": "For some reason that movie sticks out in my head the most of the franchise."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "For some reason that movie sticks out in my head the most of the franchise.",
    "response": "In a good or bad way?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "In a good or bad way?",
    "response": "Bad, it was really cheesy and had none of the main characters."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Bad, it was really cheesy and had none of the main characters.",
    "response": "Yea, neither Paul nor Vin were in it as main characters."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, neither Paul nor Vin were in it as main characters.",
    "response": "Also the music and cars were silly."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Also the music and cars were silly.",
    "response": "Yea, they really went crazy with the cars."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, they really went crazy with the cars.",
    "response": "Maybe they thought since they were in Japan they needed to up the strange factor."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Maybe they thought since they were in Japan they needed to up the strange factor.",
    "response": "Yea, most seemed like toys that would never be driving on a road."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, most seemed like toys that would never be driving on a road.",
    "response": "Yea, that black and orange one in particular."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen the newest Fast & Furious movie?",
    "response": "No. I thought that the trailer made it look really silly."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No. I thought that the trailer made it look really silly.",
    "response": "What makes you say that?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What makes you say that?",
    "response": "I just find it silly that it evolved from street racing to basically vehicular warfare."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I just find it silly that it evolved from street racing to basically vehicular warfare.",
    "response": "Okay, well that does sound pretty silly."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Okay, well that does sound pretty silly.",
    "response": "My point exactly. That's why I didn't watch the new one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "My point exactly. That's why I didn't watch the new one.",
    "response": "Oh. Well, I watched it, and I definitely thought it was alright."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh. Well, I watched it, and I definitely thought it was alright.",
    "response": "Was there anything too remarkable about it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Was there anything too remarkable about it?",
    "response": "It had great looking action scenes."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It had great looking action scenes.",
    "response": "That's about what I expected."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What does Paul Walker play in the first movie?",
    "response": "He plays an undercover cop"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He plays an undercover cop",
    "response": "Wow. That sounds pretty cool. I bet it is thrilling."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Wow. That sounds pretty cool. I bet it is thrilling.",
    "response": "It is and he falls for a girl in it and everyone eventually finds out he is a cop."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It is and he falls for a girl in it and everyone eventually finds out he is a cop.",
    "response": "Dodes the girl leave him after that?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Dodes the girl leave him after that?",
    "response": "No, because he helps save her brother Dominic."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No, because he helps save her brother Dominic.",
    "response": "Sounds cool. I love cars."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Sounds cool. I love cars.",
    "response": "That movie is all about cars."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That movie is all about cars.",
    "response": "Who is another actor in it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who is another actor in it?",
    "response": "Michelle Rodriguez."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen any of the Fast and Furious movies?",
    "response": "I don't think I have but I know about them from watching their trailers on tv."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I don't think I have but I know about them from watching their trailers on tv.",
    "response": "Yeah, me too.  They look okay, kind of interesting."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, me too.  They look okay, kind of interesting.",
    "response": "Didn't one of the main actors die a year or so ago?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Didn't one of the main actors die a year or so ago?",
    "response": "I think he did.  I think it's a little wierd that they keep making the movies and using his image in them."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think he did.  I think it's a little wierd that they keep making the movies and using his image in them.",
    "response": "I totally agree with that. It's a little creepy."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I totally agree with that. It's a little creepy.",
    "response": "On the flip side, the car chase and race seens look pretty cool."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "On the flip side, the car chase and race seens look pretty cool.",
    "response": "They really do. I do like Vin Diesel too."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They really do. I do like Vin Diesel too.",
    "response": "Me too.  I'd like to see one or more of the movies just because he's in them."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too.  I'd like to see one or more of the movies just because he's in them.",
    "response": "The newest one is called The fate of the Furious and it's got some big name actors in it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you see that plane scene in the end of fast and furious 5?",
    "response": "Yes, I did."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, I did.",
    "response": "It seems like it was infinite runway."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It seems like it was infinite runway.",
    "response": "Yes, I mean the last 15 minutes was plane running on runway."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, I mean the last 15 minutes was plane running on runway.",
    "response": "They should add that runway to world record."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They should add that runway to world record.",
    "response": "I don't see such flaws in english movies usually."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I don't see such flaws in english movies usually.",
    "response": "Yes, Even I was surprised to see that scene."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, Even I was surprised to see that scene.",
    "response": "But how was the movie otherwise besides that scene?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "But how was the movie otherwise besides that scene?",
    "response": "Well, I haven't seen any movie turn out to be good which has problems with ending."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, I haven't seen any movie turn out to be good which has problems with ending.",
    "response": "I agree, A bad ending is usually the entire movie killer."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What's your favorite scene out of all the Fast & the Furious movies?",
    "response": "Can't believe you're asking this question, but everyone's favorite scene should be Brian and Dom's first race..."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Can't believe you're asking this question, but everyone's favorite scene should be Brian and Dom's first race...",
    "response": "That honestly feels like sooo long ago! Refresh my memory, I haven't watched the orginial movie in years."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That honestly feels like sooo long ago! Refresh my memory, I haven't watched the orginial movie in years.",
    "response": "Brian's an undercover cop and tries to infiltrate Dom's shop to catch a group of street racer theives. Dom doesn't take kindly to Brian snooping around but Brian challenges Dom to a street race, something Dom cannot turn down."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Brian's an undercover cop and tries to infiltrate Dom's shop to catch a group of street racer theives. Dom doesn't take kindly to Brian snooping around but Brian challenges Dom to a street race, something Dom cannot turn down.",
    "response": "I remember now! That scene really was epic. It laid the groundwork for all the movies that followed. Crazy."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I remember now! That scene really was epic. It laid the groundwork for all the movies that followed. Crazy.",
    "response": "Dom and Brian aren't close friends yet but the core dynamic of their relationship is established with that one race. Really set the pace for everything."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Dom and Brian aren't close friends yet but the core dynamic of their relationship is established with that one race. Really set the pace for everything.",
    "response": "What did Brian tell Dom at the end of that first race?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What did Brian tell Dom at the end of that first race?",
    "response": "Brian shouted, \"Dude, I almost had you!\" with Dom responding in typical Dom fashion saying, \"You almost had me? You never had me. You never had your car! Granny shifting, not double clutching like you should...you\u2019re lucky that hundred shot of NOS didn\u2019t blow the welds on the intake...you almost had me?\""
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Brian shouted, \"Dude, I almost had you!\" with Dom responding in typical Dom fashion saying, \"You almost had me? You never had me. You never had your car! Granny shifting, not double clutching like you should...you\u2019re lucky that hundred shot of NOS didn\u2019t blow the welds on the intake...you almost had me?\"",
    "response": "Even with Dom humiliating Brian after that first race he still seems fond of Brian\u2019s competitive energy."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Even with Dom humiliating Brian after that first race he still seems fond of Brian\u2019s competitive energy.",
    "response": "Brian and Dom were like a match made in heaven. All together a great duo."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey.",
    "response": "Hi."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hi.",
    "response": "Have you seen any of the fast and the furious movies?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen any of the fast and the furious movies?",
    "response": "Yeah I think I've seen them all or at least most of them."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah I think I've seen them all or at least most of them.",
    "response": "Do you have one you like the best?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you have one you like the best?",
    "response": "The last one was pretty good."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The last one was pretty good.",
    "response": "7?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "7?",
    "response": "Yeah I think so."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah I think so.",
    "response": "There was that sad part at the end?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "There was that sad part at the end?",
    "response": "With Paul Walker?  Yeah that was very sad."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "So the 8 is then what?",
    "response": "It's currently out in the theaters. We should go watch it"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It's currently out in the theaters. We should go watch it",
    "response": "What's it about, though"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What's it about, though",
    "response": "I guess the same stuff. Except Dom gets seduced by this girl. Or something."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I guess the same stuff. Except Dom gets seduced by this girl. Or something.",
    "response": "But he's married?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "But he's married?",
    "response": "Yep. And he goes off and gets Hobbs arrested while stealing some EMP thing for the girl, so they can go steal the God's eye"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yep. And he goes off and gets Hobbs arrested while stealing some EMP thing for the girl, so they can go steal the God's eye",
    "response": "God's eye again. That's kinda getting old."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "God's eye again. That's kinda getting old.",
    "response": "Well, that's the premise anyway. Anyway this Cipher girl blackmails Dom to doing more jobs for her."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, that's the premise anyway. Anyway this Cipher girl blackmails Dom to doing more jobs for her.",
    "response": "And the English guy joins the team? Deckard guy from Furious 7?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "And the English guy joins the team? Deckard guy from Furious 7?",
    "response": "Looks that way, Maybe he wanted in the action. i don't know. Anyway, we should go see it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I just saw Fast & Furious 6.",
    "response": "What did you think?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What did you think?",
    "response": "I thought it was really good!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I thought it was really good!",
    "response": "Me too!  What did you like most about it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too!  What did you like most about it?",
    "response": "I really liked the set and how amazing it looked against the racing cars."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I really liked the set and how amazing it looked against the racing cars.",
    "response": "Yeah that was really cool.  They really outdid themselves with the special effects this time."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah that was really cool.  They really outdid themselves with the special effects this time.",
    "response": "I also really liked the addition of Luke Evans and his character."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I also really liked the addition of Luke Evans and his character.",
    "response": "He really added to the plot being the mastermind of the mercernaries."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He really added to the plot being the mastermind of the mercernaries.",
    "response": "Yeah it was crazy. I'm glad you told me to watch it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah it was crazy. I'm glad you told me to watch it.",
    "response": "You're welcome!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen the new movie Fast & Furious 8?",
    "response": "No, I saw  the trailer it looks like it is going to be another great movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No, I saw  the trailer it looks like it is going to be another great movie.",
    "response": "I have seen Fast & Furious 2."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I have seen Fast & Furious 2.",
    "response": "The movies are filled with lots of action and drag racing."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The movies are filled with lots of action and drag racing.",
    "response": "They also have great cars."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They also have great cars.",
    "response": "Do you have a favorite out of all eight movies?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you have a favorite out of all eight movies?",
    "response": "Fast & Furious 2, road of rage was pretty good."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Fast & Furious 2, road of rage was pretty good.",
    "response": "Do you like all those cool cars in the movies, like the Honda Civic Coup.and the Ford?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you like all those cool cars in the movies, like the Honda Civic Coup.and the Ford?",
    "response": "Yes, there is also was a scene in the movie were someone is driving a cool Mitsubishi Gto car."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, there is also was a scene in the movie were someone is driving a cool Mitsubishi Gto car.",
    "response": "The Fast & Furious movies are fun to watch, and the viewers will be sitting on the edge of their seats through the whole picture."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "what do you think about role of mia in fast and furious series?",
    "response": "What do you mean?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What do you mean?",
    "response": "I mean is she necessary character?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I mean is she necessary character?",
    "response": "I think she does have some role in whole story."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think she does have some role in whole story.",
    "response": "But what I am asking can the series survive without her?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "But what I am asking can the series survive without her?",
    "response": "I think the series can survive without her, but still she does play some role."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think the series can survive without her, but still she does play some role.",
    "response": "Anyways, there are lots of other characters which can be removed."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Anyways, there are lots of other characters which can be removed.",
    "response": "I do not agree, I mean many of those characters make the whole series more interesting."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I do not agree, I mean many of those characters make the whole series more interesting.",
    "response": "I can agree to ron's character on that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I can agree to ron's character on that.",
    "response": "Oh yes, he makes the whole series amusing."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen all of the Fast and Furious movies?",
    "response": "Yes, I have seen all of them. Sad to see Paul Walker Die"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, I have seen all of them. Sad to see Paul Walker Die",
    "response": "Yeah, it sure was a tragedy"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, it sure was a tragedy",
    "response": "Do you have a favorite movie?  Mine was the last one \"Fate of the Furious?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you have a favorite movie?  Mine was the last one \"Fate of the Furious?",
    "response": "Not really, I am not a huge fan of the movies.  I watch them, but only once they come to DVD"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Not really, I am not a huge fan of the movies.  I watch them, but only once they come to DVD",
    "response": "What don't you like about them?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What don't you like about them?",
    "response": "Well, I love the Rock so I'm glad they added him, but the stories are lame as hell."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, I love the Rock so I'm glad they added him, but the stories are lame as hell.",
    "response": "Really, I think they are cool.  I love the action in the movies and the car scenes are great."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Really, I think they are cool.  I love the action in the movies and the car scenes are great.",
    "response": "I guess if your a car guy you could.  I'm not and the chase scenes are ridiculously fake"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I guess if your a car guy you could.  I'm not and the chase scenes are ridiculously fake",
    "response": "Aww, come on man.  They are just fun to watch."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hi.",
    "response": "Hey."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey.",
    "response": "Do you like the fast and the furious?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you like the fast and the furious?",
    "response": "I liked it a lot when I was in high school."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I liked it a lot when I was in high school.",
    "response": "Don't like them now?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Don't like them now?",
    "response": "I haven't seen one in a long time."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I haven't seen one in a long time.",
    "response": "What was the last one that you saw?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What was the last one that you saw?",
    "response": "Maybe the 4th one?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Maybe the 4th one?",
    "response": "The one in mexico?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The one in mexico?",
    "response": "Yeah I think so."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hmmm i am not so sure i like this movie",
    "response": "What movies are you watching"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What movies are you watching",
    "response": "Well i got bored so i decided to binge watch a series"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well i got bored so i decided to binge watch a series",
    "response": "What series did you binge watch"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What series did you binge watch",
    "response": "Fast and the furious series i am just not getting it"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Fast and the furious series i am just not getting it",
    "response": "Yeah binge watching them may not be the best idea"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah binge watching them may not be the best idea",
    "response": "I know now that i have"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know now that i have",
    "response": "Yeah they are best in moderate doses"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah they are best in moderate doses",
    "response": "I am gonna try to watch the rest with breaks might enjoy them more"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I am gonna try to watch the rest with breaks might enjoy them more",
    "response": "Hopefully you do"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "So I think they should have stopped making the movies when Paul Walker died.",
    "response": "I don't know man, I think that's unfair to fans who didn't have him front and center, other characters have strong followings too."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I don't know man, I think that's unfair to fans who didn't have him front and center, other characters have strong followings too.",
    "response": "Well, I don't see how it's not going to be on everyone's mind when they watch any of them from now on."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, I don't see how it's not going to be on everyone's mind when they watch any of them from now on.",
    "response": "I think the character Dom is strong enough, and the fan base big enough they will be fine."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think the character Dom is strong enough, and the fan base big enough they will be fine.",
    "response": "I guess but I still feel it's a bit tacky."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I guess but I still feel it's a bit tacky.",
    "response": "It's business, and the movies are mostly about the cars and the mods and hey, in that lifestyle, people die."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It's business, and the movies are mostly about the cars and the mods and hey, in that lifestyle, people die.",
    "response": "We'll see, I guess ratings will drop if people agree with me more."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "We'll see, I guess ratings will drop if people agree with me more.",
    "response": "I'm still going to go see every one they make."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I'm still going to go see every one they make.",
    "response": "Are they making another one?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Are they making another one?",
    "response": "Talking about it or a spin off series."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who's your favorite character in the Fast & Furious?",
    "response": "Dom is my favorite. How about you?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Dom is my favorite. How about you?",
    "response": "Brian is my favorite. He has such pretty blue eyes."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Brian is my favorite. He has such pretty blue eyes.",
    "response": "Dom is strong and muscular, the type of bad boy I like in a man."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Dom is strong and muscular, the type of bad boy I like in a man.",
    "response": "Are you sad that the actor of Brian died in a tragic accident?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Are you sad that the actor of Brian died in a tragic accident?",
    "response": "Yes, it was very tragic. At least it wasn't my precious Dom."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, it was very tragic. At least it wasn't my precious Dom.",
    "response": "Did you like how they computer generated the scene with Brian in it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you like how they computer generated the scene with Brian in it?",
    "response": "It was awesome and looked so real. It had me in tears."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was awesome and looked so real. It had me in tears.",
    "response": "Same. He was like my husband. At least they ended the series well."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Same. He was like my husband. At least they ended the series well.",
    "response": "They actually have a new one that just came out. It's called the Fate of the Furious."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How awesome was it when the cars were dropped out of the plane in Furious7?",
    "response": "That was incredible, Rome was the best part though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That was incredible, Rome was the best part though.",
    "response": "Yeah when he was freaking out at the edge of the bay door telling them how he couldn't do it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah when he was freaking out at the edge of the bay door telling them how he couldn't do it.",
    "response": "Then Tej hits the button for his chute."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Then Tej hits the button for his chute.",
    "response": "It was great hearing him scream the whole way down."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was great hearing him scream the whole way down.",
    "response": "Then he ended up in that tree, I couldn't help but laugh."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Then he ended up in that tree, I couldn't help but laugh.",
    "response": "How cool would that be to do though?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How cool would that be to do though?",
    "response": "It would be so much fun, but I'd want to go out face first."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It would be so much fun, but I'd want to go out face first.",
    "response": "Why would you want to do that?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why would you want to do that?",
    "response": "Cause then I could floor it off the plane and it would force me into a barrel roll. I just think it'd be even more fun."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you like Fast & Furious 6?",
    "response": "Yeah I did mostly because The Rock was in it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah I did mostly because The Rock was in it.",
    "response": "Isn't his real name Dwayne Johnson?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Isn't his real name Dwayne Johnson?",
    "response": "Yes it is, he also used to wrestle in the WWE."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes it is, he also used to wrestle in the WWE.",
    "response": "Neat, do you remember the scene where they are having a cook out and The Rock walks up?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Neat, do you remember the scene where they are having a cook out and The Rock walks up?",
    "response": "Yes and Roman tells the girl she better hide her baby oil."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes and Roman tells the girl she better hide her baby oil.",
    "response": "Then The Rock said you better hide that big forehead."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Then The Rock said you better hide that big forehead.",
    "response": "That was a really funny part."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That was a really funny part.",
    "response": "Did you know that part was improvised?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you know that part was improvised?",
    "response": "No I didn't that's awesome."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you ever see the second Fast and the Furious short film?",
    "response": "You mean 2Fast2Furious?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You mean 2Fast2Furious?",
    "response": "No, there was a short called Los Bandoleros in 2009."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No, there was a short called Los Bandoleros in 2009.",
    "response": "Which movie did it come out closest to?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which movie did it come out closest to?",
    "response": "I believe Fast & Furious."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I believe Fast & Furious.",
    "response": "No I have not seen or even heard of that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No I have not seen or even heard of that.",
    "response": "It mainly featured Sung Kang and some Vin."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It mainly featured Sung Kang and some Vin.",
    "response": "I will check that out sometime."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I will check that out sometime.",
    "response": "You should, it was not bad at all."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You should, it was not bad at all.",
    "response": "I will, thanks for the recommendation."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Let us talk about the Fast and the Furious.",
    "response": "I never seen any."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I never seen any.",
    "response": "What?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What?",
    "response": "That is true."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That is true.",
    "response": "You know nothing about them?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You know nothing about them?",
    "response": "All I know is Vin Diesel is in it and it is an action film."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "All I know is Vin Diesel is in it and it is an action film.",
    "response": "Oh my goodness you have to watch them!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh my goodness you have to watch them!",
    "response": "Maybe I will some day."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Maybe I will some day.",
    "response": "We should watch the first one together."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "We should watch the first one together.",
    "response": "Sounds like a plan."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey.",
    "response": "Hi."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hi.",
    "response": "Do you have a favorite fast and furious movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you have a favorite fast and furious movie?",
    "response": "I like the first one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like the first one.",
    "response": "Oh really?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh really?",
    "response": "Yeah."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah.",
    "response": "Why is that?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why is that?",
    "response": "It reminds me of being in high school."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It reminds me of being in high school.",
    "response": "Oh is that how old you were when those came out?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh is that how old you were when those came out?",
    "response": "Yeah dating myself a bit, but I was."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What do you think of the first Fast and Furious movie?",
    "response": "I thought it was cool. I got really into cars after it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I thought it was cool. I got really into cars after it.",
    "response": "Me too. What was your favorite part?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too. What was your favorite part?",
    "response": "The first race scene where Paul Walker's car breaks on him."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The first race scene where Paul Walker's car breaks on him.",
    "response": "Yeah that was really cool."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah that was really cool.",
    "response": "I loved his car too. It looked really cool."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I loved his car too. It looked really cool.",
    "response": "Did you like Vin Diesel?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you like Vin Diesel?",
    "response": "Yes, he was really cool in this."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, he was really cool in this.",
    "response": "Was there anything you did not like?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Was there anything you did not like?",
    "response": "No, I thought the whole movie was cool."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you ever watch the Fast and Furious movies?",
    "response": "Only every year, or when I want to be surrounded by awesomeness."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Only every year, or when I want to be surrounded by awesomeness.",
    "response": "True, what do you think of Letty?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "True, what do you think of Letty?",
    "response": "You mean Michelle Rodriguez?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You mean Michelle Rodriguez?",
    "response": "Yes, I always wish she had more stunts in the movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, I always wish she had more stunts in the movies.",
    "response": "I know just what you mean, but that fit scene in the dress was epic."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know just what you mean, but that fit scene in the dress was epic.",
    "response": "Totally amazing, who played that girl though? Wasn't it some UFC chick or something?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Totally amazing, who played that girl though? Wasn't it some UFC chick or something?",
    "response": "It was Ronda Rousey man, you know, the Champion UFC chick."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was Ronda Rousey man, you know, the Champion UFC chick.",
    "response": "Whoa really, that just makes it even cooler."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Whoa really, that just makes it even cooler.",
    "response": "No what makes it cooler is I just got the full series on blue-ray, do you feel the need?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you see Fast and Furious 8, the Fate of the Furious?",
    "response": "Yes I did, and it was great.  Amazing."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes I did, and it was great.  Amazing.",
    "response": "That was good how Jason Statham got to be a good guy this time!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That was good how Jason Statham got to be a good guy this time!",
    "response": "Yes it was, and he named his baby after Brian, the Paul Walker character."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes it was, and he named his baby after Brian, the Paul Walker character.",
    "response": "Yeah, that was a nice touch."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, that was a nice touch.",
    "response": "I could tell he was going to do it when his ex-girlfriend told him she only named his middle name so Dom could give the first name."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I could tell he was going to do it when his ex-girlfriend told him she only named his middle name so Dom could give the first name.",
    "response": "I think I had an inkling too."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think I had an inkling too.",
    "response": "Then at the end they were having the barbecue and I knew what he was going to say...\"Brian!\""
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Then at the end they were having the barbecue and I knew what he was going to say...\"Brian!\"",
    "response": "Haha, yeah that was funny."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Haha, yeah that was funny.",
    "response": "He always brings that \"family\" thing into everything, that's what makes it a big hit in addition to all that action!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What was your favorite car in the fast and furious movies?",
    "response": "That's an easy one Dom's car at the end of the first movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's an easy one Dom's car at the end of the first movie.",
    "response": "Do you remember how fast it was?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you remember how fast it was?",
    "response": "It's under 10 seconds I think 9 seconds to be exact."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It's under 10 seconds I think 9 seconds to be exact.",
    "response": "Wasn't it a 1970 Dodge Charger?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Wasn't it a 1970 Dodge Charger?",
    "response": "Yes, I believe so."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, I believe so.",
    "response": "Why is that your favorite?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why is that your favorite?",
    "response": "I love the body style and it's black which is my favorite color."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I love the body style and it's black which is my favorite color.",
    "response": "Those are good reasons, do you like that the motor sticks out from the hood?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Those are good reasons, do you like that the motor sticks out from the hood?",
    "response": "I do it give sit character."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I could talk about my love for the Fast & Furious series all day.",
    "response": "I wish I could say the same."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I wish I could say the same.",
    "response": "You're not a fan?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You're not a fan?",
    "response": "Not too much. Action movies just aren't my type."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Not too much. Action movies just aren't my type.",
    "response": "Well, that's fine. There's more to it than just action."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, that's fine. There's more to it than just action.",
    "response": "Such as what?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Such as what?",
    "response": "There's plenty of drama in it, and there's also a bit of family-oriented stuff in there as well."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "There's plenty of drama in it, and there's also a bit of family-oriented stuff in there as well.",
    "response": "I don't know. The action seems to outweigh everything else."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I don't know. The action seems to outweigh everything else.",
    "response": "Oh, then I guess you won't really like the films much."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh, then I guess you won't really like the films much.",
    "response": "I thought about the same thing."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I haven't seen all of them.  I guess I should.",
    "response": "Well, It's hard to beat the original."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, It's hard to beat the original.",
    "response": "I agree.  I think they got a little carried away with all the sequels."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I agree.  I think they got a little carried away with all the sequels.",
    "response": "They did.  Some of them are good.  But I like the ones with Paul Walker and Vin Diesel the best."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They did.  Some of them are good.  But I like the ones with Paul Walker and Vin Diesel the best.",
    "response": "Yeah.  Aren't there like six or seven?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah.  Aren't there like six or seven?",
    "response": "Yep.  And they are planning more.  Without Paul Walker I just don't think they will be the same."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yep.  And they are planning more.  Without Paul Walker I just don't think they will be the same.",
    "response": "No, he just made the movies what they were."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No, he just made the movies what they were.",
    "response": "Vin Diesel can't be replaced either.  If you lose both of those characters, I really don't think you will have much of a fan base."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Vin Diesel can't be replaced either.  If you lose both of those characters, I really don't think you will have much of a fan base.",
    "response": "Hopefully he will be included in the new ones.  I'd love to see him have more of a presence."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hopefully he will be included in the new ones.  I'd love to see him have more of a presence.",
    "response": "Yeah, I might actually make an effort to watch them then."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I saw he Fast and the Furious: Tokyo Drift.",
    "response": "Was Vinny Diesel in it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Was Vinny Diesel in it?",
    "response": "Yes, but only in the end.  Paul Walker was not in it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, but only in the end.  Paul Walker was not in it.",
    "response": "Interesting.  Anybody else from number 1 and 2?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Interesting.  Anybody else from number 1 and 2?",
    "response": "No."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No.",
    "response": "Who directed it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who directed it?",
    "response": "Justin Lin."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Justin Lin.",
    "response": "Who played the main charaacter?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who played the main charaacter?",
    "response": "Lucas Black, with Natalie Kelley as his girlfriend."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Lucas Black, with Natalie Kelley as his girlfriend.",
    "response": "I saw her on CSI."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What's the most outrageous stunt featuring a car in the Fast & the Furious movies?",
    "response": "I would have to say when Paul Walker and Vin Diseal drove the supercar between the Etihad Towers in Abu Dhabi."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I would have to say when Paul Walker and Vin Diseal drove the supercar between the Etihad Towers in Abu Dhabi.",
    "response": "I was almost postivie you were going to say the bank vault scene!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I was almost postivie you were going to say the bank vault scene!",
    "response": "What Fast movie was that in? I get them all mixed up now since there are so many."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What Fast movie was that in? I get them all mixed up now since there are so many.",
    "response": "The bank vault chase was in Fast 5, released in 2011."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The bank vault chase was in Fast 5, released in 2011.",
    "response": "Didn't Brian and Dom drag that entire bank vault down the streets of Rio de Janeiro?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Didn't Brian and Dom drag that entire bank vault down the streets of Rio de Janeiro?",
    "response": "Yes that's the scene! I think the craziest car scene was in 2 Fast 2 Furious, the first race when Brain jumped over the draw bridge in his car."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes that's the scene! I think the craziest car scene was in 2 Fast 2 Furious, the first race when Brain jumped over the draw bridge in his car.",
    "response": "That scene still gives me chills when I watch it. The cinematography makes the viewer feel the adrenaline that the racers are feeling all the way up until the end."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That scene still gives me chills when I watch it. The cinematography makes the viewer feel the adrenaline that the racers are feeling all the way up until the end.",
    "response": "I think you can say that about any of the Fast & the Furious movies. Each film is adrenaline packed to the core."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think you can say that about any of the Fast & the Furious movies. Each film is adrenaline packed to the core.",
    "response": "Oh but what about that tank car chase in Fast & Furious 6? That was the most adrenaline packed scene in the entire series in my opinion."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you like dwane johnson?",
    "response": "Yes, sort of."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, sort of.",
    "response": "Have you seen fast and furious series?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen fast and furious series?",
    "response": "I am not sure if I have seen the whole series."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I am not sure if I have seen the whole series.",
    "response": "Okay, so have you seen the one in which dwayne jhonson is there?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Okay, so have you seen the one in which dwayne jhonson is there?",
    "response": "I think I have seen one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think I have seen one.",
    "response": "Did you like it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you like it?",
    "response": "Yes, it was good."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, it was good.",
    "response": "Do you think he used steroids for that role?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you think he used steroids for that role?",
    "response": "I think, I mean I don't thing you can achieve that kind of body naturally."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Lets talk about the fast and the furious",
    "response": "I love those movies"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I love those movies",
    "response": "Me too, i wish i had cars like that"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too, i wish i had cars like that",
    "response": "Same here"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Same here",
    "response": "Its wierd how brian oconnor started out a cop"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Its wierd how brian oconnor started out a cop",
    "response": "But then he was legit running from the cops"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "But then he was legit running from the cops",
    "response": "Yea he completely switched sides"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea he completely switched sides",
    "response": "It made it more interesting"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It made it more interesting",
    "response": "Yes it did"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes it did",
    "response": "Theyre great movies"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen furious 7?",
    "response": "Yes, I think so."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, I think so.",
    "response": "Do you remember the air plane scene?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you remember the air plane scene?",
    "response": "You mean the one where they drive the cars out of the plane?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You mean the one where they drive the cars out of the plane?",
    "response": "That's the one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's the one.",
    "response": "What about it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What about it?",
    "response": "Do you remember Roman Pierce being terrified?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you remember Roman Pierce being terrified?",
    "response": "I do that was hilarious."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I do that was hilarious.",
    "response": "That had to be my favorite part of the whole franchise."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That had to be my favorite part of the whole franchise.",
    "response": "Yeah that made me laugh for awhile."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen the Fast and Furious movies?",
    "response": "Yes, I've seen all of them except the 8th one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, I've seen all of them except the 8th one.",
    "response": "The one that's out in theaters now?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The one that's out in theaters now?",
    "response": "Right, I haven't seen that one yet."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Right, I haven't seen that one yet.",
    "response": "Which one -- of the ones you've seen -- is your favorite?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which one -- of the ones you've seen -- is your favorite?",
    "response": "I probably enjoyed the 1st one the most, but I liked them all. Some were better than others, though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I probably enjoyed the 1st one the most, but I liked them all. Some were better than others, though.",
    "response": "Which one did you like the least?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which one did you like the least?",
    "response": "I think the second one is probably my least favorite."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think the second one is probably my least favorite.",
    "response": "Yeah, I agree. I can't even really remember the second one very much."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, I agree. I can't even really remember the second one very much.",
    "response": "It's the one where Brian teams up with Roman Pearce as undercover cops. Vin Deisel and Michelle Rodriquez aren't in it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why did Han go to Tokyo?",
    "response": "He went after Gisele died, to clear his head and do street racing."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He went after Gisele died, to clear his head and do street racing.",
    "response": "It didn't say that in the movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It didn't say that in the movie.",
    "response": "I know, they aren't in order."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know, they aren't in order.",
    "response": "Why did Dom go to Tokyo then?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why did Dom go to Tokyo then?",
    "response": "He went to recover Han's body, after he was killed in the accident."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He went to recover Han's body, after he was killed in the accident.",
    "response": "Who was Sean, and why was he so important in this movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who was Sean, and why was he so important in this movie?",
    "response": "Han took an interest in Sean, and saw it as a way to beat the Yakuza at their own game."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Han took an interest in Sean, and saw it as a way to beat the Yakuza at their own game.",
    "response": "Who killed Han?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who killed Han?",
    "response": "Han was killed by Owen Shaw, Decker Shaw's \"big bad brother\"."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What do you think was the best set-piece of the whole Fast & Furious franchise?",
    "response": "They keep ramping up the action and topping themselves each movie.  I need a moment to think about this."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They keep ramping up the action and topping themselves each movie.  I need a moment to think about this.",
    "response": "I think mine was the scene in Fast 7 when the crew drives their cars out of the plane and parachute down."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think mine was the scene in Fast 7 when the crew drives their cars out of the plane and parachute down.",
    "response": "That was a pretty epic scene.  I read that a lot of the car sequences once they hit ground were practical effects, and not CGI."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That was a pretty epic scene.  I read that a lot of the car sequences once they hit ground were practical effects, and not CGI.",
    "response": "They actually threw a car out of a real plane too!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They actually threw a car out of a real plane too!",
    "response": "No way.  Really?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No way.  Really?",
    "response": "Yes.  There is a behind the scenes video where it is explained and shown."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes.  There is a behind the scenes video where it is explained and shown.",
    "response": "That gives me new appreciation for the series."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That gives me new appreciation for the series.",
    "response": "There were camera men jumping with the cars and everything.  I hope they continue to do this."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "There were camera men jumping with the cars and everything.  I hope they continue to do this.",
    "response": "I don't think there is any slowing down of this franchise in the near future."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What did you think of Fate of the Furious?",
    "response": "I thought it was alright, it was not going to be the same without Paul."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I thought it was alright, it was not going to be the same without Paul.",
    "response": "Yea, he was such a major part of the franchise."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, he was such a major part of the franchise.",
    "response": "It just feels off without him."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It just feels off without him.",
    "response": "The rest of the cast were pretty good though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The rest of the cast were pretty good though.",
    "response": "Yea, definitely.  Charlize Theron was great."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, definitely.  Charlize Theron was great.",
    "response": "I did also kind of miss Brewster though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I did also kind of miss Brewster though.",
    "response": "Yea, it seems strange that they wrote her out of the series."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, it seems strange that they wrote her out of the series.",
    "response": "I wonder if she wanted out or if the writers just felt it needed to be done."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I wonder if she wanted out or if the writers just felt it needed to be done.",
    "response": "I would guess she did not want to do any more."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I hope they make more Fast and Furious movies.",
    "response": "I'm not sure if they can."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I'm not sure if they can.",
    "response": "Why not?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why not?",
    "response": "They're already done a lot and Paul Walker won't be in them"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They're already done a lot and Paul Walker won't be in them",
    "response": "That is true."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That is true.",
    "response": "Paul Walker makes the franchise."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Paul Walker makes the franchise.",
    "response": "Maybe they can replace him?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Maybe they can replace him?",
    "response": "No way"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No way",
    "response": "Each movie is really good though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Each movie is really good though.",
    "response": "Yes. The only one I did not like was the second one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have. u seen the last fast and furious movie?",
    "response": "No i havent seen the last two"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No i havent seen the last two",
    "response": "Why not?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why not?",
    "response": "I havent been able to since paul walker died"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I havent been able to since paul walker died",
    "response": "Thats true i can see that"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Thats true i can see that",
    "response": "Its so sad and he was the movie"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Its so sad and he was the movie",
    "response": "Yea he kind of was"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea he kind of was",
    "response": "Dont get me wrong vin disel was too"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Dont get me wrong vin disel was too",
    "response": "But they were a great pair"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "But they were a great pair",
    "response": "Yes they were"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you think the Fast & Furious movie franchise should continue making movies?",
    "response": "No.  I definitely think this series is beyond played out and should cease immediately."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No.  I definitely think this series is beyond played out and should cease immediately.",
    "response": "Is there anything you enjoy about the Fast & Furious movies?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is there anything you enjoy about the Fast & Furious movies?",
    "response": "There were some elements of the very first movie that I did enjoy, yes.  Mostly the fact that it was new and somewhat exciting."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "There were some elements of the very first movie that I did enjoy, yes.  Mostly the fact that it was new and somewhat exciting.",
    "response": "What is it that you don't like about Fast & Furious?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is it that you don't like about Fast & Furious?",
    "response": "I really don't like the selection of actors.  Specifically, I'm annoyed by Michelle Rodriguez."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I really don't like the selection of actors.  Specifically, I'm annoyed by Michelle Rodriguez.",
    "response": "What about Vin Diesel?  Do you enjoy his acting in Fast & Furious?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What about Vin Diesel?  Do you enjoy his acting in Fast & Furious?",
    "response": "In Fast & Furious, no.  But, I do enjoy him in other movies like Saving Private Ryan."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "In Fast & Furious, no.  But, I do enjoy him in other movies like Saving Private Ryan.",
    "response": "Do you think there will be more Fast & Furious movies in the future?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you think there will be more Fast & Furious movies in the future?",
    "response": "Almost definitely, yes.  I think the fan base of this franchise has very low standards and probably wants more."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How do you feel about the series going up to 10 movies?",
    "response": "What are you talking about?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What are you talking about?",
    "response": "Oh, I'm sorry. The Fast & Furious series."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh, I'm sorry. The Fast & Furious series.",
    "response": "Oh, that one. I honestly think that's just silly."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh, that one. I honestly think that's just silly.",
    "response": "I thought the same. To think the tag line for Furious 7 was \"One last ride.\""
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I thought the same. To think the tag line for Furious 7 was \"One last ride.\"",
    "response": "Right? At this rate, there's going to be 3 extra last rides."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Right? At this rate, there's going to be 3 extra last rides.",
    "response": "For number 8, \"Just one more ride.\""
  },
  {
    "prompt": "For number 8, \"Just one more ride.\"",
    "response": "For number 9, \"Seriously, this is the last ride.\""
  },
  {
    "prompt": "For number 9, \"Seriously, this is the last ride.\"",
    "response": "For number 10, \"Someone please stop this last ride.\""
  },
  {
    "prompt": "For number 10, \"Someone please stop this last ride.\"",
    "response": "I haven't laughed this hard in years!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I just saw 2 Fast 2 Furious.",
    "response": "Was Vinnie Diesel in it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Was Vinnie Diesel in it?",
    "response": "No, he was doing xXx."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No, he was doing xXx.",
    "response": "Who directed?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who directed?",
    "response": "John Singleton."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "John Singleton.",
    "response": "Who was the hottie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who was the hottie?",
    "response": "The great Eva Mendes."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The great Eva Mendes.",
    "response": "What happens in the movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What happens in the movie?",
    "response": "Walker is a fugitive from the LAPD but works with the FBI to bring down a drug lord and clear himself."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Walker is a fugitive from the LAPD but works with the FBI to bring down a drug lord and clear himself.",
    "response": "Setting up for number three."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "If you could do one thing from Fast & Furious, what would it be?",
    "response": "Anything at all from any movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Anything at all from any movie?",
    "response": "Yes, anything, and it was completely legal."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, anything, and it was completely legal.",
    "response": "hmm... I guess I'd have to go with Driving the car between buildings."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "hmm... I guess I'd have to go with Driving the car between buildings.",
    "response": "You'd really want to drive a car out of a building and into another building?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You'd really want to drive a car out of a building and into another building?",
    "response": "No, in and out of three buildings."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No, in and out of three buildings.",
    "response": "That is just insane."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That is just insane.",
    "response": "That is the point. I think it would be awesome."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That is the point. I think it would be awesome.",
    "response": "It probably would be, but it'd be the last awesome thing you do."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It probably would be, but it'd be the last awesome thing you do.",
    "response": "Not if I jumped out at the last minute like Dom did."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen Fast & Furious 6?",
    "response": "Absolutely I loved it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Absolutely I loved it.",
    "response": "Do you recall the part where they're racing down the highway trying to save Letty?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you recall the part where they're racing down the highway trying to save Letty?",
    "response": "I don't recall that no can you rejog my memory."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I don't recall that no can you rejog my memory.",
    "response": "I can try, well there was a man I don't remember his name in a tank."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I can try, well there was a man I don't remember his name in a tank.",
    "response": "I do remember the tank that was crazy."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I do remember the tank that was crazy.",
    "response": "Yeah and they were trying to save letty."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah and they were trying to save letty.",
    "response": "I don't remember that part."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I don't remember that part.",
    "response": "Well Dom was on one side of the highway and they were on the other and Letty got thrown from the vehicle when Dom flew through the air and caught her smashing into a car."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well Dom was on one side of the highway and they were on the other and Letty got thrown from the vehicle when Dom flew through the air and caught her smashing into a car.",
    "response": "Oh yes now I remember."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I hate most things to do with racing",
    "response": "Why it is so boring to me to be honest"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why it is so boring to me to be honest",
    "response": "Then why do you seem to be into the fast and the furious so much"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Then why do you seem to be into the fast and the furious so much",
    "response": "Because Vin is awesome"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Because Vin is awesome",
    "response": "Well i guess i cannot disagree with that"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well i guess i cannot disagree with that",
    "response": "He is one of the more real actors out their"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He is one of the more real actors out their",
    "response": "What do you mean real"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What do you mean real",
    "response": "Like he is relatable and understandable"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Like he is relatable and understandable",
    "response": "Well yeah he is down to earth guy in interviews too"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well yeah he is down to earth guy in interviews too",
    "response": "He is really calm and hilarious"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen the second Fast and the Furious movie?",
    "response": "Which one is that?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which one is that?",
    "response": "It was called 2Fast2Furious."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was called 2Fast2Furious.",
    "response": "Is that the drifting one?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is that the drifting one?",
    "response": "No, that was Tokyo Drift, the third in the series."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No, that was Tokyo Drift, the third in the series.",
    "response": "I am not sure if I have seen the second one, what happens?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I am not sure if I have seen the second one, what happens?",
    "response": "It is where the FBI hires Brian to help take down a drug lord."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It is where the FBI hires Brian to help take down a drug lord.",
    "response": "That does not sound too familiar"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That does not sound too familiar",
    "response": "It was not the best one, quite forgettable."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was not the best one, quite forgettable.",
    "response": "Good thing I did not watch it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you enjoy the fast and the furious movies?",
    "response": "Yes they were very exciting!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes they were very exciting!",
    "response": "I am so sad though now that paul walker died."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I am so sad though now that paul walker died.",
    "response": "That is terrible! He was so handsome."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That is terrible! He was so handsome.",
    "response": "Vin diesel was good in the movies too."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Vin diesel was good in the movies too.",
    "response": "I should really watch them again just to see those to racing their cars really fast."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I should really watch them again just to see those to racing their cars really fast.",
    "response": "I agree, Tokyo drift was ok"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I agree, Tokyo drift was ok",
    "response": "All of the movies before that one were great!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "All of the movies before that one were great!",
    "response": "Really went downhill after paul walker"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Really went downhill after paul walker",
    "response": "Yep, he held everything together."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you remember Eva Mendes in Fast 5?",
    "response": "No I don't remember her being in that. Wasn't she only in 2 Fast 2 Furious?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No I don't remember her being in that. Wasn't she only in 2 Fast 2 Furious?",
    "response": "She was the lead actresses in 2 Fast 2 Furious but she made a post credit cameo in Fast 5."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "She was the lead actresses in 2 Fast 2 Furious but she made a post credit cameo in Fast 5.",
    "response": "Wow, I didn't realize that! What did she do?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Wow, I didn't realize that! What did she do?",
    "response": "She basically works for the Feds I think. She was handing the Rock some files."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "She basically works for the Feds I think. She was handing the Rock some files.",
    "response": "What were in the files? I need to watch Fast 5 again."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What were in the files? I need to watch Fast 5 again.",
    "response": "The files she handed over to the Rock post credit was a file on Letty. Remember she supposedly died in the 4th one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The files she handed over to the Rock post credit was a file on Letty. Remember she supposedly died in the 4th one.",
    "response": "That's really interesting! I didn't realize this scene existed. It kind of makes sense now that Michelle Rodriguez's Letty just appeared in Fast and Furious 6."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's really interesting! I didn't realize this scene existed. It kind of makes sense now that Michelle Rodriguez's Letty just appeared in Fast and Furious 6.",
    "response": "I know it's one of those Fast and Furious Easter eggs! I put it right next to that scene of Paul Walker driving to Miami, and Dom driving around Mexico."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know it's one of those Fast and Furious Easter eggs! I put it right next to that scene of Paul Walker driving to Miami, and Dom driving around Mexico.",
    "response": "I've watched those scenes! I need to go and catch that Eva Mendes scene!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "have you seen fas and furious seven?",
    "response": "yes, i have, it was very intense!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "yes, i have, it was very intense!",
    "response": "i cant believe dom went against his team!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "i cant believe dom went against his team!",
    "response": "don't forget. he had his son he needed to protect!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "don't forget. he had his son he needed to protect!",
    "response": "that is true, he wanted to protect his son."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "that is true, he wanted to protect his son.",
    "response": "letty was not happy though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "letty was not happy though.",
    "response": "yea, especially when that woman kissed him in fromt of her!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "yea, especially when that woman kissed him in fromt of her!",
    "response": "that made me so mad when she did that!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "that made me so mad when she did that!",
    "response": "me to, well i was glad when he saved his son."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "me to, well i was glad when he saved his son.",
    "response": "me too now letty and dom have a real family!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you watch all Fast and Furious movies?",
    "response": "No I only saw a few of them."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No I only saw a few of them.",
    "response": "Did you see the first one?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you see the first one?",
    "response": "Yes but it was a long time ago."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes but it was a long time ago.",
    "response": "It is worth watching again."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It is worth watching again.",
    "response": "I do remember it was good."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I do remember it was good.",
    "response": "Yes the car scenes were very well done."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes the car scenes were very well done.",
    "response": "Yes I could pay more attention to that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes I could pay more attention to that.",
    "response": "Yes the acting was excellent as well."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes the acting was excellent as well.",
    "response": "I do like the actors, thank you for the recomendation."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen all the fast and furious movies?",
    "response": "All but the last one"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "All but the last one",
    "response": "I havent seen it either."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I havent seen it either.",
    "response": "Ive been wondering what its like"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Ive been wondering what its like",
    "response": "Me too, its probably not the same without paul walker."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too, its probably not the same without paul walker.",
    "response": "I know i cant believe hes gone"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know i cant believe hes gone",
    "response": "Me either"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me either",
    "response": "He was so good in those movies"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He was so good in those movies",
    "response": "And really cute too"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "And really cute too",
    "response": "Yes and really cute"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you think The Fast and the Furious was very successful?",
    "response": "I assume it was, since they made tons of other ones."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I assume it was, since they made tons of other ones.",
    "response": "I guess so. Part 1 had the most heart."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I guess so. Part 1 had the most heart.",
    "response": "Every scene was unique and had good acting."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Every scene was unique and had good acting.",
    "response": "I liked the party scene. You could tell Paul Walker and Vin Diesel were gonna be good friends."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I liked the party scene. You could tell Paul Walker and Vin Diesel were gonna be good friends.",
    "response": "There were a lot of twists and turns in the film."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "There were a lot of twists and turns in the film.",
    "response": "I liked when it was revealed that Paul Walker was a cop."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I liked when it was revealed that Paul Walker was a cop.",
    "response": "I was not expecting that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I was not expecting that.",
    "response": "I agree. It was cool though how they kept it secret for awhile."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I agree. It was cool though how they kept it secret for awhile.",
    "response": "Yes. The story was full of surprises."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What do you think about the Fast and Furious movies?  Do you like them?",
    "response": "Yes I do.  I started watching the whole movies when Fast 5 came out."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes I do.  I started watching the whole movies when Fast 5 came out.",
    "response": "Really?  I remember I liked that one, but some people criticized it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Really?  I remember I liked that one, but some people criticized it.",
    "response": "Yeah, I loved that movie.  They drove the car off a cliff!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, I loved that movie.  They drove the car off a cliff!",
    "response": "That was amazing.  I liked that scene too."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That was amazing.  I liked that scene too.",
    "response": "And then there was the part at the end when they dragged the big safe through the city streets in Brazil."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "And then there was the part at the end when they dragged the big safe through the city streets in Brazil.",
    "response": "Yeah, I have a hart time understanding people who don't like that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, I have a hart time understanding people who don't like that.",
    "response": "Haha, me too!  It was amazing and I never understand people who don't like that!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Haha, me too!  It was amazing and I never understand people who don't like that!",
    "response": "Who did you watch it with?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who did you watch it with?",
    "response": "I watched it at the theater with a friend and his other friend, then recently I watched it with my mother."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I really miss Brian's character.",
    "response": "Me too.  Paul Walker was so great in his role."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too.  Paul Walker was so great in his role.",
    "response": "Did you notice that they tried to replace him in the latest Furious movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you notice that they tried to replace him in the latest Furious movie?",
    "response": "How so?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How so?",
    "response": "They introduced Scott Eastwood's character as another Brian.  A law man who goes rogue."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They introduced Scott Eastwood's character as another Brian.  A law man who goes rogue.",
    "response": "Now that you mention it, he even drove a similar blue car as Brian."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Now that you mention it, he even drove a similar blue car as Brian.",
    "response": "Exactly.  I understand why they would try to do it, but I don't think it was executed correctly."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Exactly.  I understand why they would try to do it, but I don't think it was executed correctly.",
    "response": "Indeed.  His character had a few lines but played no major role."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Indeed.  His character had a few lines but played no major role.",
    "response": "There was a period of maybe 20 minutes or so where he just wasn't on screen."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "There was a period of maybe 20 minutes or so where he just wasn't on screen.",
    "response": "Maybe they will better utilize his character in Fast 9."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you see Furious 7?",
    "response": "Is that the one where Paul Walker died during filming?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is that the one where Paul Walker died during filming?",
    "response": "Yes, and they used his real life brothers Cody and Caleb as stand-ins to finish the movie for him."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, and they used his real life brothers Cody and Caleb as stand-ins to finish the movie for him.",
    "response": "I didn't know that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I didn't know that.",
    "response": "Yeah, that way they could finish the movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, that way they could finish the movie.",
    "response": "So is O'Connor killed off as a character then?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "So is O'Connor killed off as a character then?",
    "response": "No they played it as he retired."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No they played it as he retired.",
    "response": "He was so important to the franchise as he is in all the movies"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He was so important to the franchise as he is in all the movies",
    "response": "Well he wasn't in Tokyo Drift or Los Bandoleros"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well he wasn't in Tokyo Drift or Los Bandoleros",
    "response": "Wow you know a lot about  Fast and Furious"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That Camaro was sweet too.",
    "response": "Yep, 1969 Yenko Camaro."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yep, 1969 Yenko Camaro.",
    "response": "427 cubic inches of solid american steel. 425 horses."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "427 cubic inches of solid american steel. 425 horses.",
    "response": "I think I prefer a 60s camaro over a mustang from the same time any day."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think I prefer a 60s camaro over a mustang from the same time any day.",
    "response": "Well they haven't used a Shelby in any of their movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well they haven't used a Shelby in any of their movies.",
    "response": "Oh Yeah Shelby GT is the best Mustang of them all."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh Yeah Shelby GT is the best Mustang of them all.",
    "response": "Shelby Cobra GT 500. That's the car that needs to be in the movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Shelby Cobra GT 500. That's the car that needs to be in the movie.",
    "response": "That will be so rad. 1969 Shelby GT 500. Now that is the quintessential American muscle car"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That will be so rad. 1969 Shelby GT 500. Now that is the quintessential American muscle car",
    "response": "That's an icon of its day. Big bad, and beautiful. 428 cubic inches of American power."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's an icon of its day. Big bad, and beautiful. 428 cubic inches of American power.",
    "response": "7 liters of gasoline burning inside that engine. That's a lot of power."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why are the Fast and Furious movies shown out of order?",
    "response": "I think because after #3 - Tokyo Drift - they did not think the franchise would come back."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think because after #3 - Tokyo Drift - they did not think the franchise would come back.",
    "response": "Why, because Vin Diesl was off staring in Triple X movies?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why, because Vin Diesl was off staring in Triple X movies?",
    "response": "Yes and because for the second movie, Paul Walker couldn't really carry it alone."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes and because for the second movie, Paul Walker couldn't really carry it alone.",
    "response": "Paul Walker wasn't in the Fast 8 movie was he?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Paul Walker wasn't in the Fast 8 movie was he?",
    "response": "No, he died during the filming of Fast and Furious 7 so they just did not include him or Jordanna Brewster, who plays Mia."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No, he died during the filming of Fast and Furious 7 so they just did not include him or Jordanna Brewster, who plays Mia.",
    "response": "Is Fast 8 just as good as the rest?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is Fast 8 just as good as the rest?",
    "response": "I think so, it has a good storyline, but I honestly think they should have stopped after Fast and Furious 7."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think so, it has a good storyline, but I honestly think they should have stopped after Fast and Furious 7.",
    "response": "Do you think they will go all the way to 10?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you think they will go all the way to 10?",
    "response": "Hard to say, but I think all the stars would definitely do it becaus the Fast and Furious franchise still makes a lot of money worldwide."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I saw The Fast and the Furious movie.  The first one.",
    "response": "Cool.  Who directed that?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Cool.  Who directed that?",
    "response": "Rob Cohen."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Rob Cohen.",
    "response": "Who plays the hot girlfriend?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who plays the hot girlfriend?",
    "response": "Michelle Rodriguez"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Michelle Rodriguez",
    "response": "She was great in Girlfight."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "She was great in Girlfight.",
    "response": "She was in Avatar, too."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "She was in Avatar, too.",
    "response": "Who is the cop's girlfriend?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who is the cop's girlfriend?",
    "response": "Jordana Brewster as Mia."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Jordana Brewster as Mia.",
    "response": "Wow, she's hot."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you like the fast and the furious?",
    "response": "Yes those are good movies"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes those are good movies",
    "response": "I cant believe paul walker is gone"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I cant believe paul walker is gone",
    "response": "I know its so sad"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know its so sad",
    "response": "Im still suprised they came out with another movie after he died"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Im still suprised they came out with another movie after he died",
    "response": "Me too"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too",
    "response": "It doesnt seem right"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It doesnt seem right",
    "response": "No it doesnt"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No it doesnt",
    "response": "Have you seen the last one?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen the last one?",
    "response": "No i haven't"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "WOuld you like to come over tonight and watch Fast & Furious: Tokyo Drift?",
    "response": "I'd love to as Tokyo Drift is my favorite of the series."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I'd love to as Tokyo Drift is my favorite of the series.",
    "response": "What is your favorite thing about F&F TD?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is your favorite thing about F&F TD?",
    "response": "I love the cars and how they are tricked out."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I love the cars and how they are tricked out.",
    "response": "My favorite part is the close up view of life in Tokyo."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "My favorite part is the close up view of life in Tokyo.",
    "response": "Though I do find it a bit of a stretch to view Lucas Black as a teenager considering he was 24 when he made the movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Though I do find it a bit of a stretch to view Lucas Black as a teenager considering he was 24 when he made the movie.",
    "response": "I know but his character was great and I enjoyed seeing him learn how to drift."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know but his character was great and I enjoyed seeing him learn how to drift.",
    "response": "The parking garage drift sequence was pretty impressive!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The parking garage drift sequence was pretty impressive!",
    "response": "It was especially how they drifted around the spiral ramps."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was especially how they drifted around the spiral ramps.",
    "response": "I look forward to coming over and I'll bring the popcorn!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I loved the backstory with Dom in the Fast and the Furious",
    "response": "Yeah, that thing with his dad was scary."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, that thing with his dad was scary.",
    "response": "Did you like the date scene?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you like the date scene?",
    "response": "Yeah, that explained the group and how they formed."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, that explained the group and how they formed.",
    "response": "I was really into that romance story with Paul Walker and Dom's sister."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I was really into that romance story with Paul Walker and Dom's sister.",
    "response": "Yeah, it was very cool."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, it was very cool.",
    "response": "I liked how he ordered the tuna everyday at her shop"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I liked how he ordered the tuna everyday at her shop",
    "response": "Yeah. That was funny"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah. That was funny",
    "response": "I knew they were gonna get together"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I knew they were gonna get together",
    "response": "Me too"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "So do you think they will keep having success on the Fast and Furious movies without Paul Walker?",
    "response": "I would say yes, they sitll have the Rock and Vin Diesel who are both headline actors"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I would say yes, they sitll have the Rock and Vin Diesel who are both headline actors",
    "response": "True but the whole series without Paul just doesn't seem right and its missing something dont you agree?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "True but the whole series without Paul just doesn't seem right and its missing something dont you agree?",
    "response": "I do agree but look at Tokyo Drift, noboby was in that one except for Lil Bow Wow and it did pretty good at the box office"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I do agree but look at Tokyo Drift, noboby was in that one except for Lil Bow Wow and it did pretty good at the box office",
    "response": "Yeah that one I don't even consider as part of the Fast series it should just be called Tokyo Drift and drop the Fast and Furious logo"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah that one I don't even consider as part of the Fast series it should just be called Tokyo Drift and drop the Fast and Furious logo",
    "response": "Did you know that a new Fast is being released sometime this year?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you know that a new Fast is being released sometime this year?",
    "response": "No I didn't but I guess i'll give it a chance and see if it's any good"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No I didn't but I guess i'll give it a chance and see if it's any good",
    "response": "Should be like I said they still have The Rock who is a great action actor"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Should be like I said they still have The Rock who is a great action actor",
    "response": "Yes I really liked him in Faster and The Scorpion King"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes I really liked him in Faster and The Scorpion King",
    "response": "Aw Man those movies were awful what bad examples of his better work."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What do you think about the Fast & Furious movies?",
    "response": "I think that they're basically superhero movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think that they're basically superhero movies.",
    "response": "How so?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How so?",
    "response": "Well, they're all basically indestructible.  No matter how many car crashes or other accidents, they always leave unscathed."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, they're all basically indestructible.  No matter how many car crashes or other accidents, they always leave unscathed.",
    "response": "That's a good point.  Pretty much no one in the core group, besides Han, died."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's a good point.  Pretty much no one in the core group, besides Han, died.",
    "response": "Remember that scene in 'Fast Five' where Dom and Brian drive off a bridge and survive?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Remember that scene in 'Fast Five' where Dom and Brian drive off a bridge and survive?",
    "response": "Yea, that was pretty ridiculous.  Or the scene in the 7th where they drive through 3 buildings."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, that was pretty ridiculous.  Or the scene in the 7th where they drive through 3 buildings.",
    "response": "I'm pretty sure the laws of physics don't apply to any of these characters."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I'm pretty sure the laws of physics don't apply to any of these characters.",
    "response": "Also, now I'm reminded of the fact that The Rock's character gets shot by rubber bullets in the latest movie, and just shrugs it off."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Also, now I'm reminded of the fact that The Rock's character gets shot by rubber bullets in the latest movie, and just shrugs it off.",
    "response": "Like I said, they're superheroes!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you want to know what I don't understand about Fast and the Furious?",
    "response": "What's that?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What's that?",
    "response": "Why is it that after eight movies, and showcasing classic, American and import cars, I've never seen a Jeep Wrangler featured."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why is it that after eight movies, and showcasing classic, American and import cars, I've never seen a Jeep Wrangler featured.",
    "response": "You probably haven't seen one because because Jeeps are notoriously slow. The movie is called Fast and The Furious not Slow and the Curious."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You probably haven't seen one because because Jeeps are notoriously slow. The movie is called Fast and The Furious not Slow and the Curious.",
    "response": "You're probably right. However, I can definitely Hobbs or Shaw sporting one!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You're probably right. However, I can definitely Hobbs or Shaw sporting one!",
    "response": "Yeah! Especially in the latest movie, Fast and Furious 8!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah! Especially in the latest movie, Fast and Furious 8!",
    "response": "What happened in that one?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What happened in that one?",
    "response": "Well, as the team was trying to stop the hacker in Russia from stealing a submarine with bombs, they were caught by the Russian military. There was snow everywhere."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, as the team was trying to stop the hacker in Russia from stealing a submarine with bombs, they were caught by the Russian military. There was snow everywhere.",
    "response": "Oh really? That would've been perfect for a Jeep!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh really? That would've been perfect for a Jeep!",
    "response": "Well maybe they will in the next one, Fast and the Furious 9!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What's your favorite Fast & Furious car?",
    "response": "The Nissan Skyline GTR R34, hands down the best car in the movie. You?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The Nissan Skyline GTR R34, hands down the best car in the movie. You?",
    "response": "The 350Z in Tokyo Drift."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The 350Z in Tokyo Drift.",
    "response": "Is Tokyo Drift your favorite Fast & Furious movie, if not which one?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is Tokyo Drift your favorite Fast & Furious movie, if not which one?",
    "response": "Yes, Tokyo Drift is my favorite movie in that series. How about you?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, Tokyo Drift is my favorite movie in that series. How about you?",
    "response": "I like the second movie, that's where they showed the silver R34."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like the second movie, that's where they showed the silver R34.",
    "response": "Have you watched the newest Fast & Furious movie yet?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you watched the newest Fast & Furious movie yet?",
    "response": "No, what is the movie called?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No, what is the movie called?",
    "response": "The Fate and the Furious, it's a must watch!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The Fate and the Furious, it's a must watch!",
    "response": "Oh wow, I will definitely check it out."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh man, you know the Fast and The Furious movie?",
    "response": "THE movie? More like which one of dozens, am I right?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "THE movie? More like which one of dozens, am I right?",
    "response": "Haha yeah, how many do they have?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Haha yeah, how many do they have?",
    "response": "I think eight by now"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think eight by now",
    "response": "Oh yeah! That recent one came out right?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh yeah! That recent one came out right?",
    "response": "Yeah, what was the name of it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, what was the name of it?",
    "response": "The Fate of the Furious"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The Fate of the Furious",
    "response": "Did you already see it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you already see it?",
    "response": "Yeah, last month."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, last month.",
    "response": "Nice, I only saw up to Furious 7"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I didn't really care for the fast and the furious franchise.",
    "response": "Really?  Why?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Really?  Why?",
    "response": "Well, it's a bunch of racers.  How entertaining can that really be?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, it's a bunch of racers.  How entertaining can that really be?",
    "response": "Don't you watch the Indy 500?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Don't you watch the Indy 500?",
    "response": "No way!! It's all just rednecks and left hand turns."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No way!! It's all just rednecks and left hand turns.",
    "response": "But it can be exciting, especially when there is a wreck"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "But it can be exciting, especially when there is a wreck",
    "response": "Yes but why would you want to watch a car accident?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes but why would you want to watch a car accident?",
    "response": "Well, there is definitely more to fast and furious than left hand turns and car accidents."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, there is definitely more to fast and furious than left hand turns and car accidents.",
    "response": "I suppose, but I still don't like the idea of a racing movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I suppose, but I still don't like the idea of a racing movie.",
    "response": "To each their own i guess."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey, you gonna see the new Fast and Furious movie?",
    "response": "What number is this again? Seveteen? Fifty-six?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What number is this again? Seveteen? Fifty-six?",
    "response": "Seven, I think."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Seven, I think.",
    "response": "Ha! You're a fan and you don't even know."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Ha! You're a fan and you don't even know.",
    "response": "I don't care what number it is. They're good movies. Except for maybe Tokyo Drift."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I don't care what number it is. They're good movies. Except for maybe Tokyo Drift.",
    "response": "I'm surprised you even wanna see this new movie. That Paul guy isn't in it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I'm surprised you even wanna see this new movie. That Paul guy isn't in it.",
    "response": "Hey! It's getting really good reviews. I'll give it a chance. So you wanna go with me?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey! It's getting really good reviews. I'll give it a chance. So you wanna go with me?",
    "response": "uh.. I\"ll think about it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "uh.. I\"ll think about it.",
    "response": "I have this feeling that if you see this one, you'll become a fan. Have you seen any of them?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I have this feeling that if you see this one, you'll become a fan. Have you seen any of them?",
    "response": "I saw the first one. It was okay."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey man what was your favorite Fast & Furious and why?",
    "response": "I'd have to say it was Fast 5."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I'd have to say it was Fast 5.",
    "response": "Really? How come?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Really? How come?",
    "response": "I liked the introduction of Dwayne Johnson's character. It really felt like he was a threat to the group."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I liked the introduction of Dwayne Johnson's character. It really felt like he was a threat to the group.",
    "response": "Yeah his character was pretty aweosme. He did a great job on it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah his character was pretty aweosme. He did a great job on it.",
    "response": "In addition to that I really liked they way they paid respects to Paul Walker and his character. It was a real tear jerker in the theaters."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "In addition to that I really liked they way they paid respects to Paul Walker and his character. It was a real tear jerker in the theaters.",
    "response": "Yeah. I agree. It wasn't my favorite of the series but I'd be lying if I said it wasn't good."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah. I agree. It wasn't my favorite of the series but I'd be lying if I said it wasn't good.",
    "response": "What was your favorite?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What was your favorite?",
    "response": "I'd say Fast 7 was mine because of Jason Statham's character."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I'd say Fast 7 was mine because of Jason Statham's character.",
    "response": "Nice choice."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen Fate of the Furious yet?",
    "response": "I am planning on going to watch it this weekend with my family."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I am planning on going to watch it this weekend with my family.",
    "response": "I won't spoil anything, but I think you're in for a pleasant surprise."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I won't spoil anything, but I think you're in for a pleasant surprise.",
    "response": "I take it that means that you liked it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I take it that means that you liked it.",
    "response": "I liked it a lot."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I liked it a lot.",
    "response": "Alright, well I'll go in with good expectations."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Alright, well I'll go in with good expectations.",
    "response": "If you liked the last 3, you'll definitely love this one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "If you liked the last 3, you'll definitely love this one.",
    "response": "That just got me excited."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That just got me excited.",
    "response": "Which of the last 3 was your favorite?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which of the last 3 was your favorite?",
    "response": "Fast Five without a doubt."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you know how to drift a car?",
    "response": "Are you asking for a friend?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Are you asking for a friend?",
    "response": "Well, I mean, I saw this new fast and the furious movie and now I want to try it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, I mean, I saw this new fast and the furious movie and now I want to try it.",
    "response": "You are going to wreck yourself."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You are going to wreck yourself.",
    "response": "But vin diesel makes it look so easy!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "But vin diesel makes it look so easy!",
    "response": "Movies aren't reality man, let it go."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Movies aren't reality man, let it go.",
    "response": "How hard can it be?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How hard can it be?",
    "response": "Is this really the person you want to be, copying movies?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is this really the person you want to be, copying movies?",
    "response": "Cars are cool."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Cars are cool.",
    "response": "You need help."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The Fast & Furious movies have had some great soundtracks over the years.",
    "response": "They have! Do you have a favorite?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They have! Do you have a favorite?",
    "response": "That'd probably be Fast & Furious 6."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That'd probably be Fast & Furious 6.",
    "response": "That film's main theme was so great."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That film's main theme was so great.",
    "response": "Yes! Whoever calls for these soundtracks really know how to appeal to big audiences.."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes! Whoever calls for these soundtracks really know how to appeal to big audiences..",
    "response": "My entire family was hooked onto that song after we went to see the film."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "My entire family was hooked onto that song after we went to see the film.",
    "response": "Fate of the Furious also has a fantastic soundtrack."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Fate of the Furious also has a fantastic soundtrack.",
    "response": "That one's a classic for rap fans, mainly."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That one's a classic for rap fans, mainly.",
    "response": "Exactly why I like it. I'm a rap fan!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Exactly why I like it. I'm a rap fan!",
    "response": "So am I!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you see the first Fast and the Furious movie?",
    "response": "Yes. It is such a good movie!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes. It is such a good movie!",
    "response": "I think I saw it eight times."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think I saw it eight times.",
    "response": "I probably saw it 12 times!  I love Paul Walker"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I probably saw it 12 times!  I love Paul Walker",
    "response": "Me too!  But I think I like Vin Diesel better."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too!  But I think I like Vin Diesel better.",
    "response": "He is in great shape!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He is in great shape!",
    "response": "When I listen to the sound track, I automatically drive faster."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When I listen to the sound track, I automatically drive faster.",
    "response": "Now I want to go watch the movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Now I want to go watch the movie.",
    "response": "I have the DVD!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I have the DVD!",
    "response": "Oh, let's go watch it now!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What do you think of the latest Fast & Furious film?",
    "response": "It's ok but it's getting a little ridiculous now."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It's ok but it's getting a little ridiculous now.",
    "response": "What do you mean?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What do you mean?",
    "response": "They keep going more over the top with the action."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They keep going more over the top with the action.",
    "response": "Oh, it's getting too unrealistic?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh, it's getting too unrealistic?",
    "response": "Basically, yes, but it's getting too far away from its roots."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Basically, yes, but it's getting too far away from its roots.",
    "response": "You mean the car racing stuff?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You mean the car racing stuff?",
    "response": "Yes, they went away from car racing and focus on heists more now."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, they went away from car racing and focus on heists more now.",
    "response": "Yeah, I liked the first film the best because it was just simple and fun."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, I liked the first film the best because it was just simple and fun.",
    "response": "Agreed, it used to be about fast, cool cars instead of all this other stuff."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you watch The Fate of the Furious?",
    "response": "Yea I did. I was really hoping there would be more racing."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea I did. I was really hoping there would be more racing.",
    "response": "Yea me too, they had some cool cars though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea me too, they had some cool cars though.",
    "response": "Yea but they didn't focus on the cars at all."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea but they didn't focus on the cars at all.",
    "response": "True, but I still really enjoyed the plot"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "True, but I still really enjoyed the plot",
    "response": "Really? The plot was terrible! There were so many holes in it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Really? The plot was terrible! There were so many holes in it.",
    "response": "Yea but the movie is supposed to be silly and over the top. You're being too critical."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea but the movie is supposed to be silly and over the top. You're being too critical.",
    "response": "Maybe you're right. It did have some cool fight scenes."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Maybe you're right. It did have some cool fight scenes.",
    "response": "Yea, I would have loved to see The Rock and Jason Stathum finish that prison fight though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, I would have loved to see The Rock and Jason Stathum finish that prison fight though.",
    "response": "Yea, me too! They stopped it too early."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The fast & Furious Franchise lost a great friend when Paul Walker died.",
    "response": "Man don't even say that to me, I always cry."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Man don't even say that to me, I always cry.",
    "response": "I remember the first day we met Brian Spilner, sitting in the dinner asking for a tuna fish sandwich."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I remember the first day we met Brian Spilner, sitting in the dinner asking for a tuna fish sandwich.",
    "response": "Spilner/ Don't you mean O'conor."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Spilner/ Don't you mean O'conor.",
    "response": "No, I mean Spilner; that was his undercover alias when he was after Dom in the first film."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No, I mean Spilner; that was his undercover alias when he was after Dom in the first film.",
    "response": "How exactly do you remember that?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How exactly do you remember that?",
    "response": "How do you not, when Dom took his ID and said \"Brian Spilner? That sounds like a serial killer's name.\""
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How do you not, when Dom took his ID and said \"Brian Spilner? That sounds like a serial killer's name.\"",
    "response": "Oh yeah, ok, now I remember. Dude how many times did you watch that movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh yeah, ok, now I remember. Dude how many times did you watch that movie?",
    "response": "30, why is that a lot?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "30, why is that a lot?",
    "response": "Yes, that is way too many, but do you wanna make it 31 because now I want to watch it again."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Today I am going to watch fast & furious movie.",
    "response": "Oh very good. All fast & furious movies are my favorite."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh very good. All fast & furious movies are my favorite.",
    "response": "Many times I have seen all the fast & furious movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Many times I have seen all the fast & furious movies.",
    "response": "Which fast & furious movie you are going to watch today?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which fast & furious movie you are going to watch today?",
    "response": "Fast & furious 7. This is the 5th time I am going to watch."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Fast & furious 7. This is the 5th time I am going to watch.",
    "response": "In that movie, all the actors have done their job very well."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "In that movie, all the actors have done their job very well.",
    "response": "Exactly. When I was watching that movie I was too serious."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Exactly. When I was watching that movie I was too serious.",
    "response": "Which character do you like the most?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which character do you like the most?",
    "response": "Letty the girl, who is more beautiful in this movie and acted very well."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Letty the girl, who is more beautiful in this movie and acted very well.",
    "response": "Overall the movie is just awesome."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Lets talk about the fast and the furious movies",
    "response": "That sounds good"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That sounds good",
    "response": "I love those movies"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I love those movies",
    "response": "Me too"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too",
    "response": "Theres so much drama and action and adventure"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Theres so much drama and action and adventure",
    "response": "They really do have it all"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They really do have it all",
    "response": "Its so sad they probably arent going to make anymore"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Its so sad they probably arent going to make anymore",
    "response": "I know"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know",
    "response": "They were the best"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They were the best",
    "response": "Yes there were"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey.",
    "response": "Hi."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hi.",
    "response": "Do you like Fast and the Furious?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you like Fast and the Furious?",
    "response": "Yeah I like some of them."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah I like some of them.",
    "response": "Which ones?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which ones?",
    "response": "I like the 4th and 5th movies the best."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like the 4th and 5th movies the best.",
    "response": "Which one is the one where they are in Brazil?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which one is the one where they are in Brazil?",
    "response": "That is 5."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That is 5.",
    "response": "I like that one quite a bit."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like that one quite a bit.",
    "response": "Yeah definitely."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you ever seen any of the Fast & Furious movies?",
    "response": "Yeah, they are awesome action films. I love Vin Diesel."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, they are awesome action films. I love Vin Diesel.",
    "response": "And I really admire how they do their car stunts live, they don't just lay back and do the whole thing with CGI."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "And I really admire how they do their car stunts live, they don't just lay back and do the whole thing with CGI.",
    "response": "It takes a lot of effort to do movies the old fashioned way, with special effects and stunts on the set. Props to them for that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It takes a lot of effort to do movies the old fashioned way, with special effects and stunts on the set. Props to them for that.",
    "response": "Yes, I saw an interview with the cast, and they were really proud of what they achieved on set."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, I saw an interview with the cast, and they were really proud of what they achieved on set.",
    "response": "I didn't know how they were going to handle Paul Walker's death, may he rest in peace."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I didn't know how they were going to handle Paul Walker's death, may he rest in peace.",
    "response": "Yeah, as I watched that last film he was in, I kept waiting for the character to get killed off."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, as I watched that last film he was in, I kept waiting for the character to get killed off.",
    "response": "I absolutely loved that they fashioned a happy ending for him, and he didn't die, he just kind of rode off into the sunset with his family."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I absolutely loved that they fashioned a happy ending for him, and he didn't die, he just kind of rode off into the sunset with his family.",
    "response": "I agree, that was the best possible ending for that character, and a terrific sendoff for Paul Walker."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I agree, that was the best possible ending for that character, and a terrific sendoff for Paul Walker.",
    "response": "I didn't expect it, and it is one of my favorite endings of any film. It gave me chills."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I saw Fast and Furious Six last night.",
    "response": "Who directed it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who directed it?",
    "response": "Justin Lin, again."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Justin Lin, again.",
    "response": "Same old crew?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Same old crew?",
    "response": "Yes, Vinny Diesel, Paul Walker, Dwayne Johnson."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, Vinny Diesel, Paul Walker, Dwayne Johnson.",
    "response": "What happens in the movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What happens in the movie?",
    "response": "Johnson persuades Diesel and Walker to go after a bad guy in exchange for amnesty."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Johnson persuades Diesel and Walker to go after a bad guy in exchange for amnesty.",
    "response": "Same old.  I hear Letty turns up."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Same old.  I hear Letty turns up.",
    "response": "Yes, they get back together."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, they get back together.",
    "response": "Very convenient."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How many movies are in the Fast series anyway?",
    "response": "They started in 2001, and had 7 sequels since, not counting the shorts."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They started in 2001, and had 7 sequels since, not counting the shorts.",
    "response": "They made short films too?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They made short films too?",
    "response": "Yep. They were just filler type of shorts. Not that good."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yep. They were just filler type of shorts. Not that good.",
    "response": "These movies made over 5 billion buvks"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "These movies made over 5 billion buvks",
    "response": "Yep., It's the 6th highest grossing film franchise of ALL time."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yep., It's the 6th highest grossing film franchise of ALL time.",
    "response": "That's right behind the Tolkien's series."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's right behind the Tolkien's series.",
    "response": "Yep. people do love nice cars and stealing stuff"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yep. people do love nice cars and stealing stuff",
    "response": "Good ol' family fun"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Good ol' family fun",
    "response": "Nothing says friedns like stealing stuff together in nice cars, all modded up."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "which fast and furious movie was your favorite?",
    "response": "hmm, thats a really hard choice."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "hmm, thats a really hard choice.",
    "response": "come on tell me already!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "come on tell me already!",
    "response": "all the ones with dom?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "all the ones with dom?",
    "response": "oh wow, you love him that much?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "oh wow, you love him that much?",
    "response": "he is a great character and leads his team well!."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "he is a great character and leads his team well!.",
    "response": "i agree"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "i agree",
    "response": "he also takes really good care of letty."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "he also takes really good care of letty.",
    "response": "well they are lovers!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "well they are lovers!",
    "response": "they make a great couple."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey what do you think about the Fast and the Furious movies? Do you like them?",
    "response": "Yes I do! I LOVE them!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes I do! I LOVE them!",
    "response": "Do you have any particular ones you love? And Why?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you have any particular ones you love? And Why?",
    "response": "I love the Tokyo drift one! It actually has a different setting. I won't say exotic, but seeing them drifting and whatnot on Tokyo streets is very interesting."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I love the Tokyo drift one! It actually has a different setting. I won't say exotic, but seeing them drifting and whatnot on Tokyo streets is very interesting.",
    "response": "I personally do not like it. The plot is kind of weak."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I personally do not like it. The plot is kind of weak.",
    "response": "Well okay, which one do you like the most then?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well okay, which one do you like the most then?",
    "response": "I love Furious 7! Paul Walker was partially still in it!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I love Furious 7! Paul Walker was partially still in it!",
    "response": "Why do you like it better than the others?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why do you like it better than the others?",
    "response": "Call me bias, I think it is because it is the last movie Paul Walker was in prior to his accident."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Call me bias, I think it is because it is the last movie Paul Walker was in prior to his accident.",
    "response": "I understand. He was a good actor."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What's your favorite scene in all of the Fast & Furious movies?",
    "response": "I would say, it was when they went under the 18 wheeler. That started it all. You?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I would say, it was when they went under the 18 wheeler. That started it all. You?",
    "response": "The bridge jump was the best! It got my adrenaline going."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The bridge jump was the best! It got my adrenaline going.",
    "response": "Which car do you think was better, the Skyline or the 1970 Dodge Charger?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which car do you think was better, the Skyline or the 1970 Dodge Charger?",
    "response": "Obviously, I would choose the Skyline. But that Dodge Charger is a classic."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Obviously, I would choose the Skyline. But that Dodge Charger is a classic.",
    "response": "I think the Dodge Charger beats them all. It's a lot of American muscle."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think the Dodge Charger beats them all. It's a lot of American muscle.",
    "response": "I feel like Japanese cars are better built, and last much longer."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I feel like Japanese cars are better built, and last much longer.",
    "response": "If you take care of the Dodge Charger, it can last just as long."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "If you take care of the Dodge Charger, it can last just as long.",
    "response": "What's the best stunt in the movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What's the best stunt in the movie?",
    "response": "I would say the Abu Dhabi Car Jump was awesome."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you think Owen and Deckard Shaw will return for the next Fast and Furious?",
    "response": "You mean Luke Evans and Jason Statham's characters?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You mean Luke Evans and Jason Statham's characters?",
    "response": "Yeah I hope those two will return. It's odd that in The Fate of the Furious they became good after all the turmoil from the Furious 7 and the one before."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah I hope those two will return. It's odd that in The Fate of the Furious they became good after all the turmoil from the Furious 7 and the one before.",
    "response": "I think they will return. I really liked what they did with Jason Statham's character."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think they will return. I really liked what they did with Jason Statham's character.",
    "response": "Me too! I liked that they gave him more action sequences. That whole scene on the plane with the baby was great in Fate of the Furious!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too! I liked that they gave him more action sequences. That whole scene on the plane with the baby was great in Fate of the Furious!",
    "response": "That scene was hilariously over the top but I loved it!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That scene was hilariously over the top but I loved it!",
    "response": "He was even at the lunch at Dom's house at the end!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He was even at the lunch at Dom's house at the end!",
    "response": "That was a little weird. I get that he helped them because they helped him and his brother but that scene at the end with all of them so happy was a bit off."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That was a little weird. I get that he helped them because they helped him and his brother but that scene at the end with all of them so happy was a bit off.",
    "response": "I think you have to understand it goes back to Dom's loyalty to family and Deckard showing he holds the same value. So they found a common point between them."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think you have to understand it goes back to Dom's loyalty to family and Deckard showing he holds the same value. So they found a common point between them.",
    "response": "You're right. I didn't think about that. I think We'll have Deckard returning as part of the crew from here on out."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "you wanna know something",
    "response": "Sure tell me"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Sure tell me",
    "response": "Well i think the lead actor is not that good"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well i think the lead actor is not that good",
    "response": "The lead actor in what"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The lead actor in what",
    "response": "The guy who stars in the fast and the furious"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The guy who stars in the fast and the furious",
    "response": "Vin diesal?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Vin diesal?",
    "response": "Yeah he is not that good"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah he is not that good",
    "response": "I do not know i love him"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I do not know i love him",
    "response": "He just seems out of place"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He just seems out of place",
    "response": "How is he out of place he is perfect"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you think that the 'Fast & Furious' movies objectify women?",
    "response": "Now that's an interesting question.  I would definitely say yes, but I have mixed feelings."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Now that's an interesting question.  I would definitely say yes, but I have mixed feelings.",
    "response": "Can you elaborate?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Can you elaborate?",
    "response": "On one hand, this franchise has so much gratuitous and random shots of scantily clad females."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "On one hand, this franchise has so much gratuitous and random shots of scantily clad females.",
    "response": "That's almost a cornerstone at this point."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's almost a cornerstone at this point.",
    "response": "But on the other hand, women should do whatever they feel is empowering to them.  Also, the coolest characters are female in the series."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "But on the other hand, women should do whatever they feel is empowering to them.  Also, the coolest characters are female in the series.",
    "response": "Letty is definitely the coolest and toughest of that whole crew next to Dom."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Letty is definitely the coolest and toughest of that whole crew next to Dom.",
    "response": "Those two characters are perfect for each other."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Those two characters are perfect for each other.",
    "response": "Gisele, portrayed by Gal Gadot, I thought was also pretty empowering as a character."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Gisele, portrayed by Gal Gadot, I thought was also pretty empowering as a character.",
    "response": "Don't forget the woman who played the police officer from Brazil.  She was a strong female character too."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hi, I heard that the new Fast & Furious movie reached 1 billion worldwide box office.",
    "response": "That is a big achievement, although I do not like the movie very much."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That is a big achievement, although I do not like the movie very much.",
    "response": "Yeah, the domestic box office of the movie is not that great, but it tops in other countries such as China, with more than 300 millions."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, the domestic box office of the movie is not that great, but it tops in other countries such as China, with more than 300 millions.",
    "response": "With such a high box office, I wish they could really think about how to make the movie fun and entertaining."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "With such a high box office, I wish they could really think about how to make the movie fun and entertaining.",
    "response": "There have been so many movies in the series. Maybe they need to think about other storylines."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "There have been so many movies in the series. Maybe they need to think about other storylines.",
    "response": "I agree. I heard that they are thinking about using other characters for the next movie in the franchise."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I agree. I heard that they are thinking about using other characters for the next movie in the franchise.",
    "response": "Dwayne Johnson's character, Hobbs."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Dwayne Johnson's character, Hobbs.",
    "response": "That seems to be interesting. I like the actor very much."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That seems to be interesting. I like the actor very much.",
    "response": "They may also put Jason Statham's character Deckard Shaw into the movie as well."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They may also put Jason Statham's character Deckard Shaw into the movie as well.",
    "response": "Great. I should wait to see the next Fast & Furious movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "My favorite Fast and Furious movie has to be number 6.",
    "response": "That one is my least favorite."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That one is my least favorite.",
    "response": "Really? It's one of the better ones in my opinion."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Really? It's one of the better ones in my opinion.",
    "response": "There's a slightly personal reason as to why I don't like it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "There's a slightly personal reason as to why I don't like it.",
    "response": "Go on."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Go on.",
    "response": "I saw less than half of it when my family went to watch it in the theaters."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I saw less than half of it when my family went to watch it in the theaters.",
    "response": "Why so little?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why so little?",
    "response": "Because I ate something beforehand that upset my stomach badly."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Because I ate something beforehand that upset my stomach badly.",
    "response": "So you spent more than half of the movie in the bathroom?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "So you spent more than half of the movie in the bathroom?",
    "response": "Unfortunately, that's how it went."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey there.",
    "response": "Hi."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hi.",
    "response": "What was the last fast and furious movie that you saw?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What was the last fast and furious movie that you saw?",
    "response": "Tokyo Drift was on tv there other day."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Tokyo Drift was on tv there other day.",
    "response": "Is  that the third one?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is  that the third one?",
    "response": "Yeah that's right."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah that's right.",
    "response": "Do you like that one?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you like that one?",
    "response": "Not a lot, but it just happened to be on tv."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Not a lot, but it just happened to be on tv.",
    "response": "Yeah I don't really like that one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah I don't really like that one.",
    "response": "It's kind of whatever."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "have you watched fate of the furious?",
    "response": "yes and i think it is an  awesome movie.."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "yes and i think it is an  awesome movie..",
    "response": "couldn't agree more but there is one thing i don't like about it"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "couldn't agree more but there is one thing i don't like about it",
    "response": "what?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "what?",
    "response": "the way the preview tell you everything about the  movie"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "the way the preview tell you everything about the  movie",
    "response": "IKR??"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "IKR??",
    "response": "yeah man,there is nothing to anticipate for in the movie"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "yeah man,there is nothing to anticipate for in the movie",
    "response": "so which one do you think is the best of them?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "so which one do you think is the best of them?",
    "response": "still think the third one was"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "still think the third one was",
    "response": "i still stick to the second one"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you remember the first time you saw The Fast and The Furious?",
    "response": "Yes, I was 14."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, I was 14.",
    "response": "What did you think of it when you were 14?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What did you think of it when you were 14?",
    "response": "I loved it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I loved it.",
    "response": "What did you love about it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What did you love about it?",
    "response": "I loved the characters, and the hot guys."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I loved the characters, and the hot guys.",
    "response": "What about the cars?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What about the cars?",
    "response": "I loved the cars too."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I loved the cars too.",
    "response": "But not as much as Dominic?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "But not as much as Dominic?",
    "response": "Of course not!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you see the Fast and Furious 7?",
    "response": "Yes! I saw it in the theatre. It was one of their best yet!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes! I saw it in the theatre. It was one of their best yet!",
    "response": "I know. I can't believe that Paul Walker's brother finished his character out for him."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know. I can't believe that Paul Walker's brother finished his character out for him.",
    "response": "Yea I know, I could barely tell which brother was playing Brian."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea I know, I could barely tell which brother was playing Brian.",
    "response": "I loved the last scene where they sort of did an homage to Paul."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I loved the last scene where they sort of did an homage to Paul.",
    "response": "Do you mean where Dom went to race him one last time?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you mean where Dom went to race him one last time?",
    "response": "Yea and then they showed a video montage of Paul Walker and Brian."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea and then they showed a video montage of Paul Walker and Brian.",
    "response": "It had me crying! It was so sad."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It had me crying! It was so sad.",
    "response": "Oh me too, I am going to miss that character in the movies. He was so great."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh me too, I am going to miss that character in the movies. He was so great.",
    "response": "I agree it is very sad to see him go."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The new Picture Fast & Furious 8 will be coming out this summer are you going to see it?",
    "response": "Yes I like Fast &Furious there are a lot of great actors in their movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes I like Fast &Furious there are a lot of great actors in their movies.",
    "response": "I like action movies and Fast & Furious has a lot of action in it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like action movies and Fast & Furious has a lot of action in it.",
    "response": "Dwayne Johnson is in a few of the movies too, he is a good actor."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Dwayne Johnson is in a few of the movies too, he is a good actor.",
    "response": "Yea! do you like Vin Diesel in the movies?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea! do you like Vin Diesel in the movies?",
    "response": "Yes! Vin Diesel is a real tough guy and drives a cool car."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes! Vin Diesel is a real tough guy and drives a cool car.",
    "response": "Do you like Tyrese Gibson?he is in a of the Fast & Furious movies too."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you like Tyrese Gibson?he is in a of the Fast & Furious movies too.",
    "response": "Yes! and Fast & Furious 1,2,and 3 were great movies too."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes! and Fast & Furious 1,2,and 3 were great movies too.",
    "response": "Do you like when they have all those drag races?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you like when they have all those drag races?",
    "response": "Yes, Fast & Furious is a great movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "did you hear about paul walker?",
    "response": "Oh yes, I did, I was so sad to hear it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh yes, I did, I was so sad to hear it.",
    "response": "At first I could not believe it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "At first I could not believe it.",
    "response": "Me too. I thought it was just a prank."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too. I thought it was just a prank.",
    "response": "So what will happen to current fast and furious movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "So what will happen to current fast and furious movie?",
    "response": "Yes, I had the same question."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, I had the same question.",
    "response": "I think they will just kill him in movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think they will just kill him in movie.",
    "response": "well, for that they will have to modify the story of the movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "well, for that they will have to modify the story of the movie.",
    "response": "Oh yes, But what else can they do?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh yes, But what else can they do?",
    "response": "I don't know, may be they can use body double or something."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Man, can you believe they've come out with eight Fast & Furious movies?",
    "response": "Hey man, if it works, I don't see why they should stop making them. Fast 7 and the Fate of the Furious both grossed over a billion dollars."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey man, if it works, I don't see why they should stop making them. Fast 7 and the Fate of the Furious both grossed over a billion dollars.",
    "response": "Jeez, don't you think they're kind of milking the franchise? I mean, I can't see them making any more movies without Paul Walker."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Jeez, don't you think they're kind of milking the franchise? I mean, I can't see them making any more movies without Paul Walker.",
    "response": "Not really, if it's not broken, don't fix it. Anyways, do you happen to have a favorite Fast & Furious movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Not really, if it's not broken, don't fix it. Anyways, do you happen to have a favorite Fast & Furious movie?",
    "response": "Honestly, I really like the first The Fast and the Furious movie. I have vivid memories of it because my dad took me to see it on my birthday."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Honestly, I really like the first The Fast and the Furious movie. I have vivid memories of it because my dad took me to see it on my birthday.",
    "response": "Good choice man, but I'd have to say Fast 7 was my favorite movie. I really like the soundtrack too, See You Again is a great song."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Good choice man, but I'd have to say Fast 7 was my favorite movie. I really like the soundtrack too, See You Again is a great song.",
    "response": "Don't you think that song is a little played out? Charlie Puth sounds like generic pop to me."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Don't you think that song is a little played out? Charlie Puth sounds like generic pop to me.",
    "response": "I think that's a little disrespectful to say man, the song is a real touching tribute to Paul Walker's memory. Brian will forever be immortalized by that song."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think that's a little disrespectful to say man, the song is a real touching tribute to Paul Walker's memory. Brian will forever be immortalized by that song.",
    "response": "No disrespect to Paul Walker, I'm just a little tired of hearing that song everyday on the radio."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No disrespect to Paul Walker, I'm just a little tired of hearing that song everyday on the radio.",
    "response": "I see what you mean, and respect your entitlement to an opinion. If they keep coming out with movies, I'll keep watching them till Fast 70 is out and I'm an 82-year-old grandpa!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you like Brian in the Fast and Furious movies?",
    "response": "Yes I love him."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes I love him.",
    "response": "Do you think he's that awesome in real life?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you think he's that awesome in real life?",
    "response": "I hope so, he's so dreamy."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I hope so, he's so dreamy.",
    "response": "Do you have a crush on him?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you have a crush on him?",
    "response": "Obviously I do."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Obviously I do.",
    "response": "What do you like about him as an actor?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What do you like about him as an actor?",
    "response": "Well first off he's all business but at the same time he's not. He will do what it takes to get the job done but for the right reasons."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well first off he's all business but at the same time he's not. He will do what it takes to get the job done but for the right reasons.",
    "response": "That's a good reason."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's a good reason.",
    "response": "Plus he's just awesome."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you like that fast and the furious movies?",
    "response": "Not really."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Not really.",
    "response": "Oh how come?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh how come?",
    "response": "I just thought it was too predictable for a action movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I just thought it was too predictable for a action movie.",
    "response": "Oh like what do you mean?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh like what do you mean?",
    "response": "Like the explosions and the women crowding around races."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Like the explosions and the women crowding around races.",
    "response": "Does that not happen in real life?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Does that not happen in real life?",
    "response": "Not that I know of."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Not that I know of.",
    "response": "Oh I had no idea."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh I had no idea.",
    "response": "Yea. I just didnt like them."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hi.",
    "response": "Hey."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey.",
    "response": "What was the last fast and furious movie you saw?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What was the last fast and furious movie you saw?",
    "response": "I just saw the latest one in theaters."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I just saw the latest one in theaters.",
    "response": "Oh really?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh really?",
    "response": "Yeah."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah.",
    "response": "How was it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How was it?",
    "response": "It wasn't the best of the series, but it was good action."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It wasn't the best of the series, but it was good action.",
    "response": "Oh that's good.  I heard it got so so reviews."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh that's good.  I heard it got so so reviews.",
    "response": "Yeah."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I watched Furious 7 again last night.",
    "response": "I can't believe that is the last we will see of Paul."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I can't believe that is the last we will see of Paul.",
    "response": "Yea, it was really unfortunate."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, it was really unfortunate.",
    "response": "The movie paid tribute to him pretty well."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The movie paid tribute to him pretty well.",
    "response": "Yea, that end scene had me tearing up a little bit."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, that end scene had me tearing up a little bit.",
    "response": "It was done really well and tastefully."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was done really well and tastefully.",
    "response": "Yea, he will always be missed."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, he will always be missed.",
    "response": "The movie itself was pretty good too."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The movie itself was pretty good too.",
    "response": "Yea, I liked how it took place after the third movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, I liked how it took place after the third movie.",
    "response": "It is nice how they were able to tie everything back together."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you know what NOS was when you watched The Fast and the Furious?",
    "response": "I had no clue and I still don't."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I had no clue and I still don't.",
    "response": "It was cool how it made him go way faster."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was cool how it made him go way faster.",
    "response": "Paul Walker?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Paul Walker?",
    "response": "Everyone actually. They all used it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Everyone actually. They all used it.",
    "response": "That movie taught me a lot about cars."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That movie taught me a lot about cars.",
    "response": "Me too."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too.",
    "response": "I loved the scene where Paul Walker put his car on the line."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I loved the scene where Paul Walker put his car on the line.",
    "response": "Yeah, I was rooting for him."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, I was rooting for him.",
    "response": "It sucks that he lost though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You know, the Fast & Furious films have really come a long way.",
    "response": "I'm not too familiar with those movies, I'm afraid. Help me out."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I'm not too familiar with those movies, I'm afraid. Help me out.",
    "response": "I got you. So, to keep it short, it basically went from simple street racing to becoming global vehicle warfare."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I got you. So, to keep it short, it basically went from simple street racing to becoming global vehicle warfare.",
    "response": "That sounds insane."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That sounds insane.",
    "response": "And it's just as insane as it sounds."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "And it's just as insane as it sounds.",
    "response": "I imagine it's been quite the journey for you."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I imagine it's been quite the journey for you.",
    "response": "It has. I just can't wait for what's in store."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It has. I just can't wait for what's in store.",
    "response": "I might have to binge watch those movies just to see for myself."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I might have to binge watch those movies just to see for myself.",
    "response": "I have the entire collection on Blu-ray. I can lend them to you if you want."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I have the entire collection on Blu-ray. I can lend them to you if you want.",
    "response": "That sounds like a good idea."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What's your favorite Fast and Furious movie?",
    "response": "Probably The Fast and the Furious: Tokyo Drift."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Probably The Fast and the Furious: Tokyo Drift.",
    "response": "What do you like about that one?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What do you like about that one?",
    "response": "It's pretty exotic.  All the neon in downtown Tokyo at night."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It's pretty exotic.  All the neon in downtown Tokyo at night.",
    "response": "Right. Anything else?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Right. Anything else?",
    "response": "The drifting technique.  Kind of fascinating."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The drifting technique.  Kind of fascinating.",
    "response": "They made it look effortless."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They made it look effortless.",
    "response": "But I think it really takes a lot of practice."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "But I think it really takes a lot of practice.",
    "response": "And the ensemble was really great in this one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "And the ensemble was really great in this one.",
    "response": "Plus so much racing on the surface streets. Spectacular!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you like Fast and Furious movies?",
    "response": "Yes, I do, although I prefer the first movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, I do, although I prefer the first movies.",
    "response": "I liked the first movies as well but think that the rock is a great addition to the team."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I liked the first movies as well but think that the rock is a great addition to the team.",
    "response": "Yeah, him and Statham are great actors but I didnt like the last two movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, him and Statham are great actors but I didnt like the last two movies.",
    "response": "I thought the last two movies were ok, I didnt like the visual effects they were just too loaded."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I thought the last two movies were ok, I didnt like the visual effects they were just too loaded.",
    "response": "I miss the days that Fast and Furious was simple."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I miss the days that Fast and Furious was simple.",
    "response": "I know, I miss those days two."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know, I miss those days two.",
    "response": "So whats your favorite Fast and Furious movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "So whats your favorite Fast and Furious movie.",
    "response": "I  liked the first and second movies the most what about you?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I  liked the first and second movies the most what about you?",
    "response": "My favorite was definetely the second movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you see the Fast and furious 8?",
    "response": "I watched it, but I couldn't really get into it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I watched it, but I couldn't really get into it.",
    "response": "What didn't you understand?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What didn't you understand?",
    "response": "I didn't really think that Dom would leave his girlfriend like that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I didn't really think that Dom would leave his girlfriend like that.",
    "response": "Well, he was blackmailed, so he didn't have a choice."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, he was blackmailed, so he didn't have a choice.",
    "response": "Yeah, but the other woman wasn't his life long soul mate."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, but the other woman wasn't his life long soul mate.",
    "response": "She had his kid, though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "She had his kid, though.",
    "response": "He didn't know that when he started the whole rebellion adventure."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He didn't know that when he started the whole rebellion adventure.",
    "response": "I didn't think it was a bad movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I didn't think it was a bad movie.",
    "response": "I don't think it was bad, it just wasn't as good as some of the others."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen entire fast and furious series?",
    "response": "Oh yes! I just love that series!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh yes! I just love that series!",
    "response": "Great. So tell me do you like brian's character?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Great. So tell me do you like brian's character?",
    "response": "Yes, he is good."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, he is good.",
    "response": "Okay. So do you like him more as a cop or as a street racer?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Okay. So do you like him more as a cop or as a street racer?",
    "response": "That's a tough question."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's a tough question.",
    "response": "Still, you can pick one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Still, you can pick one.",
    "response": "I think I like him more as street racer. It's more cool I think."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think I like him more as street racer. It's more cool I think.",
    "response": "I agree. Being cop is boring."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I agree. Being cop is boring.",
    "response": "Not always, but in this case I like him more as street racer."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen the new Fast and Furious movie?",
    "response": "No, you mean The Fate of the Furious?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No, you mean The Fate of the Furious?",
    "response": "Yeah number 8. Without Paul Walker. So sad."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah number 8. Without Paul Walker. So sad.",
    "response": "Yeah it still kind of pulls at the heart. But no I haven't seen the new one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah it still kind of pulls at the heart. But no I haven't seen the new one.",
    "response": "I just can't bring myself to see it yet. I will probably wait until it comes out on DVD so I can cry in peace."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I just can't bring myself to see it yet. I will probably wait until it comes out on DVD so I can cry in peace.",
    "response": "Well I don't know about cry, they are usually so action-packed that you don't have time to do much more than eat your popcorn and watch the screen."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well I don't know about cry, they are usually so action-packed that you don't have time to do much more than eat your popcorn and watch the screen.",
    "response": "You could be right. I just wish Paul Walker was still here. I hate it that he died like that. Well I do think the send off at the end of the last movie was touching and sweet."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You could be right. I just wish Paul Walker was still here. I hate it that he died like that. Well I do think the send off at the end of the last movie was touching and sweet.",
    "response": "It was. When he rode off into the sunset I think that said it all. It had to be hard to come up with an ending that would do him justice. I mean him and Vin Diesel were the movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was. When he rode off into the sunset I think that said it all. It had to be hard to come up with an ending that would do him justice. I mean him and Vin Diesel were the movie.",
    "response": "Yeah, family. And in real life too. But I can't wait to see The Fate of the Furious. They have some new people in it like Charlize Theron that should be a good time."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, family. And in real life too. But I can't wait to see The Fate of the Furious. They have some new people in it like Charlize Theron that should be a good time.",
    "response": "I agree, maybe we'll see it together. Pop some popcorn and get some M&Ms and do it right. RIP Paul Walker."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Are you going to catch the new Fast & Furious movie?",
    "response": "Nah. They stopped being good when they stopped being about street racing and turned into cheesy spy flicks"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Nah. They stopped being good when they stopped being about street racing and turned into cheesy spy flicks",
    "response": "Same. And when Paul Walker died, it kinda made the whole street racing thing seem like a bad idea."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Same. And when Paul Walker died, it kinda made the whole street racing thing seem like a bad idea.",
    "response": "Yeah, it sucks when you get killed trying to do the same dumb stunts in reality as in your movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, it sucks when you get killed trying to do the same dumb stunts in reality as in your movies.",
    "response": "I mean, at least they still got Vin Diesel, but he's gettin' kinda old, ya know?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I mean, at least they still got Vin Diesel, but he's gettin' kinda old, ya know?",
    "response": "Same for Jason Statham. they need new movies, not more of the same old stuff."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Same for Jason Statham. they need new movies, not more of the same old stuff.",
    "response": "Did you know Diesel play the voice of a robot?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you know Diesel play the voice of a robot?",
    "response": "Wait, seriously?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Wait, seriously?",
    "response": "Yeah, he was the robot in \"The Iron Giant.\""
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, he was the robot in \"The Iron Giant.\"",
    "response": "I can see it now: \"*BEEP BEEP* I AM GOING TO DO SOME DRIFTING AND MAKE JASON STATHAM LOOK GOOD.\""
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you remember seeing the latest fast and the furious movie?",
    "response": "I do, remember I went with you and my dad?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I do, remember I went with you and my dad?",
    "response": "Yeah I do.  What was your favorite part in it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah I do.  What was your favorite part in it?",
    "response": "It was when Vin Diesel turns bad and joins the enemy."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was when Vin Diesel turns bad and joins the enemy.",
    "response": "What is that part your favorite?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is that part your favorite?",
    "response": "It's my favorite because I love Vin plus I never saw the turn coming."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It's my favorite because I love Vin plus I never saw the turn coming.",
    "response": "Me either. I am glad they are making more of the movies to hopefully explain his actions."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me either. I am glad they are making more of the movies to hopefully explain his actions.",
    "response": "Me to.  The way they drive the cars around with the stunts makes it a great movie to see."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me to.  The way they drive the cars around with the stunts makes it a great movie to see.",
    "response": "I agree.  I love the black muscle car the Vin's character drives around."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I agree.  I love the black muscle car the Vin's character drives around.",
    "response": "I love the green honda.  It is little but packs a punch."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which is your favorite Fast & Furious movie?",
    "response": "My favorite The Fate of the Furious"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "My favorite The Fate of the Furious",
    "response": "Is that the one where Charlize Theron was the villian Cipher?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is that the one where Charlize Theron was the villian Cipher?",
    "response": "Yes! She played that part perfectly."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes! She played that part perfectly.",
    "response": "I agree she did. It was horrible when she killed Elena."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I agree she did. It was horrible when she killed Elena.",
    "response": "I know! I am so glad Dom and the team were able to beat her."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know! I am so glad Dom and the team were able to beat her.",
    "response": "Me too. Dom's son was so cute at the end."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too. Dom's son was so cute at the end.",
    "response": "He was adorable. I think it's so good Letty was accepting of his son."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He was adorable. I think it's so good Letty was accepting of his son.",
    "response": "She really supports him. She was the main one saying that he hadn't gone rouge."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "She really supports him. She was the main one saying that he hadn't gone rouge.",
    "response": "Yeah she really loves him."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is you favorite Fast and Furious movie?",
    "response": "I didn't see but one or two."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I didn't see but one or two.",
    "response": "I can't remember the first one very well it was so long ago"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I can't remember the first one very well it was so long ago",
    "response": "Yes that was 2001 with Vin Diesel"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes that was 2001 with Vin Diesel",
    "response": "Right that was one of the reasons I wanted to see it was he was someone new and interesting to see as a character."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Right that was one of the reasons I wanted to see it was he was someone new and interesting to see as a character.",
    "response": "That didn't last long. He got really boring to watch."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That didn't last long. He got really boring to watch.",
    "response": "You are right about that. He didn't entice me to want to watch that next two Fast and Furious movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You are right about that. He didn't entice me to want to watch that next two Fast and Furious movies.",
    "response": "I saw them. Not so great."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I saw them. Not so great.",
    "response": "When Tokyo Drift came out I wanted to go see it just for the drifting because it looked so cool. But I never went."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When Tokyo Drift came out I wanted to go see it just for the drifting because it looked so cool. But I never went.",
    "response": "I didn't go because they were all the same to me"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen The Fast and the Furious: Tokyo Drift?",
    "response": "No, I haven't seen that one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No, I haven't seen that one.",
    "response": "It's pretty good, you should watch it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It's pretty good, you should watch it.",
    "response": "Didn't that come out a while ago?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Didn't that come out a while ago?",
    "response": "Yeah it came out in 2006."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah it came out in 2006.",
    "response": "Wow that's so long ago. What's it about?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Wow that's so long ago. What's it about?",
    "response": "It's about the underground racing scene in Japan and how a troubled teen gets involved with it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It's about the underground racing scene in Japan and how a troubled teen gets involved with it.",
    "response": "It sounds pretty good.  Who's in it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It sounds pretty good.  Who's in it?",
    "response": "Bow Wow and Lucas Black"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Bow Wow and Lucas Black",
    "response": "I'll have to check it out."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I haven't seen furious 7 yet",
    "response": "Me either"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me either",
    "response": "Ive been afraid to"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Ive been afraid to",
    "response": "Me tooi want ro see it though"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me tooi want ro see it though",
    "response": "Yea ive always wondered what they did with paul walker"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea ive always wondered what they did with paul walker",
    "response": "Me too"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too",
    "response": "If they killed him in the movie its wven sadder because he was dead in real life"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "If they killed him in the movie its wven sadder because he was dead in real life",
    "response": "I know"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know",
    "response": "It sucks"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It sucks",
    "response": "Yes i agree with that"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you remember the first race in fast & furious?",
    "response": "The first ever race?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The first ever race?",
    "response": "Yes that is the one i'm talking about."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes that is the one i'm talking about.",
    "response": "Why do you ask?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why do you ask?",
    "response": "I was just thinking about that scene and was curious if you remember if Brian's car was or broke down."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I was just thinking about that scene and was curious if you remember if Brian's car was or broke down.",
    "response": "I believe it had some engine troubles during the race."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I believe it had some engine troubles during the race.",
    "response": "I remember he was trying to give Dom the best race he could."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I remember he was trying to give Dom the best race he could.",
    "response": "Yep Brian tried so hard that one race."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yep Brian tried so hard that one race.",
    "response": "That race set the stage for the rest of the movie and movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That race set the stage for the rest of the movie and movies.",
    "response": "I agree I think if that scene sucked it wouldn't have been as big as it was."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How is your favorite fast and furious actor?",
    "response": "I would say Ludacris?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I would say Ludacris?",
    "response": "Why Ludacris, he has such as small role?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why Ludacris, he has such as small role?",
    "response": "I beg to differ, I really like his role."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I beg to differ, I really like his role.",
    "response": "Why do you like Ludacris' role?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why do you like Ludacris' role?",
    "response": "I like his role because he is the under dog in all of the movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like his role because he is the under dog in all of the movies.",
    "response": "True, that is a good point."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "True, that is a good point.",
    "response": "Who is your favorite actor in the series?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who is your favorite actor in the series?",
    "response": "My favorite actor is the Rock."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "My favorite actor is the Rock.",
    "response": "Oh yea, I love the Rock in all of his movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you see The Fate of the Furious?",
    "response": "Is that the newest Fast and the Furious movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is that the newest Fast and the Furious movie?",
    "response": "Yea, it was pretty great, one of my favorites."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, it was pretty great, one of my favorites.",
    "response": "I have not seen any of those movies since the third one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I have not seen any of those movies since the third one.",
    "response": "Really?  Since Tokyo Drift?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Really?  Since Tokyo Drift?",
    "response": "You picked the worst time to stop, it got way better after that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You picked the worst time to stop, it got way better after that.",
    "response": "I thought it got pretty silly so I couldn't get myself to keep watching them."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I thought it got pretty silly so I couldn't get myself to keep watching them.",
    "response": "The newer ones are pretty much action movies, less about racing."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The newer ones are pretty much action movies, less about racing.",
    "response": "That is interesting, all I remember were the racing scenes."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That is interesting, all I remember were the racing scenes.",
    "response": "You should give them a shot."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which was the last Fast & Furious movie you saw?",
    "response": "Furious 7."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Furious 7.",
    "response": "That was good. Sad though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That was good. Sad though.",
    "response": "You're talking about the scene when Dom and Brian drive in different directions?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You're talking about the scene when Dom and Brian drive in different directions?",
    "response": "That's the one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's the one.",
    "response": "Made me feel awful for Paul Walker."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Made me feel awful for Paul Walker.",
    "response": "A real tragedy.  They shouldn't have been racing."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "A real tragedy.  They shouldn't have been racing.",
    "response": "I don't know the circumstances but I agree."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I don't know the circumstances but I agree.",
    "response": "Then now there's another film.  The Fate of the Furious."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Then now there's another film.  The Fate of the Furious.",
    "response": "I guess the whole franchise has been a huge moneymaker."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen the first Fast and Furious movie?",
    "response": "I've seen all of them, but that one is my favorite."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I've seen all of them, but that one is my favorite.",
    "response": "I sue it in my class to teach irony."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I sue it in my class to teach irony.",
    "response": "How do you do that?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How do you do that?",
    "response": "It's dramatic irony because we know something that the characters don't."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It's dramatic irony because we know something that the characters don't.",
    "response": "Like that Paul Walker is a cop?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Like that Paul Walker is a cop?",
    "response": "Exactly.  Plus it's also situational irony."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Exactly.  Plus it's also situational irony.",
    "response": "When does that happen?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When does that happen?",
    "response": "At the end when Paul Walker throws Vin Diesel the keys.  Not exactly what your expecting."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "At the end when Paul Walker throws Vin Diesel the keys.  Not exactly what your expecting.",
    "response": "Good point.  Those are probably good examples for kids."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What do you think was Roman Pierce's best line in 2 fast 2 furious?",
    "response": "I'm actually torn on that one. If I had to choose then when they were walking away at the end of the movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I'm actually torn on that one. If I had to choose then when they were walking away at the end of the movie.",
    "response": "After they took some of the ransom cash."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "After they took some of the ransom cash.",
    "response": "Yeah, after Brian said \"Our pockets ain't empty cuz\", then Roman lifts up his shirt and says \"and we ain't hungry no more either\", and he's got cash stuffed in his pants."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, after Brian said \"Our pockets ain't empty cuz\", then Roman lifts up his shirt and says \"and we ain't hungry no more either\", and he's got cash stuffed in his pants.",
    "response": "That was a great walkout line, what was your number two."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That was a great walkout line, what was your number two.",
    "response": "Well it's not so much what he said but what he did when he said it. It was when they were driving to the final meet."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well it's not so much what he said but what he did when he said it. It was when they were driving to the final meet.",
    "response": "Let me guess, it was just when he hit the ejector button."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Let me guess, it was just when he hit the ejector button.",
    "response": "Yes! That was hilarious, he just hit the button and shouts to the guy \"ejecto seato cuz!\", I was on the floor laughing after that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes! That was hilarious, he just hit the button and shouts to the guy \"ejecto seato cuz!\", I was on the floor laughing after that.",
    "response": "Well it is hard narrowing down a Roman Pierce quote."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well it is hard narrowing down a Roman Pierce quote.",
    "response": "Well of course it is, he never stops talking or he'd die."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hi.",
    "response": "Hey."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey.",
    "response": "Have you seen the latest Fast and Furious?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen the latest Fast and Furious?",
    "response": "8?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "8?",
    "response": "Yeah the one in theaters now."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah the one in theaters now.",
    "response": "No, I haven't.  Have you?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No, I haven't.  Have you?",
    "response": "I haven't either."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I haven't either.",
    "response": "Do you plan on seeing it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you plan on seeing it.",
    "response": "I'm not sure at the moment."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I'm not sure at the moment.",
    "response": "I don't plan on going to see it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Paul Walker was so cute in Fast and Furious.",
    "response": "I like Vin Diesel better."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like Vin Diesel better.",
    "response": "How many movies have they made now?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How many movies have they made now?",
    "response": "I don't know maybe like 8. Furious 8 I think is what they were working on when Paul Walker died."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I don't know maybe like 8. Furious 8 I think is what they were working on when Paul Walker died.",
    "response": "I thought it was neat how they still kept him in the film"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I thought it was neat how they still kept him in the film",
    "response": "Yes, it was. Did I hear his brother was a stand in for some of the stuff that hadn't been filmed yet?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, it was. Did I hear his brother was a stand in for some of the stuff that hadn't been filmed yet?",
    "response": "I'm not sure about that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I'm not sure about that.",
    "response": "Me either, I sure hate to see it end though"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me either, I sure hate to see it end though",
    "response": "Well I heard Liam Nesson was going to be in the next one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well I heard Liam Nesson was going to be in the next one.",
    "response": "That might be an interesting character change"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you think the Fast and The Furious is still relevant?",
    "response": "There are really just a lot of them."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "There are really just a lot of them.",
    "response": "Do you like the new ones?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you like the new ones?",
    "response": "I like the Rock, he makes them a bit more fun."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like the Rock, he makes them a bit more fun.",
    "response": "I think he makes the movies a bit silly."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think he makes the movies a bit silly.",
    "response": "He adds comic relief."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He adds comic relief.",
    "response": "Since he started them, with his one liners they are way less serious."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Since he started them, with his one liners they are way less serious.",
    "response": "I think they went down hill when Paul Walker passed away."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think they went down hill when Paul Walker passed away.",
    "response": "He made the movie more worthwhile."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He made the movie more worthwhile.",
    "response": "I miss that guy, his story line was always the most full."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You know part of the fast and furious movies i love the most?",
    "response": "Which one"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which one",
    "response": "The ones with the safes and they somehow switch them and nobody sees"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The ones with the safes and they somehow switch them and nobody sees",
    "response": "That was pretty awesome"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That was pretty awesome",
    "response": "It was so smart and well thought out"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was so smart and well thought out",
    "response": "Yea i didnt know what they were doing"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea i didnt know what they were doing",
    "response": "It was so shocking"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was so shocking",
    "response": "It was great"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was great",
    "response": "That whole movie was awesome"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That whole movie was awesome",
    "response": "It was"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What happens at the end of The Fast and the Furious?",
    "response": "I will not tell you. You have to watch it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I will not tell you. You have to watch it?",
    "response": "Is there a lot of drama in it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is there a lot of drama in it?",
    "response": "There is tons of drama."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "There is tons of drama.",
    "response": "What is the best part?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the best part?",
    "response": "The street race near the beginning?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The street race near the beginning?",
    "response": "Does Paul Walker win it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Does Paul Walker win it?",
    "response": "Watch the movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Watch the movie.",
    "response": "I will."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I will.",
    "response": "The whole movie is suspenseful."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen Fast & Furious?",
    "response": "Which one, haven't there been a lot?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which one, haven't there been a lot?",
    "response": "Fast & Furious is the fourth one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Fast & Furious is the fourth one.",
    "response": "It was just called Fast & Furious?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was just called Fast & Furious?",
    "response": "Strange name but that is correct."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Strange name but that is correct.",
    "response": "Then what was the first one called?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Then what was the first one called?",
    "response": "The Fast and the Furious."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The Fast and the Furious.",
    "response": "So they just took 2 words for part 4?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "So they just took 2 words for part 4?",
    "response": "Yea, seems quite lazy or they ran out of ideas."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, seems quite lazy or they ran out of ideas.",
    "response": "Yea, and no I have not seen it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hi.",
    "response": "Hello."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hello.",
    "response": "Have you seen any of the fast and furious movies?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen any of the fast and furious movies?",
    "response": "Yeah I've seen some."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah I've seen some.",
    "response": "Have you seen the one that just came out?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen the one that just came out?",
    "response": "No I haven't seen it yet.  Have you?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No I haven't seen it yet.  Have you?",
    "response": "I plan on going to see it in the theaters."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I plan on going to see it in the theaters.",
    "response": "Oh, I don't think it got very good reviews."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh, I don't think it got very good reviews.",
    "response": "Yeah I saw that but I don't care."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah I saw that but I don't care.",
    "response": "Ok."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I just watched the first Fast & Furious movie.",
    "response": "Did you like it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you like it?",
    "response": "Yeah it was really awesome."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah it was really awesome.",
    "response": "Wasn't Vin Diesel in that one?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Wasn't Vin Diesel in that one?",
    "response": "Yeah, I'm pretty sure he's in all of them."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, I'm pretty sure he's in all of them.",
    "response": "Is Dwayne Johnson in that one? The only one I saw had him in it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is Dwayne Johnson in that one? The only one I saw had him in it.",
    "response": "He's not in the first one. He joined later in the series."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He's not in the first one. He joined later in the series.",
    "response": "Have you seen any of the others?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen any of the others?",
    "response": "I've seen them all."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I've seen them all.",
    "response": "Cool."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen the latest Fast and Furious movie?",
    "response": "Not yet, have you?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Not yet, have you?",
    "response": "No, but I saw other ones."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No, but I saw other ones.",
    "response": "How were they?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How were they?",
    "response": "They were really sweet."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They were really sweet.",
    "response": "How so?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How so?",
    "response": "Vin Diesel is just an incredible actor."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Vin Diesel is just an incredible actor.",
    "response": "That's true.  The movie must be so action packed."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's true.  The movie must be so action packed.",
    "response": "You're not kidding.  I haven't seen Fate of the Furious yet, but it's next on my list."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You're not kidding.  I haven't seen Fate of the Furious yet, but it's next on my list.",
    "response": "Hey, lets see that one together."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Could you imagine a more actiony fast and furious movie",
    "response": "What in the world are you on about"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What in the world are you on about",
    "response": "Making those movies more action focused"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Making those movies more action focused",
    "response": "That makes no sense"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That makes no sense",
    "response": "How so"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How so",
    "response": "Imagine them like twisted metal or something"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Imagine them like twisted metal or something",
    "response": "Like racing cars with guns"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Like racing cars with guns",
    "response": "Yeah man"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah man",
    "response": "That is the dumbest thing ever it would kill what makes it good"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That is the dumbest thing ever it would kill what makes it good",
    "response": "Why is that"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who is your favorite actor in \"2 Fast 2 Furious\"?",
    "response": "Well, I like Ludacris who plays Tej because of his smooth acting skills."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, I like Ludacris who plays Tej because of his smooth acting skills.",
    "response": "Ludacris is cool but I am more interesting in the skills of Tyrese Gibson who plays Roman Pierce."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Ludacris is cool but I am more interesting in the skills of Tyrese Gibson who plays Roman Pierce.",
    "response": "Tyrese is very smooth in his acting skills and he has been acting for a while now."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Tyrese is very smooth in his acting skills and he has been acting for a while now.",
    "response": "I also like the story line the movie. Do you remember what happened to Carter the drug dealer?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I also like the story line the movie. Do you remember what happened to Carter the drug dealer?",
    "response": "Yes, doesn't he get arrested at the end while trying to get away from the cops?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, doesn't he get arrested at the end while trying to get away from the cops?",
    "response": "Yes, that is right. He was a very smooth actor as well. What is his real name?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, that is right. He was a very smooth actor as well. What is his real name?",
    "response": "I believe his real name is Cole Hauser. I have seen him like a couple of movies since he played in this one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I believe his real name is Cole Hauser. I have seen him like a couple of movies since he played in this one.",
    "response": "Can you imagine having a house like he did in the movie? Such a big house and all the cars he had."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Can you imagine having a house like he did in the movie? Such a big house and all the cars he had.",
    "response": "Tell me about it. I will one day be living like him."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I used to hate the Fast and the Furious movies but now I love them.",
    "response": "Really why?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Really why?",
    "response": "I just didn't understand what was happening."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I just didn't understand what was happening.",
    "response": "Makes sense. I think they're so cool!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Makes sense. I think they're so cool!",
    "response": "Yeah I went back and rewatched them all. Now I'm obsessed."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah I went back and rewatched them all. Now I'm obsessed.",
    "response": "Me too. I love Fast 5"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too. I love Fast 5",
    "response": "Fast 5 is my favorite ! The characters are great and it's so action packed."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Fast 5 is my favorite ! The characters are great and it's so action packed.",
    "response": "I agree. Plus the team makes the movie. With that switch at the end."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I agree. Plus the team makes the movie. With that switch at the end.",
    "response": "I know I was so mind blown."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know I was so mind blown.",
    "response": "It was genius that they got all that money."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen any of the Fast and Furious movies?",
    "response": "I've only seen the 6th one, and the end of the 7th one.  Do you like them?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I've only seen the 6th one, and the end of the 7th one.  Do you like them?",
    "response": "I think they're pretty fun.  Dumb but fun."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think they're pretty fun.  Dumb but fun.",
    "response": "I liked what I saw.  It's always fun to watch Dwayne Johnson throw people around."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I liked what I saw.  It's always fun to watch Dwayne Johnson throw people around.",
    "response": "Oh yeah, the scene in the interrogation room?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh yeah, the scene in the interrogation room?",
    "response": "Yeah - jeez, that was a lot of damage!  The light fixtures too?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah - jeez, that was a lot of damage!  The light fixtures too?",
    "response": "Well, that's what you get when you mess with Dwayne."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, that's what you get when you mess with Dwayne.",
    "response": "I can tell!  How about that scene with the plane?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I can tell!  How about that scene with the plane?",
    "response": "That was great!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That was great!",
    "response": "How did the plane stay at such a low altitude without crashing?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Wow i have never seen one of these before but it is pretty intense",
    "response": "seen what before"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "seen what before",
    "response": "The fast and the furious movies"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The fast and the furious movies",
    "response": "Oh yeah those are pretty rad"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh yeah those are pretty rad",
    "response": "I love paul walker"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I love paul walker",
    "response": "He is pretty amazing"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He is pretty amazing",
    "response": "Shame that it happened"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Shame that it happened",
    "response": "What happened"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What happened",
    "response": "Him passing"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Him passing",
    "response": "Oh i had not know about that actually"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you like the Fast & Furious Tokyo Drift?",
    "response": "Yes I do."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes I do.",
    "response": "What is your favorite part?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is your favorite part?",
    "response": "I like the part where they race through the housing construction."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like the part where they race through the housing construction.",
    "response": "I like that part as well.  Probably not my favorite though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like that part as well.  Probably not my favorite though.",
    "response": "What is your favorite?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is your favorite?",
    "response": "Mine is when they are drifting in the parking ramp."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Mine is when they are drifting in the parking ramp.",
    "response": "That is a really great part as well."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That is a really great part as well.",
    "response": "I need to watch that movie again sometime soon."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I need to watch that movie again sometime soon.",
    "response": "Me as well."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How do you feel about the series?",
    "response": "It's alright, tons of action though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It's alright, tons of action though.",
    "response": "And really hot guys haha."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "And really hot guys haha.",
    "response": "Yea, definitely! I love dom!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, definitely! I love dom!",
    "response": "Han too!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Han too!",
    "response": "Oh you like tokyo drift?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh you like tokyo drift?",
    "response": "Yea I do!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea I do!",
    "response": "The timeline gets a bit weird in the series."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The timeline gets a bit weird in the series.",
    "response": "Yea, but it's not so bad."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, but it's not so bad.",
    "response": "I hope they only go forward after this."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who is your favorite character in the Fast & Furious franchise?",
    "response": "I would have to say Dom."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I would have to say Dom.",
    "response": "He is a great character, why do you like him so much?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He is a great character, why do you like him so much?",
    "response": "Well he's like a double sided blade one side is rough and tough the other side is soft and sentimental."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well he's like a double sided blade one side is rough and tough the other side is soft and sentimental.",
    "response": "That's a very good point, I never thought of him like that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's a very good point, I never thought of him like that.",
    "response": "Well he makes all these decisions to appear as this bad guy especially early on, then he always makes the morally right choice when it matters."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well he makes all these decisions to appear as this bad guy especially early on, then he always makes the morally right choice when it matters.",
    "response": "That's a very good point.  He is this brutal person yet so moral when it matters."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's a very good point.  He is this brutal person yet so moral when it matters.",
    "response": "That's why he is my favorite."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's why he is my favorite.",
    "response": "I might have to watch the movies again."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I might have to watch the movies again.",
    "response": "Yeah you're making me nostalgic."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you have a favorite character in the Fast & Furious series?",
    "response": "If I'm being honest, it's just got to be Dom."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "If I'm being honest, it's just got to be Dom.",
    "response": "Really? Care to explain?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Really? Care to explain?",
    "response": "I just find him to be the coolest character is all."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I just find him to be the coolest character is all.",
    "response": "Cool how, though?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Cool how, though?",
    "response": "His tone of voice, his facial expressions, his fashion, his overall demeanor, it all just screams cool guy to me."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "His tone of voice, his facial expressions, his fashion, his overall demeanor, it all just screams cool guy to me.",
    "response": "But is there any bigger reasons why?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "But is there any bigger reasons why?",
    "response": "I think he has a decent amount of depth to his character."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think he has a decent amount of depth to his character.",
    "response": "Do you mean emotionally."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you mean emotionally.",
    "response": "Of course. He's more softhearted than most will say he is."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The latest 'Fast' movie felt rather empty with Brian, Paul Walker's character.",
    "response": "I absolutely agree.  I am just glad that the send-off was so good in 7."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I absolutely agree.  I am just glad that the send-off was so good in 7.",
    "response": "It was truly an emotional and touching farewell."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was truly an emotional and touching farewell.",
    "response": "I liked that Dom named his new baby after Brian in the latest movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I liked that Dom named his new baby after Brian in the latest movie.",
    "response": "I did as well, though I don't think it necessarily made sense."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I did as well, though I don't think it necessarily made sense.",
    "response": "How so?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How so?",
    "response": "Well in that movie universe, Brian is technically still alive and has just retired.  By that logic, why would they tribute the baby with Brian's name?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well in that movie universe, Brian is technically still alive and has just retired.  By that logic, why would they tribute the baby with Brian's name?",
    "response": "Oh wow that's actually an excellent point."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh wow that's actually an excellent point.",
    "response": "I think it would have made more sense to name the baby, Paul."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think it would have made more sense to name the baby, Paul.",
    "response": "I agree.  That way, it is a tribute to Paul Walker but it also makes sense in terms of the movie's story."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you like the Fast & Furious movies",
    "response": "I did, up until number 6.  They just got too crazy."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I did, up until number 6.  They just got too crazy.",
    "response": "I agree.  They are what got me into cars."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I agree.  They are what got me into cars.",
    "response": "Yeah, they were so cheesy but it helped get a whole new generation into the car scene."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, they were so cheesy but it helped get a whole new generation into the car scene.",
    "response": "Yep, I was even crazy enough to get street-glow on my car"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yep, I was even crazy enough to get street-glow on my car",
    "response": "Oh, I am so sorry.  You must regret that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh, I am so sorry.  You must regret that.",
    "response": "I really do.  Have you seen the new one yet?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I really do.  Have you seen the new one yet?",
    "response": "No I haven't.  I doubt I will."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No I haven't.  I doubt I will.",
    "response": "It's just not the same without Paul."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It's just not the same without Paul.",
    "response": "I agree.  They need to stop making them."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What did you think of the latest Fast and Furious movie?",
    "response": "I only saw the first movie.  I hated it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I only saw the first movie.  I hated it.",
    "response": "I think that they should have stopped with the third movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think that they should have stopped with the third movie.",
    "response": "I think they should have not made the first one. Vin Diesel has no acting talent."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think they should have not made the first one. Vin Diesel has no acting talent.",
    "response": "I agree. Vin Diesel has muscles and that's it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I agree. Vin Diesel has muscles and that's it.",
    "response": "Paul Walker was decent though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Paul Walker was decent though.",
    "response": "I thought Paul Walker was good as well."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I thought Paul Walker was good as well.",
    "response": "The cars in those movies were not that impressive to me."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The cars in those movies were not that impressive to me.",
    "response": "I can think of a better way to waste 90 minutes."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I can think of a better way to waste 90 minutes.",
    "response": "Waste is right. Those movies were so boring."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The cars in the first movie are so old",
    "response": "What series"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What series",
    "response": "The fast and the furious"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The fast and the furious",
    "response": "Well the movie is over ten years old"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well the movie is over ten years old",
    "response": "Are you kidding me"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Are you kidding me",
    "response": "nope i am serious it is pretty old"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "nope i am serious it is pretty old",
    "response": "Wow that is surprising"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Wow that is surprising",
    "response": "Why"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why",
    "response": "Because it means it has lasted quite some time"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Because it means it has lasted quite some time",
    "response": "I know but thats also impressive"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You know what car I really want?",
    "response": "Ford Mustang."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Ford Mustang.",
    "response": "Yep. Fast back 1967."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yep. Fast back 1967.",
    "response": "They modded that up so it will have 500 HP for the movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They modded that up so it will have 500 HP for the movie.",
    "response": "That's a lot of horses."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's a lot of horses.",
    "response": "Did you know every single one of the mustangs used in the film survived? They were eventually auctioned off."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you know every single one of the mustangs used in the film survived? They were eventually auctioned off.",
    "response": "Are they even street legal? Thought they were like props or something."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Are they even street legal? Thought they were like props or something.",
    "response": "no these were real street legal cars, all modded up for the movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "no these were real street legal cars, all modded up for the movie.",
    "response": "I wonder how they went for?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I wonder how they went for?",
    "response": "They were auctioned off on ebay. They got between 14K to 22K for them"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you know which character I feel was underused in 'Fate of the Furious?'",
    "response": "Which character?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which character?",
    "response": "Ramsey."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Ramsey.",
    "response": "She was the character portrayed by Nathalie Emmanuel from 'Game of Thrones' right?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "She was the character portrayed by Nathalie Emmanuel from 'Game of Thrones' right?",
    "response": "Yea that's her.  She barely did anything in the last movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea that's her.  She barely did anything in the last movie.",
    "response": "I did notice that too.  She was almost just there for Tyrese and Tej to fight over."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I did notice that too.  She was almost just there for Tyrese and Tej to fight over.",
    "response": "Also, the fact that she is a super hacker is almost redundant."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Also, the fact that she is a super hacker is almost redundant.",
    "response": "Yea.  I mean why does the group need another hacker when Tej has already been doing everything else for them?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea.  I mean why does the group need another hacker when Tej has already been doing everything else for them?",
    "response": "I understood Ramsey's role in Furious 7, but they sort of shoehorned her in."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I understood Ramsey's role in Furious 7, but they sort of shoehorned her in.",
    "response": "I hope they utilize her character more in the next movie, as she is a phenomenal actress."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey.",
    "response": "Hi."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hi.",
    "response": "Do you like Fast and the Furious?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you like Fast and the Furious?",
    "response": "Yeah I guess so."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah I guess so.",
    "response": "Any one that stands out as the worst?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Any one that stands out as the worst?",
    "response": "The second one or third one is pretty bad."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The second one or third one is pretty bad.",
    "response": "I didn't like the one where they are in japan."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I didn't like the one where they are in japan.",
    "response": "That was 3 I think."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That was 3 I think.",
    "response": "Yeah that one was pretty bad."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah that one was pretty bad.",
    "response": "I agree."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you like Vin Diesel in the Fast and the Furious?",
    "response": "Oh yeah. He was so cool."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh yeah. He was so cool.",
    "response": "Is he in anything else?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is he in anything else?",
    "response": "Yeah, I remember him in Pitch Black"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, I remember him in Pitch Black",
    "response": "That was a cool movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That was a cool movie.",
    "response": "He brings that coolness to every role and he brought it to The Fast and the Furious."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He brings that coolness to every role and he brought it to The Fast and the Furious.",
    "response": "Did you like his car in part 1?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you like his car in part 1?",
    "response": "Yes, it was cool. I liked the red."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, it was cool. I liked the red.",
    "response": "Did you think his character would ever get killed off during the movies?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you think his character would ever get killed off during the movies?",
    "response": "I thought so, since he did some crazy things."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen the most recent Fast and Furious movie?",
    "response": "I haven't yet. I plan to, though. You saw it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I haven't yet. I plan to, though. You saw it?",
    "response": "I did. I wasn't sure if I was going to after Paul Walker's accident."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I did. I wasn't sure if I was going to after Paul Walker's accident.",
    "response": "That's kind of why I haven't seen it yet. I think it'll just be too sad."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's kind of why I haven't seen it yet. I think it'll just be too sad.",
    "response": "That's what I thought, too. And it was sad, for sure."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's what I thought, too. And it was sad, for sure.",
    "response": "I bet. The whole thing with the way he died is just so ironic."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I bet. The whole thing with the way he died is just so ironic.",
    "response": "I know. Too much like the movies, but no happy ending."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know. Too much like the movies, but no happy ending.",
    "response": "But the movie was good?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "But the movie was good?",
    "response": "It was. I actually feel better because they had a really beautiful tribute to Paul in it. It was very well-done and emotional."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was. I actually feel better because they had a really beautiful tribute to Paul in it. It was very well-done and emotional.",
    "response": "Wow, I really respect that they did that. He deserved it. He was a good guy."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How do you feel about the Fast & Furious series?",
    "response": "I love those movies. Honestly, it's my favorite film franchise ever."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I love those movies. Honestly, it's my favorite film franchise ever.",
    "response": "So you actually like the entire series, movie by movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "So you actually like the entire series, movie by movie?",
    "response": "Yes. Well, there's one thing that kind of bothers me."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes. Well, there's one thing that kind of bothers me.",
    "response": "What's that?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What's that?",
    "response": "Probably the naming. Over the years, they've had some pretty odd names."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Probably the naming. Over the years, they've had some pretty odd names.",
    "response": "The fourth one was literally just Fast & Furious, wasn't it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The fourth one was literally just Fast & Furious, wasn't it?",
    "response": "Yeah, that one has my least favorite title."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, that one has my least favorite title.",
    "response": "It's my least favorite everything."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It's my least favorite everything.",
    "response": "I can understand that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I watched Fast Five for the first time last night.",
    "response": "What did you think of it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What did you think of it?",
    "response": "I actually quite enjoyed it, I had never seen past the third one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I actually quite enjoyed it, I had never seen past the third one.",
    "response": "Did you watch the fourth as well?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you watch the fourth as well?",
    "response": "No, I heard it gets better around the fifth."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No, I heard it gets better around the fifth.",
    "response": "Yea, the franchise turns into an action movie instead of mainly about racing."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, the franchise turns into an action movie instead of mainly about racing.",
    "response": "Yea, that is exactly how I felt."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, that is exactly how I felt.",
    "response": "The sixth one is a lot like that too."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The sixth one is a lot like that too.",
    "response": "That was pretty smart of them to spin off the genre."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That was pretty smart of them to spin off the genre.",
    "response": "Yea, the movies have been getting pretty good compared to the originals."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What did you think of the new Fast & the Furious movie?",
    "response": "Honestly man they need to stop making them."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Honestly man they need to stop making them.",
    "response": "Why do you say that?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why do you say that?",
    "response": "Dude they've already run their course, now the movies are turning into nothing but cgi and b.s. scenes with fast cars!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Dude they've already run their course, now the movies are turning into nothing but cgi and b.s. scenes with fast cars!",
    "response": "You have a point. Which movie is your favorite though?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You have a point. Which movie is your favorite though?",
    "response": "The orginial one! Paul Walker in that first race scene was epic."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The orginial one! Paul Walker in that first race scene was epic.",
    "response": "You're talking about the one with Ludacris right? When Paul Walker jumps the bridge in his eclipse?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You're talking about the one with Ludacris right? When Paul Walker jumps the bridge in his eclipse?",
    "response": "Yes, that was probably one of the best racing scenes in any of the Fast movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, that was probably one of the best racing scenes in any of the Fast movies.",
    "response": "Oh man I don't know about that. Tokyo Drift had some pretty epic racing scenes too!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh man I don't know about that. Tokyo Drift had some pretty epic racing scenes too!",
    "response": "Ehh serisouly? That's my least favorite Fast & the Furious movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you like the first Fast & Furious movie?",
    "response": "Yes, it is my favorite."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, it is my favorite.",
    "response": "It is my favorite as well."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It is my favorite as well.",
    "response": "What is your favorite scene?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is your favorite scene?",
    "response": "I love when they are robbing the trucks."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I love when they are robbing the trucks.",
    "response": "Yeah, that is pretty action packed."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, that is pretty action packed.",
    "response": "I think the other movies are good but the first one is the best."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think the other movies are good but the first one is the best.",
    "response": "I would have to agree."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I would have to agree.",
    "response": "I think I have seen the movie at least ten times."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think I have seen the movie at least ten times.",
    "response": "I have as well."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I need more movies based on cars",
    "response": "Why do you say that bro"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why do you say that bro",
    "response": "Well their is only one series that comes to mind"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well their is only one series that comes to mind",
    "response": "What series"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What series",
    "response": "Fast and the furious"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Fast and the furious",
    "response": "but that is a pretty good series"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "but that is a pretty good series",
    "response": "it is so its a shame it is one of its kind"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "it is so its a shame it is one of its kind",
    "response": "Well nothing can compete with its quality"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well nothing can compete with its quality",
    "response": "The last one was the only bad one"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The last one was the only bad one",
    "response": "Even that one was not that bad"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How did you get into watching the Fast and Furious movies?",
    "response": "I am really into cars so of course I love those movies!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I am really into cars so of course I love those movies!",
    "response": "That's great!  Do you have a favorite one?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's great!  Do you have a favorite one?",
    "response": "Furious 7 is my all time favorite!  The whole sequence of them dropping the cars out of the back of an airplane was totally awesome!  The ending tribute to Paul Walker was also very nice!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Furious 7 is my all time favorite!  The whole sequence of them dropping the cars out of the back of an airplane was totally awesome!  The ending tribute to Paul Walker was also very nice!",
    "response": "I totally agree!  I was worried that the movies would not be as good without him but the latest one was still very good!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I totally agree!  I was worried that the movies would not be as good without him but the latest one was still very good!",
    "response": "I know!  They really know how to step those movies up!  The twist with Alana being captured and then later killed really was a shock to me!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know!  They really know how to step those movies up!  The twist with Alana being captured and then later killed really was a shock to me!",
    "response": "I know!  It was really cool to see Dominic being bad but at the same time it was sad!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know!  It was really cool to see Dominic being bad but at the same time it was sad!",
    "response": "Yes!!  I thought Charlize Theron did a very good job playing a villian!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes!!  I thought Charlize Theron did a very good job playing a villian!",
    "response": "For sure!  The fact that she's hot is a plus!  I love that they also brought both Shaw brothers into the mix!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "For sure!  The fact that she's hot is a plus!  I love that they also brought both Shaw brothers into the mix!",
    "response": "I agree!  That made the movie that more exciting!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "My favorite fast and furious movie is fast five",
    "response": "When did that one come out"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When did that one come out",
    "response": "In 2011"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "In 2011",
    "response": "Wheres that one take place"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Wheres that one take place",
    "response": "Rio di jianaro"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Rio di jianaro",
    "response": "Oh okay, i think i remember that one"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh okay, i think i remember that one",
    "response": "I think its the best one"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think its the best one",
    "response": "Its the one after they got dom out of custody, right?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Its the one after they got dom out of custody, right?",
    "response": "Yes thats the one"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes thats the one",
    "response": "It was a good one"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you think Letti was actually dead ?",
    "response": "I never really questioned it until the 6th movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I never really questioned it until the 6th movie.",
    "response": "I was like what?!?!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I was like what?!?!",
    "response": "I know right. Such a plot twist."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know right. Such a plot twist.",
    "response": "I really like Letty so I'm glad they brought her back."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I really like Letty so I'm glad they brought her back.",
    "response": "Me too, she's such a strong character."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me too, she's such a strong character.",
    "response": "I was so sad to see she didn't remember Dom though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I was so sad to see she didn't remember Dom though.",
    "response": "At least she still falls in love with him again !"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "At least she still falls in love with him again !",
    "response": "True, that was a plus."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "True, that was a plus.",
    "response": "The poor cop lady he was with though. She basically got pushed to the side."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "do you like the fast series?",
    "response": "what's the 'fast' series?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "what's the 'fast' series?",
    "response": "the fast and the furious movie series, do you know it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "the fast and the furious movie series, do you know it?",
    "response": "yes, though i'm not concerned about tools"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "yes, though i'm not concerned about tools",
    "response": "what do you mean tools?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "what do you mean tools?",
    "response": "well i was under the impression the movies were regarding vehicles, is this correct?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "well i was under the impression the movies were regarding vehicles, is this correct?",
    "response": "yes, it's always got a car race or car chase scene"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "yes, it's always got a car race or car chase scene",
    "response": "a car is a vehicle, a vehicle is a tool"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "a car is a vehicle, a vehicle is a tool",
    "response": "do you think the fast and the furious are tool movies?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "do you think the fast and the furious are tool movies?",
    "response": "uhh, like all subjects in life, what i think is of no relevance;  the facts are clear"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Just saw Tokyo Drift, it sucked without Vin Diesel.",
    "response": "Doesn't he do a cameo at the end."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Doesn't he do a cameo at the end.",
    "response": "Drifting seems so lame compared to racing"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Drifting seems so lame compared to racing",
    "response": "I do love American muscle cars."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I do love American muscle cars.",
    "response": "I love how he kicks in the nitro at just the right moment."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I love how he kicks in the nitro at just the right moment.",
    "response": "He's unbeatable."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He's unbeatable.",
    "response": "That Dodge Charger makes me drool."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That Dodge Charger makes me drool.",
    "response": "I wonder if they have more than one to make the movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I wonder if they have more than one to make the movie.",
    "response": "I really like the sister character."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I really like the sister character.",
    "response": "She's cool."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I'm really impressed that the Fast & Furious movies are able to get such great actors to join the franchise.",
    "response": "Yeah, they really stepped it up ever since The Rock joined."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, they really stepped it up ever since The Rock joined.",
    "response": "He was the first one to bring that kind of outside star power into the franchise."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He was the first one to bring that kind of outside star power into the franchise.",
    "response": "'Fast Five' was probably my favorite one, and it had everything to do with The Rock."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "'Fast Five' was probably my favorite one, and it had everything to do with The Rock.",
    "response": "It's unbelievable that now, they have actors like Charlize Theron playing the main villain."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It's unbelievable that now, they have actors like Charlize Theron playing the main villain.",
    "response": "Yeah. I mean she's won an Oscar before."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah. I mean she's won an Oscar before.",
    "response": "Also, Kurt Russell as Mr. Nobody."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Also, Kurt Russell as Mr. Nobody.",
    "response": "I loved him in that role."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I loved him in that role.",
    "response": "I suppose if they can get Helen Mirren, they can get anyone."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I suppose if they can get Helen Mirren, they can get anyone.",
    "response": "That's right, I almost forgot about her!  I can't wait to see who they bring into the franchise next."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I've always felt that the Fast & Furious films have had great settings.",
    "response": "I can agree with that. The settings always add so much more to the movie overall."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I can agree with that. The settings always add so much more to the movie overall.",
    "response": "Absolutely. Do you have a favorite?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Absolutely. Do you have a favorite?",
    "response": "Yes. For me, it's Tokyo Drift."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes. For me, it's Tokyo Drift.",
    "response": "I wanted to say that too! I thought seeing them race through the streets of Japan looked absolutely gorgeous."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I wanted to say that too! I thought seeing them race through the streets of Japan looked absolutely gorgeous.",
    "response": "You took the words from my mouth there. It was a great experience."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You took the words from my mouth there. It was a great experience.",
    "response": "Do you have a second place for setting?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you have a second place for setting?",
    "response": "Well, because I absolutely love Dubai, I'm going to say Furious 7."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, because I absolutely love Dubai, I'm going to say Furious 7.",
    "response": "But that movie wasn't only in Dubai."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "But that movie wasn't only in Dubai.",
    "response": "That's true, but the time that they were in Dubai was great, I thought."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey, do you like the new Fast & Furious?",
    "response": "It was ok, I really miss Paul Walker through."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was ok, I really miss Paul Walker through.",
    "response": "Yes, that was a terrible shame."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, that was a terrible shame.",
    "response": "The last FF movie was so sad."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The last FF movie was so sad.",
    "response": "Yes, that song at the end literally had me in tears."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, that song at the end literally had me in tears.",
    "response": "What a beautiful man, such a shame."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What a beautiful man, such a shame.",
    "response": "I know right? But Vin Diesel is hott."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know right? But Vin Diesel is hott.",
    "response": "Heck yeah he is! I like the all the movies, they are all entertaining."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Heck yeah he is! I like the all the movies, they are all entertaining.",
    "response": "Yes, definately. Especially the special effects.."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, definately. Especially the special effects..",
    "response": "I can watch them all a few times each."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you catch the latest Fast and Furious, The Fate of the Furious?",
    "response": "I caught it last night!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I caught it last night!",
    "response": "That's great, I caught it a few weeks ago. What were your impressions of it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's great, I caught it a few weeks ago. What were your impressions of it?",
    "response": "I really enjoyed it. I liked Charlize Theron as the villain. She is so smooth."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I really enjoyed it. I liked Charlize Theron as the villain. She is so smooth.",
    "response": "She's definitely one of my favorites and it was fun to see her in the Fast and the Furious universe now. Cypher!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "She's definitely one of my favorites and it was fun to see her in the Fast and the Furious universe now. Cypher!",
    "response": "I was hoping to see more action sequences from her because you know she can do some really cool stunts. They kept her as more of the intellectual villain."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I was hoping to see more action sequences from her because you know she can do some really cool stunts. They kept her as more of the intellectual villain.",
    "response": "I loved her interactions with Dom and how she was manipulating his motivations to turn against his family and team."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I loved her interactions with Dom and how she was manipulating his motivations to turn against his family and team.",
    "response": "The whole movie I was trying to figure out what exactly did she have on him to make him turn considering he's probably the most loyal character in the series."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The whole movie I was trying to figure out what exactly did she have on him to make him turn considering he's probably the most loyal character in the series.",
    "response": "I know! I was guessing the whole way. I really enjoyed that mystery aspect of it, but let's not forget about the crazy action sequences!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know! I was guessing the whole way. I really enjoyed that mystery aspect of it, but let's not forget about the crazy action sequences!",
    "response": "I can't forget about that! That's why we go watch the Fast and the Furious!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you see Tokyo Drift.",
    "response": "Yes I did."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes I did.",
    "response": "I really liked it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I really liked it.",
    "response": "Yes I did too."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes I did too.",
    "response": "I wonder why it got bad reviews."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I wonder why it got bad reviews.",
    "response": "I thought the lead actor did a great job."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I thought the lead actor did a great job.",
    "response": "Yes I really enjoyed it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes I really enjoyed it.",
    "response": "Yes I like that it was filmed in Tokyo."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes I like that it was filmed in Tokyo.",
    "response": "Yes it was a great movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes it was a great movie.",
    "response": "Yes it was fun to watch."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you see the last Fast and Furious movie?",
    "response": "The Fate of the Furious, yeah like 4 times already."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The Fate of the Furious, yeah like 4 times already.",
    "response": "I just watched it for the first time last night."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I just watched it for the first time last night.",
    "response": "Ok, first question, how did you \"just\" see that movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Ok, first question, how did you \"just\" see that movie?",
    "response": "I know I'm super late, but I couldn't get a chance to see it in the theaters."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know I'm super late, but I couldn't get a chance to see it in the theaters.",
    "response": "Well anyway what did you think of the first part in Cuba?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well anyway what did you think of the first part in Cuba?",
    "response": "Where Dom freaking drove a car backward to win?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Where Dom freaking drove a car backward to win?",
    "response": "No, I mean where he drove a car backward, that had been ripped down to the studs, and was on fire?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No, I mean where he drove a car backward, that had been ripped down to the studs, and was on fire?",
    "response": "It is by far the best way to open that movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It is by far the best way to open that movie.",
    "response": "Are you kidding me, every action movie should open with that scene; not just racing ones, I mean action movies in general"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What did you think of the Fast and the Furious movies?",
    "response": "I thought they were ok."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I thought they were ok.",
    "response": "Why just ok?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why just ok?",
    "response": "I just miss Paul Walker.  I really watched those movies because of him."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I just miss Paul Walker.  I really watched those movies because of him.",
    "response": "Yea it's pretty sad that he's gone."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea it's pretty sad that he's gone.",
    "response": "It really is, he had great chemistry with Tyrese and Ludacris."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It really is, he had great chemistry with Tyrese and Ludacris.",
    "response": "Yea, he will be missed."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, he will be missed.",
    "response": "Definitely, without him I get a bit sad when watching the new films."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Definitely, without him I get a bit sad when watching the new films.",
    "response": "At least he has a legacy."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "At least he has a legacy.",
    "response": "Yea, those original movies were great."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "So did you see fate of furious?",
    "response": "Oh yes! What a great movie!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh yes! What a great movie!",
    "response": "Indeed! it was absolutely awesome!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Indeed! it was absolutely awesome!",
    "response": "The thing with fast and furious series that it gets better with each movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The thing with fast and furious series that it gets better with each movie.",
    "response": "I absolutely agree."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I absolutely agree.",
    "response": "I mean what a movie!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I mean what a movie!",
    "response": "I just loved the stunts. It just blew my mind!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I just loved the stunts. It just blew my mind!",
    "response": "So do you think there will be another fast and furious movie?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "So do you think there will be another fast and furious movie?",
    "response": "It's hard to say, because the title of last movie seems it's the end of series."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It's hard to say, because the title of last movie seems it's the end of series.",
    "response": "I wish they continue with the series."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Guess what movie I just watched last night?",
    "response": "No idea, lay it on me."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No idea, lay it on me.",
    "response": "The original Fast and the Furious was on TV."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The original Fast and the Furious was on TV.",
    "response": "Wow, I have not seen that movie since it was in the theaters."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Wow, I have not seen that movie since it was in the theaters.",
    "response": "Yea, it was out when we were in high school."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, it was out when we were in high school.",
    "response": "I can not believe it has been so long."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I can not believe it has been so long.",
    "response": "I really enjoyed it when I first watched it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I really enjoyed it when I first watched it.",
    "response": "Of course, we were all into cars and the modding culture."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Of course, we were all into cars and the modding culture.",
    "response": "That movie really did a lot for tuners."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That movie really did a lot for tuners.",
    "response": "Yea, it somewhat started the whole import craze here."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen the newest Fast and Furious movie?",
    "response": "I haven't actually. The Fate of the Furious, right?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I haven't actually. The Fate of the Furious, right?",
    "response": "Yeah! That is the one!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah! That is the one!",
    "response": "Was it any good?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Was it any good?",
    "response": "It wasn't my favorite, but I liked it quite a bit."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It wasn't my favorite, but I liked it quite a bit.",
    "response": "I just can't imagine the series without Brian."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I just can't imagine the series without Brian.",
    "response": "I know, it was pretty sad. Dom named his baby after him, though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know, it was pretty sad. Dom named his baby after him, though.",
    "response": "Dom has a baby!?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Dom has a baby!?",
    "response": "Oh shoot! I am sorry that I spoiled it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh shoot! I am sorry that I spoiled it.",
    "response": "It's okay. I will definitely have to watch it now!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That scene with the truck though in the movie is amazing",
    "response": "I love that scene it is so intense"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I love that scene it is so intense",
    "response": "I know is it something special"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know is it something special",
    "response": "I honestly thought something would go wrong"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I honestly thought something would go wrong",
    "response": "It was begging for something to go wrong"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was begging for something to go wrong",
    "response": "I know right"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know right",
    "response": "Just one of the best scenes in the whole series"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Just one of the best scenes in the whole series",
    "response": "I know i was expecting him to fall of the moving truck"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know i was expecting him to fall of the moving truck",
    "response": "Precisely what i thought"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Precisely what i thought",
    "response": "I know man it was tense"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When did the first Fast and Furious movie come out?",
    "response": "In 2001"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "In 2001",
    "response": "Wow, it has been around for a long time."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Wow, it has been around for a long time.",
    "response": "Yes, it has. It is a very lucrative franchise."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, it has. It is a very lucrative franchise.",
    "response": "Is The Rock in part 1?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is The Rock in part 1?",
    "response": "No, that one is just Paul Walker and Vin Diesel."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No, that one is just Paul Walker and Vin Diesel.",
    "response": "Who directed part 1?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who directed part 1?",
    "response": "Rob Cohen"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Rob Cohen",
    "response": "Is part 1 the best?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is part 1 the best?",
    "response": "By far."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What about fast & furious makes you want to watch it?",
    "response": "Action packed and all my favorite characters."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Action packed and all my favorite characters.",
    "response": "What about the action makes you thrilled to see it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What about the action makes you thrilled to see it?",
    "response": "It makes you feel like you are there, and makes you want to start racing like them."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It makes you feel like you are there, and makes you want to start racing like them.",
    "response": "How many of the fils did you currently see?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How many of the fils did you currently see?",
    "response": "The first, second and two others and not sure of there names."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The first, second and two others and not sure of there names.",
    "response": "What was you favorite scene in fast & furious"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What was you favorite scene in fast & furious",
    "response": "The first movie where all the cars pull up nd they switch vehicles to escape the cops. Loved it"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The first movie where all the cars pull up nd they switch vehicles to escape the cops. Loved it",
    "response": "Does fast & furious ever bring memories to your life?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Does fast & furious ever bring memories to your life?",
    "response": "My father works on cars and loves to rev engines. Everytime he revs an engine, i think of the movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen Fate of the Furious yet?",
    "response": "No I haven't, how many have there been now?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No I haven't, how many have there been now?",
    "response": "That is the eighth one, came out not too long ago."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That is the eighth one, came out not too long ago.",
    "response": "I have not seen any since Tokyo Drift?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I have not seen any since Tokyo Drift?",
    "response": "You stopped right when it starts to get good."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You stopped right when it starts to get good.",
    "response": "Really?  It felt like it was getting so bad."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Really?  It felt like it was getting so bad.",
    "response": "I think the fifth and the sixth were the best."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think the fifth and the sixth were the best.",
    "response": "The third was really bad."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The third was really bad.",
    "response": "Yea, they became more entertaining and more action movies after that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, they became more entertaining and more action movies after that.",
    "response": "Maybe I will go back and watch some."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you see the last Fast and Furious movie?",
    "response": "No not yet.  Whats that one called again?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No not yet.  Whats that one called again?",
    "response": "Its called The Fate of the Furious."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Its called The Fate of the Furious.",
    "response": "Do you think that's going to be the last one?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you think that's going to be the last one?",
    "response": "I'm not sure.  I think they said it would be the last one but they seem to just keep churning them out."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I'm not sure.  I think they said it would be the last one but they seem to just keep churning them out.",
    "response": "It was really sad when Paul Walker died."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was really sad when Paul Walker died.",
    "response": "It was.  I really liked the ending of Fast and Furious 7 where they did kind of like a little tribute to him."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was.  I really liked the ending of Fast and Furious 7 where they did kind of like a little tribute to him.",
    "response": "Oh yeah that was really cool.  I wonder how they did those scenes since he was already dead?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh yeah that was really cool.  I wonder how they did those scenes since he was already dead?",
    "response": "I think they used a lot of CGI but I know his brothers stepped in and filmed some for him."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think they used a lot of CGI but I know his brothers stepped in and filmed some for him.",
    "response": "That's so cool that they can do stuff like that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you see the first movie in the Fast and Furious series?",
    "response": "Oh yes, back when it was first released!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh yes, back when it was first released!",
    "response": "Who was your favorite character?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who was your favorite character?",
    "response": "Brian - who was yours?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Brian - who was yours?",
    "response": "I really like Letty.  She is the only one who can contain Dom."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I really like Letty.  She is the only one who can contain Dom.",
    "response": "She's not the only one, Brian really reigned in him too."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "She's not the only one, Brian really reigned in him too.",
    "response": "But, Brian let him go at the end."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "But, Brian let him go at the end.",
    "response": "That is true, but they did team up again in later movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That is true, but they did team up again in later movies.",
    "response": "The soundtrack for the first will always be my favorite though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The soundtrack for the first will always be my favorite though.",
    "response": "I still like the soundtrack from the seventh movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Was that street race intense in part 1?",
    "response": "You mean the one where Paul Walker lost his car?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You mean the one where Paul Walker lost his car?",
    "response": "Yes."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes.",
    "response": "I loved that scene. I thought for sure he would win."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I loved that scene. I thought for sure he would win.",
    "response": "The first Fast and the Furious was so good."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The first Fast and the Furious was so good.",
    "response": "Yeah, especially that scene."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, especially that scene.",
    "response": "When his laptop told him the car was in danger, I knew he was not going to win."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When his laptop told him the car was in danger, I knew he was not going to win.",
    "response": "I agree."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I agree.",
    "response": "Vin Diesel was definitely gonna win that race from the start."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Vin Diesel was definitely gonna win that race from the start.",
    "response": "It was fun to watch though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you like the fast and the furious?",
    "response": "Yes i love those movies"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes i love those movies",
    "response": "I do too"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I do too",
    "response": "They are so exciting and well made"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They are so exciting and well made",
    "response": "And vin diesel is hot"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "And vin diesel is hot",
    "response": "He is really hot"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He is really hot",
    "response": "I love watching him in them"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I love watching him in them",
    "response": "He looks so good"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "He looks so good",
    "response": "And hes really manly"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "And hes really manly",
    "response": "Yes he is"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I love the Fast and Furious original.",
    "response": "Its the best one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Its the best one.",
    "response": "They were so young looking."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They were so young looking.",
    "response": "It was so cool to see it for the first time."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was so cool to see it for the first time.",
    "response": "The ending was awesome."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The ending was awesome.",
    "response": "That old muscle car was powerful."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That old muscle car was powerful.",
    "response": "It did a wheelie off the line."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It did a wheelie off the line.",
    "response": "I liked that he didnt get caught."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I liked that he didnt get caught.",
    "response": "The cop let him go."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The cop let him go.",
    "response": "He risked his job for his friend."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You've seen Fast & Furious movies right?",
    "response": "Yes, it's some of my favorite movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, it's some of my favorite movies.",
    "response": "Do you remember when Roman Pierce was in a demolition derby?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you remember when Roman Pierce was in a demolition derby?",
    "response": "Yes I do, why?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes I do, why?",
    "response": "Well I was talking to a friend and wanted to settle something."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well I was talking to a friend and wanted to settle something.",
    "response": "Alright, well ask away."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Alright, well ask away.",
    "response": "Did he bring his trailer to the derby and wasn't he also on house arrest?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did he bring his trailer to the derby and wasn't he also on house arrest?",
    "response": "Yes and yes, that's why he had to bring his home with him so he could race."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes and yes, that's why he had to bring his home with him so he could race.",
    "response": "That's what I told my friend but he thought I was wrong."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's what I told my friend but he thought I was wrong.",
    "response": "Well your friend is wrong then."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen The Fate of the Furious?",
    "response": "No, not yet. I'm dying to. I love those movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No, not yet. I'm dying to. I love those movies.",
    "response": "I heard that it's one of the most expensive movies ever made."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I heard that it's one of the most expensive movies ever made.",
    "response": "I can't imagine the price tag. But it's killing at the box office, I'm sure."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I can't imagine the price tag. But it's killing at the box office, I'm sure.",
    "response": "Remember the first one that came out?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Remember the first one that came out?",
    "response": "Of course! I can't believe that came out, like, 16 years ago."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Of course! I can't believe that came out, like, 16 years ago.",
    "response": "Vin Diesel was astonishing in that one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Vin Diesel was astonishing in that one.",
    "response": "I was hooked from the very beginning. Totally. Blew me away."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I was hooked from the very beginning. Totally. Blew me away.",
    "response": "Now I have the watch the first one again. Maybe tonight!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Now I have the watch the first one again. Maybe tonight!",
    "response": "Sounds like a plan."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How many of The Fast and the Furious movies have you seen?",
    "response": "All of them."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "All of them.",
    "response": "What do you think of The Rock's character."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What do you think of The Rock's character.",
    "response": "i really like him, I think he brought a much needed outside element to the movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "i really like him, I think he brought a much needed outside element to the movie.",
    "response": "How so?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How so?",
    "response": "Well they already had big name stars, but they didnt really have that cop presence since Brian became part of the team."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well they already had big name stars, but they didnt really have that cop presence since Brian became part of the team.",
    "response": "I see, so you think he legitimized it a little?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I see, so you think he legitimized it a little?",
    "response": "I do. I think he added credibility to a franchise quickly losing it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I do. I think he added credibility to a franchise quickly losing it.",
    "response": "I think you'e right, he fights well too."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think you'e right, he fights well too.",
    "response": "Yea, i liked how they incorporated some of his WWE stuff in there too."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What's your favorite Fast and Furious movie?",
    "response": "The original for sure."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The original for sure.",
    "response": "I like the Furious 7."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like the Furious 7.",
    "response": "They were all good."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They were all good.",
    "response": "Who was your favorite character?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who was your favorite character?",
    "response": "Paul Walker for sure."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Paul Walker for sure.",
    "response": "I like Vin Diesel."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like Vin Diesel.",
    "response": "I heard he is short and wears lifts in his shoes."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I heard he is short and wears lifts in his shoes.",
    "response": "Too bad that Paul Walker died."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Too bad that Paul Walker died.",
    "response": "Yeah but he went out doing what he loved."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I just watched the Fast and the Furious series for the first time.",
    "response": "What did you think of it. I love those movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What did you think of it. I love those movies.",
    "response": "I really liked them. There was one I wasn't thrilled about though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I really liked them. There was one I wasn't thrilled about though.",
    "response": "Which one was that?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which one was that?",
    "response": "I wasn't a big fan of Tokyo Drift."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I wasn't a big fan of Tokyo Drift.",
    "response": "Really?! That is one of my favorites."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Really?! That is one of my favorites.",
    "response": "I know, I hear that from a lot of people. I just feel it is kind of thrown in and doesn't really go with the rest of the series."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I know, I hear that from a lot of people. I just feel it is kind of thrown in and doesn't really go with the rest of the series.",
    "response": "Ya I guess I can see that. I really like the main character though."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Ya I guess I can see that. I really like the main character though.",
    "response": "Ya he is ok. The best thing for me out of this movie was the introduction of Han."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Ya he is ok. The best thing for me out of this movie was the introduction of Han.",
    "response": "Oh ya definitely. He is one of my favorites."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What did you think about Fast 8?",
    "response": "I thought it was okay, a little over the top if you ask me. I thought Fast 8 was better."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I thought it was okay, a little over the top if you ask me. I thought Fast 8 was better.",
    "response": "Why do you say that?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Why do you say that?",
    "response": "Well, the part where all the cars were dropping from the above parking garage and the auto driving cars causing havoc in the city, that was a little too cheesy."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well, the part where all the cars were dropping from the above parking garage and the auto driving cars causing havoc in the city, that was a little too cheesy.",
    "response": "Yea, I guess I agree a bit but that's how these movies usually are.  The storyline wasn't as good either."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea, I guess I agree a bit but that's how these movies usually are.  The storyline wasn't as good either.",
    "response": "Also, the part where they had 5 cars latched onto Dom's car trying to take it apart yet it remained steady.  A bit unbelievable."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Also, the part where they had 5 cars latched onto Dom's car trying to take it apart yet it remained steady.  A bit unbelievable.",
    "response": "I like how they worked Jason Statham into the story and he eventually became a good guy."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like how they worked Jason Statham into the story and he eventually became a good guy.",
    "response": "Yea probably.  I think they're going to have a story where Jason Statham is part of the team in Fast 9"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea probably.  I think they're going to have a story where Jason Statham is part of the team in Fast 9",
    "response": "You think there will be a Fast 9?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You think there will be a Fast 9?",
    "response": "Yes, the movie franchise is on a roll right now."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you hear they are planning on making more Fast and the Furious movies?",
    "response": "Wow, how long are they going to milk that franchise?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Wow, how long are they going to milk that franchise?",
    "response": "It is still going strong, one of the most popular action movie series."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It is still going strong, one of the most popular action movie series.",
    "response": "They should really consider ending it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They should really consider ending it.",
    "response": "Have you been watching the newer ones?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you been watching the newer ones?",
    "response": "No I have not."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No I have not.",
    "response": "They are actually really good, better than the originals."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They are actually really good, better than the originals.",
    "response": "The originals were terrible so no surprise there."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The originals were terrible so no surprise there.",
    "response": "I think the new ones are coming out in 2019 and 2021."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think the new ones are coming out in 2019 and 2021.",
    "response": "That is still so far away, they already announced that?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What's the most underrated Fast & Furious movie, in your opinion?",
    "response": "I think it's 2 Fast 2 Furious."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think it's 2 Fast 2 Furious.",
    "response": "Hmm, interesting choice. Any reason why?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hmm, interesting choice. Any reason why?",
    "response": "People tend to overlook it because it doesn't feature Vin Diesel."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "People tend to overlook it because it doesn't feature Vin Diesel.",
    "response": "Oh yeah, it starred Tyrese as the sidekick right."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh yeah, it starred Tyrese as the sidekick right.",
    "response": "Yeah, Tyrese was able to inject more humor into the movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, Tyrese was able to inject more humor into the movie.",
    "response": "It makes sense that they brought him back for future movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It makes sense that they brought him back for future movies.",
    "response": "Exactly. The chemistry between Paul Walker and Tyrese was undeniable."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Exactly. The chemistry between Paul Walker and Tyrese was undeniable.",
    "response": "I guess people dislike the movie because of its ridiculous plot, but that ridiculousness would be the hallmark of the franchise."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I guess people dislike the movie because of its ridiculous plot, but that ridiculousness would be the hallmark of the franchise.",
    "response": "Yeah, it was the precursor to the later movies, where insane plot lines are the norm."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I just saw Fast Five.",
    "response": "Who directed it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who directed it?",
    "response": "Justin Lin."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Justin Lin.",
    "response": "Any new actors?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Any new actors?",
    "response": "Dwayne Johnson plays a cop."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Dwayne Johnson plays a cop.",
    "response": "Wow, the Rock.  What happens?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Wow, the Rock.  What happens?",
    "response": "Diesel and Walker steal $100M from a drug lord."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Diesel and Walker steal $100M from a drug lord.",
    "response": "They seem to steal from drug lords a lot."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They seem to steal from drug lords a lot.",
    "response": "Yes, they do.  Johnson lets the pair go off."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, they do.  Johnson lets the pair go off.",
    "response": "Very predictable."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Whats your favorite movie series?",
    "response": "Definitely the fast and the furious"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Definitely the fast and the furious",
    "response": "Thats mine too"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Thats mine too",
    "response": "Vin diesel and paul walker are awesome together"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Vin diesel and paul walker are awesome together",
    "response": "They do make a great team"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They do make a great team",
    "response": "I love watching their chemistry"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I love watching their chemistry",
    "response": "Plus they are both great actors"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Plus they are both great actors",
    "response": "And they are both so perfect for the movies"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "And they are both so perfect for the movies",
    "response": "Exactly it seems like those movies were made for them"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Exactly it seems like those movies were made for them",
    "response": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hi.",
    "response": "Hey."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Hey.",
    "response": "Have you seen the fast and furious movies?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have you seen the fast and furious movies?",
    "response": "Yeah I've seen a few."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah I've seen a few.",
    "response": "Have a favorite?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Have a favorite?",
    "response": "I like the 4th one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like the 4th one.",
    "response": "That the one with the cartel?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That the one with the cartel?",
    "response": "Yeah."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah.",
    "response": "That one was pretty good."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That one was pretty good.",
    "response": "I enjoyed it the most."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you know what year the movie \"Fast & Furious \" came out?",
    "response": "I believe it came out in 2009.  It was right after Tokyo Drift."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I believe it came out in 2009.  It was right after Tokyo Drift.",
    "response": "I believe this was Paul Walker's best acting performance when speaking of the fast and furious movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I believe this was Paul Walker's best acting performance when speaking of the fast and furious movies.",
    "response": "I agree with you. He was really strong in this movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I agree with you. He was really strong in this movie.",
    "response": "I also think Michelle Rodriquez did well in this movie. She matched well with Vin Diesel."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I also think Michelle Rodriquez did well in this movie. She matched well with Vin Diesel.",
    "response": "That is so true. They look like a match made in heaven. They were so into each other."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That is so true. They look like a match made in heaven. They were so into each other.",
    "response": "Did you see the types of cars they use in this movie? I was really feeling the Buick GNX."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you see the types of cars they use in this movie? I was really feeling the Buick GNX.",
    "response": "It was a nice car but I liked the Nissan Skyline R34 GT-R that  was in the movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was a nice car but I liked the Nissan Skyline R34 GT-R that  was in the movie.",
    "response": "I'm sure they enjoyed driving those cars. It sure looks like a lot of fun."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I'm sure they enjoyed driving those cars. It sure looks like a lot of fun.",
    "response": "Tell me about it. I need all those cars in my life some day."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you remember the truck heist from Fast & Furious 4?",
    "response": "Yes of course, who doesn't?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes of course, who doesn't?",
    "response": "Didn't the driver of the truck have an iguana?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Didn't the driver of the truck have an iguana?",
    "response": "Yes he did and hit ate a piece of chocolate."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes he did and hit ate a piece of chocolate.",
    "response": "That's crazy I didn't know Iguanas ate chocolate."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's crazy I didn't know Iguanas ate chocolate.",
    "response": "Me either could just be for the scene."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Me either could just be for the scene.",
    "response": "I liked the part when the truck blew up and rolled down the road and Dom sped up and drove under it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I liked the part when the truck blew up and rolled down the road and Dom sped up and drove under it.",
    "response": "I loved that scene I thought they would be crushed."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I loved that scene I thought they would be crushed.",
    "response": "I think that's my favorite scene of that specific movie."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think that's my favorite scene of that specific movie.",
    "response": "Yeah it was very well done."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Which Fast and the Furious did you think had the best car chases or races?",
    "response": "I think the original The Fast and The Furious had the best. It was actually a racing movie with a heist background."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I think the original The Fast and The Furious had the best. It was actually a racing movie with a heist background.",
    "response": "That's true, the original had I think three actual races. The first street race at night, the desert race battles, and then there was that race with the Ferrari guy."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's true, the original had I think three actual races. The first street race at night, the desert race battles, and then there was that race with the Ferrari guy.",
    "response": "That guy had one of the best lines in the series, \"More than you can afford pal, Ferrari.\""
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That guy had one of the best lines in the series, \"More than you can afford pal, Ferrari.\"",
    "response": "Then Dom tells Brian to smoke him in that legendary orange Toyota Supra."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Then Dom tells Brian to smoke him in that legendary orange Toyota Supra.",
    "response": "If you go back to watch the original The Fast and The Furious, you'd be surprise at how many great one liners you'll be able to recite."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "If you go back to watch the original The Fast and The Furious, you'd be surprise at how many great one liners you'll be able to recite.",
    "response": "Nobody comes here for the tuna! I kind of miss those early characters, Vince and Jesse."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Nobody comes here for the tuna! I kind of miss those early characters, Vince and Jesse.",
    "response": "Well Vince made a return and redeemed himself later in the series which was cool, but Jesse died! He got shot up at the end remember?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Well Vince made a return and redeemed himself later in the series which was cool, but Jesse died! He got shot up at the end remember?",
    "response": "That's right how could I forget about Jesse's unfortunate murder."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's right how could I forget about Jesse's unfortunate murder.",
    "response": "They need to keep the core characters that are there now, people need Dom obviously, but now you can't take away the Rock from us."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What the hell happened to the Fast and Furious movie series?",
    "response": "What are you talking about?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What are you talking about?",
    "response": "It use to be about cool cars and racing."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It use to be about cool cars and racing.",
    "response": "It's still about that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It's still about that.",
    "response": "No, now they are on some Oceans 11 bank robbery stuff."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No, now they are on some Oceans 11 bank robbery stuff.",
    "response": "Yeah, I can see why you think that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, I can see why you think that.",
    "response": "What do you think was the worst one?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What do you think was the worst one?",
    "response": "Easy, that's Tokyo Drift."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Easy, that's Tokyo Drift.",
    "response": "Is that the one with Lil Bow Wow?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Is that the one with Lil Bow Wow?",
    "response": "That's the one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "So I heard that the Fast & Furious series is going all the way up to ten?",
    "response": "Wait, ten what?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Wait, ten what?",
    "response": "Ten films. They announced around the sixth one that they were going all the way to ten."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Ten films. They announced around the sixth one that they were going all the way to ten.",
    "response": "Oh, really? That's interesting."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Oh, really? That's interesting.",
    "response": "Yeah, I'm just curious to see where they;ll take the story."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, I'm just curious to see where they;ll take the story.",
    "response": "I'd like to think that they'll retire all of the characters."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I'd like to think that they'll retire all of the characters.",
    "response": "As in the same way they did with Brian's character?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "As in the same way they did with Brian's character?",
    "response": "Yeah. Just write them into normal lives."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah. Just write them into normal lives.",
    "response": "I can't help but think they're going to kill somebody off."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I can't help but think they're going to kill somebody off.",
    "response": "That's a bit morbid."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Did you see the first Fast and Furious short film?",
    "response": "What do you mean by short film?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What do you mean by short film?",
    "response": "There were two short films released outside of the movies."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "There were two short films released outside of the movies.",
    "response": "I do not believe I have seen either, when did they come out?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I do not believe I have seen either, when did they come out?",
    "response": "One in 2003 one in 2009."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "One in 2003 one in 2009.",
    "response": "No I have not seen either."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "No I have not seen either.",
    "response": "The Turbo Charged Prelude for 2 Fast 2 Furious was the first."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The Turbo Charged Prelude for 2 Fast 2 Furious was the first.",
    "response": "That is a long name, at least I know what it is about."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That is a long name, at least I know what it is about.",
    "response": "Yea it pretty much bridges the first and second films."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yea it pretty much bridges the first and second films.",
    "response": "I had no idea it even existed."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What Fast & Furious movie was Jesse in?",
    "response": "The first one: The Fast & The Furious"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "The first one: The Fast & The Furious",
    "response": "Where does 2 Fast 2 Furious take place"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Where does 2 Fast 2 Furious take place",
    "response": "That's the one in Miami, Florida"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That's the one in Miami, Florida",
    "response": "What car does Brian finally beat Dom in?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What car does Brian finally beat Dom in?",
    "response": "2011 Dodge Charger in Fast 5"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "2011 Dodge Charger in Fast 5",
    "response": "What was Dom's girlfriends name in The Fast & The Furious"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What was Dom's girlfriends name in The Fast & The Furious",
    "response": "Letty"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Letty",
    "response": "Who drove the purple gen 3 Mitsubishi Eclipse in 2 Fast 2 Furious"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Who drove the purple gen 3 Mitsubishi Eclipse in 2 Fast 2 Furious",
    "response": "That's Brian's childhood friend Roman Pierce"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You know what really upset me about Fast & Furious 6?",
    "response": "What disappointed you?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What disappointed you?",
    "response": "I feel like the characters totally forgot about Gisele at the end."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I feel like the characters totally forgot about Gisele at the end.",
    "response": "Wow.  Now that you mention it, they totally glossed over that."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Wow.  Now that you mention it, they totally glossed over that.",
    "response": "One of their crew members died, but they seemed so happy about celebrating when they got Mia back."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "One of their crew members died, but they seemed so happy about celebrating when they got Mia back.",
    "response": "That was very uncharacteristic of the crew to forget a family member."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That was very uncharacteristic of the crew to forget a family member.",
    "response": "They should have at least had a moment of silence for Gisele.  Especially since she died sacrificing herself for Han."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "They should have at least had a moment of silence for Gisele.  Especially since she died sacrificing herself for Han.",
    "response": "That made me angry as well.  By the way, you realize who the actress who portrayed Gisele was?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That made me angry as well.  By the way, you realize who the actress who portrayed Gisele was?",
    "response": "Yeah, it was Gal Gadot!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, it was Gal Gadot!",
    "response": "I guess we can't be too sad about her leaving the franchise, now that she's Wonder Woman."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What did you think of the Fast & Furious movies?",
    "response": "I liked them, but it was really sad when Paul Walker died."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I liked them, but it was really sad when Paul Walker died.",
    "response": "Yes it definitely was sad. I was glad they were able to complete the last film anyway."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes it definitely was sad. I was glad they were able to complete the last film anyway.",
    "response": "Yes, it was a nice tribute to him to finish the movie with him CGI'd in it."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yes, it was a nice tribute to him to finish the movie with him CGI'd in it.",
    "response": "But did it seem realistic? Knowing he'd died and all?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "But did it seem realistic? Knowing he'd died and all?",
    "response": "It was somewhat unrealistic, I have to admit. You could tell where they made changes."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was somewhat unrealistic, I have to admit. You could tell where they made changes.",
    "response": "You definitely could see the changes. Who is your favorite actor in the series?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "You definitely could see the changes. Who is your favorite actor in the series?",
    "response": "I love Vin Diesel! He's so good in it!"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I love Vin Diesel! He's so good in it!",
    "response": "I like him, too. He's funny, serious, action packed. He can do it all."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I like him, too. He's funny, serious, action packed. He can do it all.",
    "response": "Yes, he certainly is versatile in his acting abilities. It's a great series for sure."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Do you think there will be another Fast and the Furious movie?",
    "response": "I just watched the current one and it really seems like there is opportunity for another one."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I just watched the current one and it really seems like there is opportunity for another one.",
    "response": "How did you like it?"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "How did you like it?",
    "response": "It was pretty good. I didn't think it would be but it was full of great actors."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "It was pretty good. I didn't think it would be but it was full of great actors.",
    "response": "I really love Jason Statham. He was supposed to be a bad guy but I kind of cried when I thought he died."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I really love Jason Statham. He was supposed to be a bad guy but I kind of cried when I thought he died.",
    "response": "That was horrible. I thought Dom had turned to the bad side and Jason Statham was becoming a good guy."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That was horrible. I thought Dom had turned to the bad side and Jason Statham was becoming a good guy.",
    "response": "I thought it was so cute the way Jason Statham rescued Dom's baby."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "I thought it was so cute the way Jason Statham rescued Dom's baby.",
    "response": "That baby was adorable. He was right on cue with whatever was said."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "That baby was adorable. He was right on cue with whatever was said.",
    "response": "Yeah, and then Letty was so accepting of the baby."
  },
  {
    "prompt": "Yeah, and then Letty was so accepting of the baby.",
    "response": "I can't wait to see what happens in the next movie if they make another one."
  }
]